signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.7V delay:21ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:0.0m Distance:1.3m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:23
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.7V delay:25ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:0.0m Distance:1.4m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:23
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.7V delay:26ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:0.0m Distance:1.4m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:23
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.7V delay:27ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:0.0m Distance:1.4m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:23
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.8V delay:26ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:0.0m Distance:1.4m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:23
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.8V delay:27ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:0.0m Distance:1.4m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:23
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.8V delay:24ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:0.0m Distance:1.4m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:23
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.8V delay:23ms bitrate:50.5Mbps Height:0.0m Distance:1.4m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:23
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.8V delay:24ms bitrate:50.5Mbps Height:0.0m Distance:1.4m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:23
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.8V delay:25ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:0.0m Distance:1.4m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:23
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.8V delay:27ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:0.0m Distance:1.4m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:23
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.6V delay:21ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:0.0m Distance:1.4m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:23
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.6V delay:23ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:0.0m Distance:1.4m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:23
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.6V delay:24ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:0.0m Distance:1.4m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:23
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.6V delay:25ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:0.0m Distance:1.4m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:23
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.6V delay:27ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:0.0m Distance:1.4m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:23
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.6V delay:21ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:0.0m Distance:1.4m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:23
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.6V delay:25ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:0.0m Distance:1.5m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:23
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.9V delay:24ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:0.0m Distance:1.5m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:23
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.9V delay:25ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:0.0m Distance:1.5m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:23
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.9V delay:26ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:0.0m Distance:1.5m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:23
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.9V delay:28ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:0.0m Distance:1.5m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:23
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.9V delay:29ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:0.0m Distance:1.5m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:23
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.9V delay:20ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:0.0m Distance:1.5m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:23
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:25ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:0.0m Distance:1.5m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:23
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:26ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:0.0m Distance:1.5m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:23
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:22ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:0.0m Distance:1.5m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:23
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:23ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:0.0m Distance:1.6m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:23
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:26ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:0.0m Distance:1.6m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:23
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:24ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:0.0m Distance:1.6m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:23
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:26ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:0.0m Distance:1.6m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:22
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:30ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:0.0m Distance:1.6m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:22
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:25ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:0.0m Distance:1.6m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:22
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:26ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:0.0m Distance:1.6m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:22
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:27ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:0.0m Distance:1.7m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:22
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.6V delay:25ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:0.0m Distance:1.7m HS:0.1m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:22
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.6V delay:30ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:0.0m Distance:1.7m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:22
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.6V delay:24ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:0.0m Distance:1.7m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:22
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.6V delay:26ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:0.0m Distance:1.7m HS:0.1m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:22
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.6V delay:24ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:0.0m Distance:0.0m HS:0.1m/s VS:0.3m/s gpsNum:22
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.6V delay:25ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:0.1m Distance:0.0m HS:0.1m/s VS:1.0m/s gpsNum:22
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.6V delay:27ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:0.1m Distance:0.0m HS:0.1m/s VS:1.0m/s gpsNum:22
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.5V delay:28ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:0.3m Distance:0.0m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.7m/s gpsNum:23
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.5V delay:24ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:0.7m Distance:0.0m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.8m/s gpsNum:24
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.5V delay:31ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:1.1m Distance:0.1m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.4m/s gpsNum:24
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.5V delay:25ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:1.1m Distance:0.1m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.4m/s gpsNum:24
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.5V delay:26ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:1.4m Distance:0.0m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.0m/s gpsNum:23
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.5V delay:28ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:1.6m Distance:0.0m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.8m/s gpsNum:23
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.5V delay:25ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:1.8m Distance:0.1m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.7m/s gpsNum:23
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.4V delay:24ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:1.9m Distance:0.1m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.7m/s gpsNum:24
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.4V delay:25ms bitrate:50.2Mbps Height:1.9m Distance:0.1m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.7m/s gpsNum:24
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.4V delay:26ms bitrate:50.2Mbps Height:2.0m Distance:0.2m HS:0.1m/s VS:0.4m/s gpsNum:25
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.4V delay:29ms bitrate:50.4Mbps Height:2.1m Distance:0.2m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.3m/s gpsNum:25
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.4V delay:29ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:2.1m Distance:0.2m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.3m/s gpsNum:25
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.4V delay:30ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:2.2m Distance:0.2m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.3m/s gpsNum:25
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.5V delay:25ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:2.2m Distance:0.2m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.1m/s gpsNum:25
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.5V delay:26ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:2.3m Distance:0.3m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:25
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.5V delay:24ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:2.2m Distance:0.3m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:25
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.5V delay:29ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:2.2m Distance:0.3m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:25
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.5V delay:27ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:2.2m Distance:0.4m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.5V delay:31ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:2.2m Distance:0.4m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.5V delay:26ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:2.2m Distance:0.4m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.4V delay:27ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:2.2m Distance:0.4m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.4V delay:25ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:2.2m Distance:0.5m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.4V delay:27ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:2.1m Distance:0.5m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.4V delay:28ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:2.1m Distance:0.6m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.4V delay:27ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:2.1m Distance:0.6m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.4V delay:31ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:2.1m Distance:0.6m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.4V delay:25ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:2.1m Distance:0.6m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.4V delay:27ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:2.1m Distance:0.6m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.4V delay:29ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:2.1m Distance:0.7m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.4V delay:24ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:2.1m Distance:0.7m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.1m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.4V delay:25ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:2.0m Distance:0.7m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.2m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.4V delay:23ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:2.0m Distance:0.7m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.2m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.9V delay:25ms bitrate:50.5Mbps Height:2.0m Distance:0.7m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.2m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.9V delay:29ms bitrate:50.5Mbps Height:1.9m Distance:0.7m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.3m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.9V delay:31ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:1.9m Distance:0.7m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.3m/s gpsNum:25
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.9V delay:25ms bitrate:50.4Mbps Height:1.9m Distance:0.7m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.3m/s gpsNum:25
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.9V delay:26ms bitrate:50.4Mbps Height:1.8m Distance:0.7m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.3m/s gpsNum:25
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.9V delay:28ms bitrate:50.4Mbps Height:1.7m Distance:0.7m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.3m/s gpsNum:25
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.9V delay:26ms bitrate:50.4Mbps Height:1.6m Distance:0.7m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.3m/s gpsNum:25
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:27ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:1.6m Distance:0.7m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.3m/s gpsNum:25
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:29ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:1.6m Distance:0.7m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.2m/s gpsNum:25
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:30ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:1.5m Distance:0.7m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.2m/s gpsNum:25
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:31ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:1.5m Distance:0.7m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.1m/s gpsNum:25
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:26ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:1.5m Distance:0.7m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.1m/s gpsNum:25
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:27ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:1.4m Distance:0.7m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.1m/s gpsNum:25
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:28ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:1.4m Distance:0.7m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.1m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.2V delay:31ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:1.4m Distance:0.7m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.1m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.2V delay:24ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:1.4m Distance:0.7m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.1m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.2V delay:26ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:1.4m Distance:0.7m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.1m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.2V delay:27ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:1.3m Distance:0.7m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.1m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.2V delay:28ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:1.3m Distance:0.8m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.1m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.2V delay:30ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:1.3m Distance:0.8m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.1m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.9V delay:24ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:1.3m Distance:0.8m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.1m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.9V delay:32ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:1.3m Distance:0.8m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.1m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.9V delay:27ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:1.3m Distance:0.8m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.1m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.9V delay:25ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:1.3m Distance:0.8m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.1m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.9V delay:29ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:1.2m Distance:0.8m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.1m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.9V delay:31ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:1.2m Distance:0.8m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.1m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.9V delay:32ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:1.2m Distance:0.8m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.1m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.8V delay:27ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:1.2m Distance:0.8m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.1m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.8V delay:25ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:1.2m Distance:0.8m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.1m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.8V delay:26ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:1.1m Distance:0.8m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.1m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.8V delay:24ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:1.1m Distance:0.8m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.1m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.8V delay:25ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:1.1m Distance:0.8m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.1m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.8V delay:26ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:1.1m Distance:0.8m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.1m/s gpsNum:25
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.8V delay:25ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:1.1m Distance:0.8m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.1m/s gpsNum:25
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.9V delay:26ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:1.1m Distance:0.8m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:25
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.9V delay:28ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:1.1m Distance:0.8m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:25
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.9V delay:25ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:1.1m Distance:0.8m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:25
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.9V delay:23ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:1.0m Distance:0.8m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:25
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.9V delay:32ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:1.0m Distance:0.8m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:24
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.9V delay:26ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:1.0m Distance:0.8m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:24
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.0V delay:27ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:1.0m Distance:0.8m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:24
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.0V delay:28ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:1.0m Distance:0.8m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:24
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.0V delay:30ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:1.0m Distance:0.9m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:25
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.0V delay:24ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:1.0m Distance:0.9m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:25
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.0V delay:26ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:1.1m Distance:0.9m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:25
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.0V delay:24ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:1.1m Distance:0.9m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:25
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.0V delay:28ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:1.1m Distance:0.9m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:25
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.8V delay:30ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:1.1m Distance:0.9m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:25
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.8V delay:21ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:1.1m Distance:0.9m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:25
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.8V delay:24ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:1.0m Distance:0.9m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:25
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.8V delay:27ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:1.0m Distance:0.9m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:25
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.8V delay:25ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:1.0m Distance:0.9m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:25
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.8V delay:31ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:1.1m Distance:0.9m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.3m/s gpsNum:25
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.8V delay:28ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:1.2m Distance:0.9m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.4m/s gpsNum:25
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.9V delay:25ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:1.3m Distance:0.9m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.5m/s gpsNum:25
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.9V delay:27ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:1.3m Distance:0.9m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.5m/s gpsNum:25
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.9V delay:25ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:1.4m Distance:0.9m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.5m/s gpsNum:25
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.9V delay:26ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:1.5m Distance:1.0m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.6m/s gpsNum:24
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.9V delay:27ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:1.6m Distance:0.9m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.6m/s gpsNum:24
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.9V delay:25ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:1.6m Distance:0.9m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.6m/s gpsNum:24
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:26ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:1.7m Distance:1.0m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.5m/s gpsNum:24
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:25ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:1.9m Distance:1.0m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.5m/s gpsNum:25
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:26ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:2.0m Distance:0.9m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.5m/s gpsNum:25
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:24ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:2.0m Distance:0.9m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.5m/s gpsNum:25
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:29ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:2.1m Distance:0.9m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.5m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:23ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:2.2m Distance:0.9m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.5m/s gpsNum:25
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:29ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:2.3m Distance:0.9m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.4m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:26ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:2.3m Distance:0.9m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.4m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:27ms bitrate:50.5Mbps Height:2.4m Distance:1.0m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.4m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:28ms bitrate:50.5Mbps Height:2.5m Distance:1.0m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.4m/s gpsNum:25
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:30ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:2.6m Distance:1.0m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.4m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:24ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:2.6m Distance:1.0m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.4m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:26ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:2.6m Distance:1.0m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.3m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.4V delay:27ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:2.7m Distance:1.0m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.2m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.4V delay:25ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:2.7m Distance:1.0m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.1m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.4V delay:30ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:2.7m Distance:1.0m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.1m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.4V delay:31ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:2.8m Distance:1.0m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.1m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.4V delay:25ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:2.8m Distance:1.1m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.4m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.4V delay:27ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:3.0m Distance:1.1m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.6m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.4V delay:25ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:3.0m Distance:1.1m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.6m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.3V delay:26ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:3.1m Distance:1.1m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.7m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.3V delay:28ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:3.2m Distance:1.1m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.6m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.3V delay:25ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:3.4m Distance:1.1m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.6m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.3V delay:27ms bitrate:50.3Mbps Height:3.4m Distance:1.1m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.6m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.3V delay:25ms bitrate:50.3Mbps Height:3.5m Distance:1.1m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.5m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.3V delay:26ms bitrate:50.4Mbps Height:3.6m Distance:1.1m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.5m/s gpsNum:25
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.3V delay:24ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:3.7m Distance:1.1m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.5m/s gpsNum:25
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.3V delay:29ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:3.7m Distance:1.1m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.5m/s gpsNum:25
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.3V delay:30ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:3.9m Distance:1.2m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.5m/s gpsNum:25
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.3V delay:25ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:4.0m Distance:1.2m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.5m/s gpsNum:25
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.3V delay:26ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:4.1m Distance:1.2m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.5m/s gpsNum:25
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.3V delay:27ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:4.2m Distance:1.2m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.5m/s gpsNum:25
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.3V delay:29ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:4.2m Distance:1.2m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.5m/s gpsNum:25
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.3V delay:30ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:4.3m Distance:1.2m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.5m/s gpsNum:25
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.3V delay:24ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:4.4m Distance:1.2m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.5m/s gpsNum:24
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.3V delay:23ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:4.6m Distance:1.2m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.5m/s gpsNum:25
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.3V delay:24ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:4.6m Distance:1.2m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.5m/s gpsNum:25
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.3V delay:25ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:4.7m Distance:1.2m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.5m/s gpsNum:25
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.3V delay:27ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:4.8m Distance:1.2m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.5m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.3V delay:24ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:4.9m Distance:1.2m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.6m/s gpsNum:25
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.3V delay:26ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:4.9m Distance:1.2m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.6m/s gpsNum:25
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.3V delay:24ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:5.0m Distance:1.3m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.6m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.3V delay:25ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:5.2m Distance:1.3m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.6m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.3V delay:27ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:5.3m Distance:1.3m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.6m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.3V delay:28ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:5.3m Distance:1.3m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.6m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.3V delay:29ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:5.5m Distance:1.4m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.7m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.3V delay:31ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:5.6m Distance:1.3m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.7m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.2V delay:32ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:5.8m Distance:1.3m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.7m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.2V delay:26ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:5.8m Distance:1.3m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.7m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.2V delay:28ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:5.9m Distance:1.3m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.7m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.2V delay:29ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:6.1m Distance:1.4m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.7m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.2V delay:30ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:6.2m Distance:1.4m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.7m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.2V delay:25ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:6.2m Distance:1.4m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.7m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.0V delay:26ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:6.4m Distance:1.4m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.7m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.0V delay:28ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:6.5m Distance:1.4m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.7m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.0V delay:29ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:6.7m Distance:1.4m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.9m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.0V delay:30ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:6.7m Distance:1.4m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.9m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.0V delay:25ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:6.9m Distance:1.5m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.0m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.0V delay:26ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:7.1m Distance:1.5m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.0m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.0V delay:24ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:7.3m Distance:1.5m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.0m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:26ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:7.3m Distance:1.5m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.0m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:27ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:7.5m Distance:1.5m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.1m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:26ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:7.8m Distance:1.5m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.2m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:26ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:8.0m Distance:1.5m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.2m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:27ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:8.0m Distance:1.5m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.2m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:25ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:8.3m Distance:1.5m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.2m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:27ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:8.5m Distance:1.5m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.2m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:28ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:8.8m Distance:1.5m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.2m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:29ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:8.8m Distance:1.5m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.2m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:31ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:9.0m Distance:1.6m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.3m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:25ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:9.3m Distance:1.5m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.3m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:31ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:9.6m Distance:1.5m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.3m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:25ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:9.6m Distance:1.5m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.3m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.1V delay:29ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:9.8m Distance:1.5m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.3m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.1V delay:31ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:10.1m Distance:1.6m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.3m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.1V delay:32ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:10.4m Distance:1.5m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.3m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.1V delay:25ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:10.7m Distance:1.6m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.4m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.1V delay:28ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:10.7m Distance:1.6m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.4m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.1V delay:26ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:11.0m Distance:1.6m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.5m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.1V delay:31ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:11.3m Distance:1.6m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.5m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.0V delay:25ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:11.3m Distance:1.6m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.5m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.0V delay:26ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:11.6m Distance:1.6m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.6m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.0V delay:28ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:11.9m Distance:1.6m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.6m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.0V delay:26ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:12.2m Distance:1.6m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.5m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.0V delay:30ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:12.2m Distance:1.6m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.5m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.0V delay:29ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:12.6m Distance:1.6m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.5m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.0V delay:33ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:12.9m Distance:1.6m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.6m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.1V delay:27ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:13.2m Distance:1.6m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.8m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.1V delay:26ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:13.2m Distance:1.6m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.8m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.1V delay:27ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:13.6m Distance:1.6m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.9m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.1V delay:28ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:14.0m Distance:1.6m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.9m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.1V delay:26ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:14.4m Distance:1.6m HS:0.0m/s VS:2.0m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.1V delay:24ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:14.4m Distance:1.6m HS:0.0m/s VS:2.0m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.1V delay:29ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:14.8m Distance:1.6m HS:0.0m/s VS:2.0m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.1V delay:27ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:15.2m Distance:1.6m HS:0.0m/s VS:2.0m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.1V delay:26ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:15.6m Distance:1.6m HS:0.0m/s VS:2.0m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.1V delay:30ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:15.6m Distance:1.6m HS:0.0m/s VS:2.0m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.1V delay:31ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:16.0m Distance:1.7m HS:0.0m/s VS:2.0m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.1V delay:25ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:16.4m Distance:1.7m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.9m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.1V delay:30ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:16.8m Distance:1.7m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.9m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:31ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:16.8m Distance:1.7m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.9m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:29ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:17.2m Distance:1.7m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.9m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:31ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:17.6m Distance:1.7m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.9m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:28ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:18.0m Distance:1.8m HS:0.1m/s VS:1.9m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:31ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:18.4m Distance:1.7m HS:0.1m/s VS:1.9m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:28ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:18.4m Distance:1.7m HS:0.1m/s VS:1.9m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:29ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:18.7m Distance:1.7m HS:0.1m/s VS:1.8m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:9.0V delay:28ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:19.0m Distance:1.8m HS:0.1m/s VS:1.9m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:9.0V delay:32ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:19.0m Distance:1.8m HS:0.1m/s VS:1.9m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:9.0V delay:33ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:19.4m Distance:1.8m HS:0.1m/s VS:2.0m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:9.0V delay:28ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:19.8m Distance:1.7m HS:0.1m/s VS:2.0m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:9.0V delay:29ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:20.3m Distance:1.7m HS:0.1m/s VS:2.1m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:9.0V delay:30ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:20.3m Distance:1.7m HS:0.1m/s VS:2.1m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:32ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:20.7m Distance:1.7m HS:0.1m/s VS:2.0m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:33ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:21.1m Distance:1.7m HS:0.1m/s VS:2.1m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:34ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:21.6m Distance:1.8m HS:0.1m/s VS:2.1m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:29ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:21.6m Distance:1.8m HS:0.1m/s VS:2.1m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:30ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:22.0m Distance:1.8m HS:0.1m/s VS:2.1m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:28ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:22.4m Distance:1.8m HS:0.1m/s VS:2.1m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:33ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:22.8m Distance:1.8m HS:0.1m/s VS:2.1m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:27ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:22.8m Distance:1.8m HS:0.1m/s VS:2.1m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:26ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:23.3m Distance:1.7m HS:0.1m/s VS:2.1m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:30ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:23.7m Distance:1.8m HS:0.1m/s VS:2.2m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:28ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:24.2m Distance:1.8m HS:0.0m/s VS:2.2m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:30ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:24.2m Distance:1.8m HS:0.0m/s VS:2.2m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:31ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:24.6m Distance:1.8m HS:0.0m/s VS:2.2m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.1V delay:25ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:25.1m Distance:1.8m HS:0.0m/s VS:2.2m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.1V delay:27ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:25.6m Distance:1.8m HS:0.1m/s VS:2.2m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.1V delay:28ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:25.6m Distance:1.8m HS:0.1m/s VS:2.2m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.1V delay:29ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:26.0m Distance:1.9m HS:0.1m/s VS:2.1m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.1V delay:31ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:26.4m Distance:1.9m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.9m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.1V delay:32ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:26.8m Distance:1.9m HS:0.1m/s VS:1.9m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.1V delay:27ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:26.8m Distance:1.9m HS:0.1m/s VS:1.9m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.1V delay:28ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:27.2m Distance:2.0m HS:0.2m/s VS:1.9m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.1V delay:29ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:27.6m Distance:2.0m HS:0.1m/s VS:1.9m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.1V delay:31ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:28.0m Distance:2.0m HS:0.2m/s VS:2.0m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.1V delay:32ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:28.0m Distance:2.0m HS:0.2m/s VS:2.0m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.1V delay:26ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:28.4m Distance:2.0m HS:0.2m/s VS:2.1m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.1V delay:25ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:28.9m Distance:2.1m HS:0.1m/s VS:2.2m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.1V delay:26ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:29.3m Distance:2.1m HS:0.1m/s VS:2.2m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.2V delay:27ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:29.3m Distance:2.1m HS:0.1m/s VS:2.2m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.2V delay:29ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:29.8m Distance:2.2m HS:0.1m/s VS:2.2m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.2V delay:30ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:30.2m Distance:2.2m HS:0.1m/s VS:2.2m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.2V delay:26ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:30.7m Distance:2.3m HS:0.1m/s VS:2.2m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.2V delay:27ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:31.2m Distance:2.3m HS:0.1m/s VS:2.2m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.2V delay:32ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:31.6m Distance:2.4m HS:0.1m/s VS:2.2m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.2V delay:30ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:32.1m Distance:2.4m HS:0.1m/s VS:2.2m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.2V delay:31ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:32.1m Distance:2.4m HS:0.1m/s VS:2.2m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.2V delay:29ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:32.5m Distance:2.4m HS:0.1m/s VS:2.1m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.2V delay:30ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:33.0m Distance:2.4m HS:0.1m/s VS:1.8m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.2V delay:28ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:33.3m Distance:2.5m HS:0.1m/s VS:1.5m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.2V delay:30ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:33.3m Distance:2.5m HS:0.1m/s VS:1.5m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:31ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:33.7m Distance:2.5m HS:0.1m/s VS:1.5m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:30ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:33.9m Distance:2.5m HS:0.1m/s VS:1.5m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:27ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:34.2m Distance:2.5m HS:0.1m/s VS:1.6m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:28ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:34.2m Distance:2.5m HS:0.1m/s VS:1.6m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:30ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:34.6m Distance:2.5m HS:0.1m/s VS:1.6m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:31ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:34.9m Distance:2.5m HS:0.1m/s VS:1.6m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:32ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:35.2m Distance:2.5m HS:0.1m/s VS:1.6m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.2V delay:31ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:35.5m Distance:2.5m HS:0.1m/s VS:1.7m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.2V delay:28ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:35.5m Distance:2.5m HS:0.1m/s VS:1.7m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.2V delay:29ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:35.9m Distance:2.5m HS:0.1m/s VS:1.7m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.2V delay:27ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:36.2m Distance:2.5m HS:0.2m/s VS:1.8m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.2V delay:32ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:36.6m Distance:2.5m HS:0.2m/s VS:1.8m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.2V delay:26ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:36.6m Distance:2.5m HS:0.2m/s VS:1.8m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.2V delay:28ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:37.0m Distance:2.4m HS:0.2m/s VS:1.9m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.2V delay:29ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:37.3m Distance:2.4m HS:0.2m/s VS:1.9m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.2V delay:27ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:37.8m Distance:2.4m HS:0.2m/s VS:2.0m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.2V delay:32ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:37.8m Distance:2.4m HS:0.2m/s VS:2.0m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.2V delay:33ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:38.2m Distance:2.4m HS:0.2m/s VS:2.0m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.2V delay:28ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:38.6m Distance:2.4m HS:0.2m/s VS:2.1m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.2V delay:29ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:39.0m Distance:2.4m HS:0.1m/s VS:2.1m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:27ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:39.0m Distance:2.4m HS:0.1m/s VS:2.1m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:28ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:39.5m Distance:2.4m HS:0.1m/s VS:2.2m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:30ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:39.9m Distance:2.4m HS:0.1m/s VS:2.2m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:31ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:40.4m Distance:2.4m HS:0.1m/s VS:2.2m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:26ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:40.4m Distance:2.4m HS:0.1m/s VS:2.2m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:27ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:40.8m Distance:2.4m HS:0.1m/s VS:2.1m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:28ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:41.2m Distance:2.4m HS:0.1m/s VS:1.9m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:30ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:41.5m Distance:2.5m HS:0.1m/s VS:1.8m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:31ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:41.5m Distance:2.5m HS:0.1m/s VS:1.8m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:32ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:41.9m Distance:2.5m HS:0.1m/s VS:1.8m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:27ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:42.2m Distance:2.5m HS:0.1m/s VS:1.7m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:28ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:42.5m Distance:2.6m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.5m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:29ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:42.5m Distance:2.6m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.5m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.2V delay:31ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:42.8m Distance:2.7m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.5m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.2V delay:25ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:43.1m Distance:2.7m HS:0.1m/s VS:1.5m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.2V delay:23ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:43.5m Distance:2.7m HS:0.1m/s VS:1.6m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.2V delay:25ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:43.5m Distance:2.7m HS:0.1m/s VS:1.6m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.2V delay:26ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:43.8m Distance:2.8m HS:0.1m/s VS:1.7m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.2V delay:28ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:44.2m Distance:2.8m HS:0.1m/s VS:1.8m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.2V delay:29ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:44.5m Distance:2.9m HS:0.1m/s VS:1.7m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.3V delay:26ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:44.5m Distance:2.9m HS:0.1m/s VS:1.7m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.3V delay:28ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:44.8m Distance:3.0m HS:0.1m/s VS:1.7m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.3V delay:26ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:45.2m Distance:3.0m HS:0.1m/s VS:1.6m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.3V delay:27ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:45.5m Distance:3.1m HS:0.2m/s VS:1.5m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.3V delay:29ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:45.5m Distance:3.1m HS:0.2m/s VS:1.5m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.3V delay:30ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:45.9m Distance:3.2m HS:0.2m/s VS:1.4m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.3V delay:31ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:46.2m Distance:3.2m HS:0.3m/s VS:1.6m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.1V delay:26ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:46.5m Distance:3.2m HS:0.4m/s VS:1.6m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.1V delay:27ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:46.5m Distance:3.2m HS:0.4m/s VS:1.6m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.1V delay:29ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:46.8m Distance:3.3m HS:0.3m/s VS:1.6m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.1V delay:30ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:47.1m Distance:3.3m HS:0.2m/s VS:1.6m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.1V delay:31ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:47.4m Distance:3.4m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.7m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.1V delay:26ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:47.4m Distance:3.4m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.7m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.3V delay:27ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:47.7m Distance:3.4m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.7m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.3V delay:25ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:48.1m Distance:3.5m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.8m/s gpsNum:25
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.3V delay:27ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:48.5m Distance:3.6m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.8m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.3V delay:28ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:48.5m Distance:3.6m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.8m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.3V delay:26ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:48.8m Distance:3.7m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.8m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.3V delay:27ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:49.2m Distance:3.8m HS:0.1m/s VS:1.8m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.3V delay:25ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:49.6m Distance:3.9m HS:0.2m/s VS:1.8m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:26ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:49.6m Distance:3.9m HS:0.2m/s VS:1.8m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:28ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:50.0m Distance:3.9m HS:0.2m/s VS:1.9m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:30ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:50.4m Distance:4.0m HS:0.3m/s VS:2.0m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:34ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:50.8m Distance:4.0m HS:0.4m/s VS:2.0m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:28ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:50.8m Distance:4.0m HS:0.4m/s VS:2.0m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:34ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:51.2m Distance:4.0m HS:0.4m/s VS:2.0m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:28ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:51.6m Distance:4.0m HS:0.5m/s VS:2.0m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.9V delay:29ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:52.1m Distance:4.0m HS:0.5m/s VS:2.1m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.9V delay:30ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:52.1m Distance:4.0m HS:0.5m/s VS:2.1m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.9V delay:25ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:52.5m Distance:4.0m HS:0.5m/s VS:2.2m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.9V delay:26ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:52.9m Distance:4.0m HS:0.4m/s VS:2.3m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.9V delay:27ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:53.3m Distance:4.1m HS:0.4m/s VS:2.2m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.9V delay:29ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:53.3m Distance:4.1m HS:0.4m/s VS:2.2m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.2V delay:30ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:53.7m Distance:4.1m HS:0.4m/s VS:2.1m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.2V delay:31ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:54.1m Distance:4.1m HS:0.5m/s VS:2.2m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.2V delay:33ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:54.6m Distance:4.1m HS:0.5m/s VS:2.2m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.2V delay:27ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:54.6m Distance:4.1m HS:0.5m/s VS:2.2m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.2V delay:29ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:55.0m Distance:4.1m HS:0.4m/s VS:2.3m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.2V delay:30ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:55.5m Distance:4.1m HS:0.4m/s VS:2.3m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.2V delay:31ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:56.0m Distance:4.1m HS:0.4m/s VS:2.3m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:26ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:56.0m Distance:4.1m HS:0.4m/s VS:2.3m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:27ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:56.4m Distance:4.0m HS:0.4m/s VS:2.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:29ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:56.8m Distance:4.0m HS:0.4m/s VS:2.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:27ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:57.2m Distance:4.0m HS:0.3m/s VS:2.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:28ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:57.2m Distance:4.0m HS:0.3m/s VS:2.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:26ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:57.6m Distance:4.0m HS:0.3m/s VS:1.5m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:27ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:57.9m Distance:4.0m HS:0.2m/s VS:1.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.0V delay:25ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:58.1m Distance:4.0m HS:0.1m/s VS:1.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.0V delay:26ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:58.1m Distance:4.0m HS:0.1m/s VS:1.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.0V delay:28ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:58.4m Distance:4.1m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.0V delay:29ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:58.6m Distance:4.1m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.9m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.0V delay:30ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:58.7m Distance:4.2m HS:0.2m/s VS:0.9m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.0V delay:25ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:58.7m Distance:4.2m HS:0.2m/s VS:0.9m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.0V delay:26ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:58.9m Distance:4.2m HS:0.3m/s VS:0.9m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.0V delay:28ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:59.0m Distance:4.3m HS:0.5m/s VS:0.9m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.0V delay:29ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:59.1m Distance:4.4m HS:0.8m/s VS:0.9m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.0V delay:30ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:59.1m Distance:4.4m HS:0.8m/s VS:0.9m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.0V delay:32ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:59.3m Distance:4.4m HS:1.0m/s VS:0.9m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.0V delay:33ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:59.5m Distance:4.5m HS:1.3m/s VS:0.9m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.0V delay:27ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:59.6m Distance:4.6m HS:1.5m/s VS:0.9m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.0V delay:26ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:59.6m Distance:4.6m HS:1.5m/s VS:0.9m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.0V delay:30ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:59.8m Distance:4.7m HS:1.8m/s VS:0.9m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.0V delay:25ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:59.9m Distance:4.9m HS:2.2m/s VS:1.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.0V delay:26ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:60.1m Distance:5.1m HS:2.4m/s VS:0.9m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.0V delay:27ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:60.1m Distance:5.1m HS:2.4m/s VS:0.9m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.0V delay:29ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:60.3m Distance:5.4m HS:2.7m/s VS:1.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.9V delay:27ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:60.5m Distance:5.8m HS:3.0m/s VS:0.9m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.9V delay:28ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:60.6m Distance:6.2m HS:3.1m/s VS:0.9m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.9V delay:30ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:60.6m Distance:6.2m HS:3.1m/s VS:0.9m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.9V delay:27ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:60.8m Distance:6.7m HS:3.4m/s VS:0.9m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.9V delay:25ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:61.0m Distance:7.3m HS:3.5m/s VS:0.9m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.9V delay:30ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:61.2m Distance:7.9m HS:3.7m/s VS:0.9m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.9V delay:28ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:61.2m Distance:7.9m HS:3.7m/s VS:0.9m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:27ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:61.4m Distance:8.6m HS:3.8m/s VS:0.9m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:31ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:61.6m Distance:9.2m HS:3.5m/s VS:1.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:32ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:61.8m Distance:9.8m HS:2.6m/s VS:1.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:27ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:61.8m Distance:9.8m HS:2.6m/s VS:1.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:28ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:62.0m Distance:10.2m HS:1.7m/s VS:1.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:26ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:62.3m Distance:10.5m HS:0.9m/s VS:1.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:31ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:62.5m Distance:10.7m HS:0.3m/s VS:1.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.9V delay:32ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:62.7m Distance:10.8m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.9V delay:26ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:62.7m Distance:10.8m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.9V delay:28ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:63.0m Distance:10.8m HS:0.1m/s VS:1.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.9V delay:26ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:63.2m Distance:10.8m HS:0.1m/s VS:1.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.9V delay:27ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:63.4m Distance:10.8m HS:0.1m/s VS:1.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.9V delay:32ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:63.4m Distance:10.8m HS:0.1m/s VS:1.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.3V delay:26ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:63.7m Distance:10.8m HS:0.1m/s VS:1.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.3V delay:24ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:63.9m Distance:10.7m HS:0.1m/s VS:1.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.3V delay:29ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:64.2m Distance:10.7m HS:0.2m/s VS:1.3m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.3V delay:27ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:64.2m Distance:10.7m HS:0.2m/s VS:1.3m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.3V delay:29ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:64.4m Distance:10.6m HS:0.1m/s VS:1.4m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.3V delay:26ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:64.7m Distance:10.6m HS:0.1m/s VS:1.4m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.3V delay:27ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:65.0m Distance:10.6m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.4m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:26ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:65.0m Distance:10.6m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.4m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:27ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:65.2m Distance:10.5m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.6m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:28ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:65.6m Distance:10.5m HS:0.1m/s VS:2.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:30ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:66.0m Distance:10.6m HS:0.1m/s VS:2.3m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:31ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:66.0m Distance:10.6m HS:0.1m/s VS:2.3m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:26ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:66.5m Distance:10.5m HS:0.0m/s VS:2.4m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:27ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:67.0m Distance:10.6m HS:0.0m/s VS:2.5m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:28ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:67.5m Distance:10.6m HS:0.0m/s VS:2.9m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:29ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:67.5m Distance:10.6m HS:0.0m/s VS:2.9m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:31ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:68.1m Distance:10.6m HS:0.0m/s VS:2.6m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:25ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:68.6m Distance:10.5m HS:0.0m/s VS:2.5m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:27ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:69.1m Distance:10.5m HS:0.1m/s VS:2.5m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:28ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:69.1m Distance:10.5m HS:0.1m/s VS:2.5m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.5V delay:29ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:69.6m Distance:10.5m HS:0.1m/s VS:2.4m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.5V delay:31ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:70.1m Distance:10.5m HS:0.0m/s VS:2.4m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.5V delay:29ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:70.6m Distance:10.5m HS:0.0m/s VS:2.4m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.5V delay:30ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:70.6m Distance:10.5m HS:0.0m/s VS:2.4m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.5V delay:25ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:71.1m Distance:10.5m HS:0.0m/s VS:2.4m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.5V delay:26ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:71.6m Distance:10.5m HS:0.1m/s VS:2.4m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.5V delay:27ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:72.1m Distance:10.6m HS:0.1m/s VS:2.5m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.5V delay:29ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:72.1m Distance:10.6m HS:0.1m/s VS:2.5m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.5V delay:30ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:72.6m Distance:10.6m HS:0.0m/s VS:2.6m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.5V delay:31ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:73.1m Distance:10.6m HS:0.0m/s VS:2.6m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.5V delay:26ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:73.7m Distance:10.6m HS:0.0m/s VS:2.6m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.5V delay:27ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:73.7m Distance:10.6m HS:0.0m/s VS:2.6m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.5V delay:26ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:74.2m Distance:10.6m HS:0.0m/s VS:2.4m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.5V delay:30ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:74.7m Distance:10.6m HS:0.0m/s VS:2.4m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.4V delay:24ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:75.2m Distance:10.7m HS:0.1m/s VS:2.4m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.4V delay:32ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:75.2m Distance:10.7m HS:0.1m/s VS:2.4m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.4V delay:27ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:75.7m Distance:10.7m HS:0.1m/s VS:2.4m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.4V delay:30ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:76.2m Distance:10.7m HS:0.1m/s VS:2.4m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.4V delay:30ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:76.7m Distance:10.7m HS:0.1m/s VS:2.4m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.4V delay:28ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:76.7m Distance:10.7m HS:0.1m/s VS:2.4m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.5V delay:25ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:77.1m Distance:10.7m HS:0.1m/s VS:2.4m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.5V delay:27ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:77.6m Distance:10.8m HS:0.2m/s VS:2.4m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.5V delay:28ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:78.1m Distance:10.8m HS:0.4m/s VS:2.4m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.5V delay:26ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:78.1m Distance:10.8m HS:0.4m/s VS:2.4m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.5V delay:28ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:78.6m Distance:10.8m HS:0.6m/s VS:2.4m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.5V delay:27ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:79.1m Distance:10.8m HS:0.4m/s VS:2.4m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.5V delay:30ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:79.6m Distance:10.8m HS:0.7m/s VS:2.4m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:32ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:79.6m Distance:10.8m HS:0.7m/s VS:2.4m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:33ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:80.1m Distance:10.8m HS:1.3m/s VS:2.4m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:27ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:80.5m Distance:10.8m HS:1.6m/s VS:2.5m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:26ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:81.0m Distance:10.8m HS:1.1m/s VS:2.5m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:30ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:81.0m Distance:10.8m HS:1.1m/s VS:2.5m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:32ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:81.5m Distance:10.8m HS:0.5m/s VS:2.4m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:33ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:82.0m Distance:10.8m HS:0.1m/s VS:2.4m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.9V delay:27ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:82.5m Distance:10.8m HS:0.1m/s VS:2.4m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.9V delay:26ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:82.5m Distance:10.8m HS:0.1m/s VS:2.4m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.9V delay:30ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:83.0m Distance:10.8m HS:0.5m/s VS:2.4m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.9V delay:31ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:83.5m Distance:10.9m HS:0.8m/s VS:2.4m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.9V delay:26ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:84.0m Distance:10.9m HS:1.1m/s VS:2.4m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.9V delay:32ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:84.5m Distance:11.0m HS:1.3m/s VS:2.5m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:25ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:84.5m Distance:11.0m HS:1.3m/s VS:2.5m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:27ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:85.0m Distance:11.0m HS:1.1m/s VS:2.4m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:31ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:85.4m Distance:11.1m HS:1.5m/s VS:2.3m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:26ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:85.4m Distance:11.1m HS:1.5m/s VS:2.3m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:27ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:85.9m Distance:11.1m HS:2.0m/s VS:2.4m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:25ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:86.4m Distance:11.2m HS:2.4m/s VS:2.5m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:27ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:86.9m Distance:11.4m HS:2.7m/s VS:2.4m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:29ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:87.4m Distance:11.5m HS:3.1m/s VS:2.4m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:31ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:87.9m Distance:11.8m HS:3.5m/s VS:2.4m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:25ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:88.3m Distance:12.1m HS:3.9m/s VS:2.4m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:33ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:88.3m Distance:12.1m HS:3.9m/s VS:2.4m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:31ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:88.8m Distance:12.5m HS:4.2m/s VS:2.4m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.8V delay:29ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:89.3m Distance:12.9m HS:4.5m/s VS:2.4m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.8V delay:30ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:89.8m Distance:13.5m HS:4.7m/s VS:2.4m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.8V delay:32ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:89.8m Distance:13.5m HS:4.7m/s VS:2.4m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.8V delay:26ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:90.3m Distance:14.1m HS:5.1m/s VS:2.4m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.8V delay:28ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:90.8m Distance:14.8m HS:5.4m/s VS:2.5m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.8V delay:26ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:91.2m Distance:15.6m HS:5.6m/s VS:2.4m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.8V delay:27ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:91.2m Distance:15.6m HS:5.6m/s VS:2.4m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.8V delay:32ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:91.7m Distance:16.5m HS:5.7m/s VS:2.4m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.8V delay:27ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:92.2m Distance:17.4m HS:5.7m/s VS:2.4m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.8V delay:27ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:92.7m Distance:18.3m HS:4.8m/s VS:3.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.8V delay:29ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:92.7m Distance:18.3m HS:4.8m/s VS:3.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.8V delay:27ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:93.4m Distance:19.0m HS:3.1m/s VS:3.8m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.8V delay:31ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:94.1m Distance:19.4m HS:1.6m/s VS:4.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.8V delay:26ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:94.9m Distance:19.8m HS:0.7m/s VS:4.2m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.8V delay:27ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:94.9m Distance:19.8m HS:0.7m/s VS:4.2m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.8V delay:29ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:95.8m Distance:20.0m HS:0.2m/s VS:4.3m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.8V delay:30ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:96.7m Distance:20.1m HS:0.2m/s VS:4.5m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.8V delay:28ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:97.7m Distance:20.1m HS:0.2m/s VS:4.9m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.8V delay:26ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:97.7m Distance:20.1m HS:0.2m/s VS:4.9m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.8V delay:27ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:98.7m Distance:20.1m HS:0.1m/s VS:5.3m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.8V delay:25ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:99.8m Distance:20.0m HS:0.0m/s VS:5.5m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.8V delay:27ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:101.0m Distance:20.0m HS:0.0m/s VS:5.9m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.8V delay:28ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:101.0m Distance:20.0m HS:0.0m/s VS:5.9m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.8V delay:29ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:102.3m Distance:20.0m HS:0.0m/s VS:6.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.8V delay:31ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:103.6m Distance:20.0m HS:0.0m/s VS:6.3m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.8V delay:32ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:104.8m Distance:20.0m HS:0.1m/s VS:6.4m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.8V delay:26ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:104.8m Distance:20.0m HS:0.1m/s VS:6.4m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:28ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:106.2m Distance:20.0m HS:0.1m/s VS:6.6m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:27ms bitrate:50.5Mbps Height:107.5m Distance:20.0m HS:0.1m/s VS:6.7m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:30ms bitrate:50.5Mbps Height:108.8m Distance:20.0m HS:0.1m/s VS:6.8m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:32ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:108.8m Distance:20.0m HS:0.1m/s VS:6.8m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:29ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:110.2m Distance:20.0m HS:0.1m/s VS:6.9m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:28ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:111.6m Distance:20.0m HS:0.1m/s VS:7.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:29ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:113.0m Distance:20.0m HS:0.1m/s VS:7.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.6V delay:30ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:113.0m Distance:20.0m HS:0.1m/s VS:7.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.6V delay:32ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:114.4m Distance:20.0m HS:0.1m/s VS:7.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.6V delay:26ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:115.9m Distance:20.0m HS:0.0m/s VS:7.3m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.6V delay:27ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:117.4m Distance:20.1m HS:0.0m/s VS:7.3m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.6V delay:26ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:118.8m Distance:20.1m HS:0.0m/s VS:7.3m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.6V delay:27ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:118.8m Distance:20.1m HS:0.0m/s VS:7.3m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.6V delay:25ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:120.3m Distance:20.1m HS:0.0m/s VS:7.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.6V delay:26ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:121.7m Distance:20.1m HS:0.0m/s VS:7.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.6V delay:27ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:123.1m Distance:20.1m HS:0.0m/s VS:6.9m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.6V delay:29ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:123.1m Distance:20.1m HS:0.0m/s VS:6.9m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.6V delay:27ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:124.4m Distance:20.1m HS:0.0m/s VS:6.6m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.6V delay:28ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:125.7m Distance:20.1m HS:0.0m/s VS:6.4m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.6V delay:29ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:127.0m Distance:20.1m HS:0.0m/s VS:6.3m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:31ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:127.0m Distance:20.1m HS:0.0m/s VS:6.3m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:28ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:128.2m Distance:20.1m HS:0.0m/s VS:5.7m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:27ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:129.3m Distance:20.1m HS:0.0m/s VS:4.7m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:28ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:130.1m Distance:20.1m HS:0.0m/s VS:3.7m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:29ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:130.1m Distance:20.1m HS:0.0m/s VS:3.7m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:31ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:130.8m Distance:20.1m HS:0.0m/s VS:2.9m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:32ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:131.4m Distance:20.1m HS:0.0m/s VS:3.4m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:26ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:132.1m Distance:20.1m HS:0.0m/s VS:3.7m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:25ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:132.1m Distance:20.1m HS:0.0m/s VS:3.7m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:26ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:132.9m Distance:20.1m HS:0.0m/s VS:3.8m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:27ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:133.6m Distance:20.1m HS:0.0m/s VS:3.6m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:29ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:134.3m Distance:20.1m HS:0.0m/s VS:3.3m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:30ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:134.3m Distance:20.1m HS:0.0m/s VS:3.3m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.7V delay:31ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:134.9m Distance:20.1m HS:0.0m/s VS:2.9m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.7V delay:29ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:135.5m Distance:20.1m HS:0.0m/s VS:2.8m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.7V delay:37ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:136.0m Distance:20.1m HS:0.0m/s VS:2.8m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.7V delay:29ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:136.0m Distance:20.1m HS:0.0m/s VS:2.8m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.7V delay:30ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:136.6m Distance:20.1m HS:0.0m/s VS:2.7m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.7V delay:31ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:137.1m Distance:20.1m HS:0.0m/s VS:2.7m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.7V delay:26ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:137.6m Distance:20.1m HS:0.0m/s VS:2.7m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.7V delay:27ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:137.6m Distance:20.1m HS:0.0m/s VS:2.7m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.7V delay:33ms bitrate:50.4Mbps Height:138.1m Distance:20.2m HS:0.0m/s VS:2.7m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.7V delay:30ms bitrate:50.4Mbps Height:138.6m Distance:20.2m HS:0.0m/s VS:2.7m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.7V delay:31ms bitrate:50.4Mbps Height:139.2m Distance:20.2m HS:0.0m/s VS:2.7m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.7V delay:29ms bitrate:50.4Mbps Height:139.2m Distance:20.2m HS:0.0m/s VS:2.7m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.7V delay:27ms bitrate:50.1Mbps Height:139.7m Distance:20.2m HS:0.0m/s VS:2.7m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.6V delay:26ms bitrate:50.1Mbps Height:140.3m Distance:20.2m HS:0.0m/s VS:2.7m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.6V delay:30ms bitrate:50.1Mbps Height:140.8m Distance:20.2m HS:0.0m/s VS:2.7m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.6V delay:31ms bitrate:50.2Mbps Height:140.8m Distance:20.2m HS:0.0m/s VS:2.7m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.6V delay:25ms bitrate:50.2Mbps Height:141.3m Distance:20.2m HS:0.0m/s VS:2.7m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.6V delay:34ms bitrate:49.9Mbps Height:141.8m Distance:20.3m HS:0.0m/s VS:2.7m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.6V delay:28ms bitrate:49.9Mbps Height:142.4m Distance:20.3m HS:0.0m/s VS:2.7m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.6V delay:26ms bitrate:49.9Mbps Height:142.4m Distance:20.3m HS:0.0m/s VS:2.7m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.5V delay:28ms bitrate:49.9Mbps Height:142.9m Distance:20.3m HS:0.0m/s VS:2.7m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.5V delay:39ms bitrate:49.9Mbps Height:143.5m Distance:20.3m HS:0.0m/s VS:2.7m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.5V delay:27ms bitrate:50.2Mbps Height:144.0m Distance:20.3m HS:0.0m/s VS:2.7m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.5V delay:28ms bitrate:50.0Mbps Height:144.0m Distance:20.3m HS:0.0m/s VS:2.7m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.5V delay:26ms bitrate:50.0Mbps Height:144.5m Distance:20.3m HS:0.0m/s VS:2.7m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.5V delay:27ms bitrate:50.1Mbps Height:145.0m Distance:20.3m HS:0.0m/s VS:2.7m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.5V delay:29ms bitrate:50.1Mbps Height:145.6m Distance:20.3m HS:0.0m/s VS:2.7m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:30ms bitrate:50.2Mbps Height:145.6m Distance:20.3m HS:0.0m/s VS:2.7m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:31ms bitrate:50.3Mbps Height:146.1m Distance:20.3m HS:0.0m/s VS:2.7m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:27ms bitrate:50.3Mbps Height:146.7m Distance:20.3m HS:0.0m/s VS:2.7m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:27ms bitrate:50.4Mbps Height:147.2m Distance:20.3m HS:0.0m/s VS:2.7m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:29ms bitrate:50.4Mbps Height:147.2m Distance:20.3m HS:0.0m/s VS:2.7m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:25ms bitrate:50.4Mbps Height:147.8m Distance:20.3m HS:0.0m/s VS:2.7m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:31ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:148.3m Distance:20.2m HS:0.0m/s VS:2.8m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:9.0V delay:33ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:149.0m Distance:20.2m HS:0.0m/s VS:2.8m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:9.0V delay:28ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:149.0m Distance:20.2m HS:0.0m/s VS:2.8m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:9.0V delay:28ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:149.5m Distance:20.2m HS:0.0m/s VS:2.7m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:9.0V delay:33ms bitrate:48.9Mbps Height:150.0m Distance:20.2m HS:0.0m/s VS:2.7m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:9.0V delay:32ms bitrate:47.6Mbps Height:150.6m Distance:20.2m HS:0.0m/s VS:2.7m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:27ms bitrate:47.4Mbps Height:151.1m Distance:20.2m HS:0.0m/s VS:2.7m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:28ms bitrate:47.4Mbps Height:151.7m Distance:20.2m HS:0.0m/s VS:2.7m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:26ms bitrate:49.0Mbps Height:152.2m Distance:20.2m HS:0.0m/s VS:2.7m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:31ms bitrate:49.6Mbps Height:152.2m Distance:20.2m HS:0.0m/s VS:2.7m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:25ms bitrate:49.6Mbps Height:152.8m Distance:20.3m HS:0.0m/s VS:2.7m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:27ms bitrate:50.0Mbps Height:153.3m Distance:20.3m HS:0.0m/s VS:2.7m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:25ms bitrate:50.0Mbps Height:153.9m Distance:20.3m HS:0.0m/s VS:2.7m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.2V delay:36ms bitrate:50.1Mbps Height:153.9m Distance:20.3m HS:0.0m/s VS:2.7m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.2V delay:38ms bitrate:44.9Mbps Height:154.4m Distance:20.3m HS:0.0m/s VS:2.7m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.2V delay:29ms bitrate:44.9Mbps Height:155.0m Distance:20.3m HS:0.0m/s VS:2.7m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.2V delay:40ms bitrate:40.2Mbps Height:155.5m Distance:20.3m HS:0.0m/s VS:2.7m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.2V delay:32ms bitrate:40.2Mbps Height:155.5m Distance:20.3m HS:0.0m/s VS:2.7m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.2V delay:26ms bitrate:38.1Mbps Height:156.1m Distance:20.3m HS:0.0m/s VS:2.7m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:27ms bitrate:40.0Mbps Height:156.6m Distance:20.3m HS:0.0m/s VS:2.7m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:29ms bitrate:40.0Mbps Height:157.2m Distance:20.3m HS:0.0m/s VS:2.7m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:30ms bitrate:43.2Mbps Height:157.2m Distance:20.3m HS:0.0m/s VS:2.7m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:31ms bitrate:43.2Mbps Height:157.7m Distance:20.3m HS:0.0m/s VS:2.7m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:26ms bitrate:46.6Mbps Height:158.3m Distance:20.3m HS:0.0m/s VS:2.7m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:24ms bitrate:48.5Mbps Height:158.8m Distance:20.3m HS:0.0m/s VS:2.7m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:26ms bitrate:48.5Mbps Height:158.8m Distance:20.3m HS:0.0m/s VS:2.7m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:30ms bitrate:49.6Mbps Height:159.4m Distance:20.3m HS:0.0m/s VS:2.7m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:31ms bitrate:49.6Mbps Height:159.9m Distance:20.3m HS:0.0m/s VS:2.7m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:26ms bitrate:50.2Mbps Height:160.5m Distance:20.3m HS:0.0m/s VS:2.8m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:34ms bitrate:50.3Mbps Height:160.5m Distance:20.3m HS:0.0m/s VS:2.8m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:28ms bitrate:50.3Mbps Height:161.0m Distance:20.3m HS:0.0m/s VS:2.7m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:30ms bitrate:50.3Mbps Height:161.6m Distance:20.3m HS:0.0m/s VS:2.8m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:28ms bitrate:50.3Mbps Height:162.1m Distance:20.3m HS:0.0m/s VS:2.7m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:29ms bitrate:50.2Mbps Height:162.1m Distance:20.3m HS:0.0m/s VS:2.7m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:31ms bitrate:50.2Mbps Height:162.7m Distance:20.3m HS:0.0m/s VS:2.7m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:25ms bitrate:50.2Mbps Height:163.2m Distance:20.3m HS:0.0m/s VS:2.7m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:33ms bitrate:50.2Mbps Height:163.7m Distance:20.3m HS:0.0m/s VS:2.7m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:28ms bitrate:50.2Mbps Height:163.7m Distance:20.3m HS:0.0m/s VS:2.7m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:29ms bitrate:50.4Mbps Height:164.3m Distance:20.3m HS:0.0m/s VS:2.7m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:31ms bitrate:50.5Mbps Height:164.8m Distance:20.3m HS:0.0m/s VS:2.7m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:28ms bitrate:50.5Mbps Height:165.3m Distance:20.3m HS:0.0m/s VS:2.7m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:26ms bitrate:50.5Mbps Height:165.9m Distance:20.3m HS:0.0m/s VS:2.7m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:28ms bitrate:50.5Mbps Height:165.9m Distance:20.3m HS:0.0m/s VS:2.7m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:39ms bitrate:50.4Mbps Height:166.4m Distance:20.3m HS:0.0m/s VS:2.7m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:30ms bitrate:50.1Mbps Height:167.0m Distance:20.3m HS:0.0m/s VS:2.8m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:29ms bitrate:50.1Mbps Height:167.6m Distance:20.3m HS:0.0m/s VS:2.7m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:26ms bitrate:50.2Mbps Height:167.6m Distance:20.3m HS:0.0m/s VS:2.7m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:27ms bitrate:49.9Mbps Height:168.1m Distance:20.4m HS:0.0m/s VS:2.7m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:26ms bitrate:49.9Mbps Height:168.7m Distance:20.3m HS:0.0m/s VS:2.7m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:37ms bitrate:49.8Mbps Height:169.2m Distance:20.3m HS:0.0m/s VS:2.7m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:28ms bitrate:49.8Mbps Height:169.2m Distance:20.3m HS:0.0m/s VS:2.7m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:27ms bitrate:49.9Mbps Height:169.7m Distance:20.3m HS:0.0m/s VS:2.7m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:31ms bitrate:50.1Mbps Height:170.3m Distance:20.3m HS:0.0m/s VS:2.7m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:29ms bitrate:50.1Mbps Height:170.8m Distance:20.3m HS:0.0m/s VS:2.7m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:27ms bitrate:50.2Mbps Height:170.8m Distance:20.3m HS:0.0m/s VS:2.7m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:28ms bitrate:50.2Mbps Height:171.3m Distance:20.3m HS:0.0m/s VS:2.7m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:30ms bitrate:50.3Mbps Height:171.9m Distance:20.3m HS:0.0m/s VS:2.7m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:31ms bitrate:50.3Mbps Height:172.4m Distance:20.3m HS:0.0m/s VS:2.8m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:32ms bitrate:50.3Mbps Height:172.4m Distance:20.3m HS:0.0m/s VS:2.8m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.8V delay:27ms bitrate:50.2Mbps Height:173.0m Distance:20.3m HS:0.0m/s VS:2.8m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.8V delay:28ms bitrate:50.2Mbps Height:173.5m Distance:20.3m HS:0.0m/s VS:2.7m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.8V delay:29ms bitrate:50.0Mbps Height:174.1m Distance:20.2m HS:0.0m/s VS:2.7m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.8V delay:24ms bitrate:50.2Mbps Height:174.1m Distance:20.2m HS:0.0m/s VS:2.7m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.8V delay:32ms bitrate:50.2Mbps Height:174.6m Distance:20.2m HS:0.0m/s VS:2.7m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.8V delay:33ms bitrate:50.4Mbps Height:175.2m Distance:20.2m HS:0.0m/s VS:3.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.8V delay:28ms bitrate:50.4Mbps Height:175.8m Distance:20.2m HS:0.0m/s VS:3.2m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.2V delay:26ms bitrate:50.2Mbps Height:175.8m Distance:20.2m HS:0.0m/s VS:3.2m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.2V delay:32ms bitrate:50.2Mbps Height:176.5m Distance:20.2m HS:0.0m/s VS:3.4m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.2V delay:25ms bitrate:50.2Mbps Height:177.2m Distance:20.3m HS:0.0m/s VS:3.8m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.2V delay:33ms bitrate:50.4Mbps Height:178.0m Distance:20.3m HS:0.0m/s VS:4.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.2V delay:32ms bitrate:50.4Mbps Height:178.0m Distance:20.3m HS:0.0m/s VS:4.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.2V delay:26ms bitrate:50.5Mbps Height:178.7m Distance:20.3m HS:0.0m/s VS:3.9m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.2V delay:30ms bitrate:50.2Mbps Height:179.5m Distance:20.3m HS:0.0m/s VS:3.7m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:32ms bitrate:50.2Mbps Height:180.2m Distance:20.3m HS:0.0m/s VS:3.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:30ms bitrate:50.2Mbps Height:180.2m Distance:20.3m HS:0.0m/s VS:3.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:31ms bitrate:50.2Mbps Height:180.8m Distance:20.3m HS:0.0m/s VS:2.9m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:27ms bitrate:50.3Mbps Height:181.5m Distance:20.3m HS:0.1m/s VS:2.8m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:30ms bitrate:50.4Mbps Height:182.0m Distance:20.4m HS:0.4m/s VS:2.7m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:28ms bitrate:50.4Mbps Height:182.0m Distance:20.4m HS:0.4m/s VS:2.7m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.8V delay:38ms bitrate:49.8Mbps Height:182.6m Distance:20.5m HS:0.8m/s VS:2.6m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.8V delay:34ms bitrate:49.8Mbps Height:183.1m Distance:20.7m HS:1.4m/s VS:2.6m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.8V delay:42ms bitrate:46.7Mbps Height:183.6m Distance:21.0m HS:2.0m/s VS:2.6m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.8V delay:37ms bitrate:44.7Mbps Height:183.6m Distance:21.0m HS:2.0m/s VS:2.6m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.8V delay:38ms bitrate:44.7Mbps Height:184.2m Distance:21.4m HS:2.4m/s VS:2.6m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.8V delay:30ms bitrate:45.7Mbps Height:184.7m Distance:21.8m HS:2.8m/s VS:2.6m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.8V delay:31ms bitrate:45.7Mbps Height:185.2m Distance:22.3m HS:3.3m/s VS:2.6m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.8V delay:32ms bitrate:46.0Mbps Height:185.2m Distance:22.3m HS:3.3m/s VS:2.6m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.8V delay:32ms bitrate:46.6Mbps Height:185.7m Distance:22.9m HS:3.6m/s VS:2.6m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.8V delay:28ms bitrate:46.6Mbps Height:186.3m Distance:23.6m HS:4.0m/s VS:2.6m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.8V delay:26ms bitrate:45.3Mbps Height:186.8m Distance:24.4m HS:4.5m/s VS:2.6m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.8V delay:32ms bitrate:46.2Mbps Height:187.3m Distance:25.2m HS:4.8m/s VS:2.6m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.8V delay:33ms bitrate:47.6Mbps Height:187.8m Distance:26.1m HS:5.2m/s VS:2.5m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.9V delay:36ms bitrate:47.6Mbps Height:188.3m Distance:27.1m HS:5.5m/s VS:2.5m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.9V delay:29ms bitrate:41.4Mbps Height:188.3m Distance:27.1m HS:5.5m/s VS:2.5m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.9V delay:27ms bitrate:41.4Mbps Height:188.8m Distance:28.1m HS:5.9m/s VS:2.5m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.9V delay:29ms bitrate:40.0Mbps Height:189.3m Distance:29.3m HS:6.4m/s VS:2.6m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.9V delay:30ms bitrate:44.3Mbps Height:189.8m Distance:30.5m HS:6.7m/s VS:2.6m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.9V delay:25ms bitrate:44.3Mbps Height:189.8m Distance:30.5m HS:6.7m/s VS:2.6m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:23ms bitrate:46.4Mbps Height:190.3m Distance:31.8m HS:7.0m/s VS:2.6m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:37ms bitrate:46.4Mbps Height:190.9m Distance:33.1m HS:7.4m/s VS:2.7m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:32ms bitrate:46.2Mbps Height:191.5m Distance:34.6m HS:7.6m/s VS:2.7m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:30ms bitrate:44.1Mbps Height:191.5m Distance:34.6m HS:7.6m/s VS:2.7m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:31ms bitrate:44.1Mbps Height:192.0m Distance:36.0m HS:7.9m/s VS:2.6m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:30ms bitrate:44.4Mbps Height:192.6m Distance:37.7m HS:8.2m/s VS:2.6m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:27ms bitrate:44.4Mbps Height:193.1m Distance:39.2m HS:8.5m/s VS:2.6m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.8V delay:29ms bitrate:46.8Mbps Height:193.1m Distance:39.2m HS:8.5m/s VS:2.6m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.8V delay:27ms bitrate:48.6Mbps Height:193.7m Distance:40.9m HS:8.6m/s VS:2.6m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.8V delay:31ms bitrate:48.6Mbps Height:194.2m Distance:42.5m HS:8.8m/s VS:2.7m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.8V delay:33ms bitrate:49.5Mbps Height:194.7m Distance:44.3m HS:9.1m/s VS:2.6m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.8V delay:27ms bitrate:49.5Mbps Height:194.7m Distance:44.3m HS:9.1m/s VS:2.6m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.8V delay:28ms bitrate:50.1Mbps Height:195.2m Distance:46.1m HS:9.3m/s VS:2.6m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.8V delay:27ms bitrate:50.2Mbps Height:195.8m Distance:48.0m HS:9.5m/s VS:2.6m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:9.0V delay:28ms bitrate:50.2Mbps Height:196.3m Distance:49.8m HS:9.7m/s VS:2.6m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:9.0V delay:29ms bitrate:50.2Mbps Height:196.3m Distance:49.8m HS:9.7m/s VS:2.6m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:9.0V delay:31ms bitrate:50.2Mbps Height:196.8m Distance:51.7m HS:9.8m/s VS:2.6m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:9.0V delay:32ms bitrate:50.1Mbps Height:197.3m Distance:53.6m HS:10.0m/s VS:2.6m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:9.0V delay:26ms bitrate:50.1Mbps Height:197.9m Distance:55.6m HS:10.1m/s VS:2.6m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:9.0V delay:28ms bitrate:50.1Mbps Height:197.9m Distance:55.6m HS:10.1m/s VS:2.6m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:29ms bitrate:49.8Mbps Height:198.4m Distance:57.6m HS:10.3m/s VS:2.6m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:30ms bitrate:49.8Mbps Height:198.9m Distance:59.5m HS:10.4m/s VS:2.6m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:42ms bitrate:49.4Mbps Height:199.5m Distance:61.8m HS:10.4m/s VS:2.6m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:33ms bitrate:48.0Mbps Height:199.5m Distance:61.8m HS:10.4m/s VS:2.6m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:28ms bitrate:48.0Mbps Height:200.0m Distance:63.8m HS:10.5m/s VS:2.6m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:29ms bitrate:48.5Mbps Height:200.5m Distance:65.8m HS:10.6m/s VS:2.6m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:30ms bitrate:48.5Mbps Height:201.1m Distance:68.0m HS:10.7m/s VS:2.6m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.2V delay:25ms bitrate:49.5Mbps Height:201.1m Distance:68.0m HS:10.7m/s VS:2.6m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.2V delay:33ms bitrate:49.8Mbps Height:201.6m Distance:70.1m HS:10.7m/s VS:2.6m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.2V delay:27ms bitrate:49.8Mbps Height:202.1m Distance:72.2m HS:10.8m/s VS:2.7m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.2V delay:29ms bitrate:49.5Mbps Height:202.7m Distance:74.4m HS:10.7m/s VS:2.7m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.2V delay:27ms bitrate:49.5Mbps Height:202.7m Distance:74.4m HS:10.7m/s VS:2.7m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.2V delay:28ms bitrate:47.9Mbps Height:203.2m Distance:76.5m HS:10.7m/s VS:2.6m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:29ms bitrate:48.3Mbps Height:203.7m Distance:78.7m HS:10.7m/s VS:2.6m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:27ms bitrate:48.3Mbps Height:204.4m Distance:80.8m HS:10.7m/s VS:2.7m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:25ms bitrate:49.2Mbps Height:204.4m Distance:80.8m HS:10.7m/s VS:2.7m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:27ms bitrate:49.2Mbps Height:204.9m Distance:82.9m HS:10.6m/s VS:2.6m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:28ms bitrate:50.0Mbps Height:205.4m Distance:85.1m HS:10.6m/s VS:2.6m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:49ms bitrate:44.1Mbps Height:205.9m Distance:87.2m HS:10.8m/s VS:2.6m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:31ms bitrate:44.1Mbps Height:205.9m Distance:87.2m HS:10.8m/s VS:2.6m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:32ms bitrate:36.6Mbps Height:206.4m Distance:89.4m HS:10.8m/s VS:2.6m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:30ms bitrate:36.6Mbps Height:207.0m Distance:91.5m HS:10.8m/s VS:2.6m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:28ms bitrate:37.1Mbps Height:207.5m Distance:93.8m HS:10.8m/s VS:2.7m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:29ms bitrate:36.1Mbps Height:207.5m Distance:93.8m HS:10.8m/s VS:2.7m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:29ms bitrate:36.1Mbps Height:208.0m Distance:96.0m HS:10.8m/s VS:2.6m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:25ms bitrate:40.7Mbps Height:208.5m Distance:98.0m HS:10.7m/s VS:2.6m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:26ms bitrate:40.7Mbps Height:209.0m Distance:100.2m HS:10.7m/s VS:2.6m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:28ms bitrate:46.0Mbps Height:209.6m Distance:102.4m HS:10.7m/s VS:2.6m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:29ms bitrate:48.0Mbps Height:209.6m Distance:102.4m HS:10.7m/s VS:2.6m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:30ms bitrate:48.0Mbps Height:210.1m Distance:104.1m HS:10.7m/s VS:2.6m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:32ms bitrate:49.2Mbps Height:210.6m Distance:106.8m HS:10.8m/s VS:2.6m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:43ms bitrate:49.2Mbps Height:211.1m Distance:109.0m HS:10.8m/s VS:2.6m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:28ms bitrate:46.0Mbps Height:211.1m Distance:109.0m HS:10.8m/s VS:2.6m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:26ms bitrate:42.8Mbps Height:211.7m Distance:111.2m HS:10.8m/s VS:2.6m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:27ms bitrate:42.8Mbps Height:212.2m Distance:113.4m HS:10.8m/s VS:2.6m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:39ms bitrate:45.5Mbps Height:212.7m Distance:115.6m HS:10.9m/s VS:2.6m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:26ms bitrate:45.5Mbps Height:212.7m Distance:115.6m HS:10.9m/s VS:2.6m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:27ms bitrate:44.8Mbps Height:213.3m Distance:117.9m HS:11.0m/s VS:2.6m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:26ms bitrate:39.3Mbps Height:213.9m Distance:120.0m HS:11.0m/s VS:2.6m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:37ms bitrate:39.3Mbps Height:214.4m Distance:122.3m HS:11.0m/s VS:2.7m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:28ms bitrate:37.2Mbps Height:214.4m Distance:122.3m HS:11.0m/s VS:2.7m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:31ms bitrate:38.2Mbps Height:214.9m Distance:124.5m HS:11.0m/s VS:2.7m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:31ms bitrate:38.2Mbps Height:215.5m Distance:126.1m HS:10.0m/s VS:3.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:25ms bitrate:43.6Mbps Height:216.0m Distance:128.6m HS:9.3m/s VS:2.7m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:34ms bitrate:43.6Mbps Height:216.0m Distance:128.6m HS:9.3m/s VS:2.7m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:31ms bitrate:46.9Mbps Height:216.5m Distance:130.5m HS:9.1m/s VS:2.4m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:29ms bitrate:42.6Mbps Height:217.0m Distance:132.4m HS:9.2m/s VS:2.5m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:31ms bitrate:42.6Mbps Height:217.5m Distance:134.3m HS:9.3m/s VS:2.5m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:25ms bitrate:41.3Mbps Height:217.5m Distance:134.3m HS:9.3m/s VS:2.5m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:35ms bitrate:41.3Mbps Height:218.1m Distance:136.2m HS:9.1m/s VS:2.8m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:25ms bitrate:39.5Mbps Height:218.7m Distance:137.8m HS:7.7m/s VS:3.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:36ms bitrate:38.7Mbps Height:219.2m Distance:139.2m HS:6.2m/s VS:2.8m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:28ms bitrate:38.7Mbps Height:219.2m Distance:139.2m HS:6.2m/s VS:2.8m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.8V delay:32ms bitrate:41.6Mbps Height:219.8m Distance:140.4m HS:4.8m/s VS:2.7m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.8V delay:26ms bitrate:41.6Mbps Height:220.3m Distance:141.3m HS:3.5m/s VS:2.6m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.8V delay:35ms bitrate:44.9Mbps Height:220.8m Distance:141.9m HS:2.1m/s VS:2.6m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.8V delay:36ms bitrate:47.2Mbps Height:220.8m Distance:141.9m HS:2.1m/s VS:2.6m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.8V delay:27ms bitrate:47.2Mbps Height:221.3m Distance:142.2m HS:0.8m/s VS:2.5m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.8V delay:25ms bitrate:48.6Mbps Height:221.8m Distance:142.3m HS:0.0m/s VS:2.3m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.8V delay:23ms bitrate:48.6Mbps Height:222.3m Distance:142.3m HS:0.2m/s VS:2.2m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:28ms bitrate:49.3Mbps Height:222.3m Distance:142.3m HS:0.2m/s VS:2.2m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:29ms bitrate:50.0Mbps Height:222.7m Distance:142.2m HS:0.4m/s VS:2.1m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:27ms bitrate:50.0Mbps Height:223.2m Distance:142.1m HS:0.4m/s VS:2.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:29ms bitrate:50.5Mbps Height:223.6m Distance:142.0m HS:0.4m/s VS:2.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:30ms bitrate:50.5Mbps Height:223.6m Distance:142.0m HS:0.4m/s VS:2.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:31ms bitrate:50.5Mbps Height:224.0m Distance:141.9m HS:0.4m/s VS:2.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:29ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:224.5m Distance:141.7m HS:0.4m/s VS:2.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:27ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:224.9m Distance:141.6m HS:0.2m/s VS:2.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:28ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:224.9m Distance:141.6m HS:0.2m/s VS:2.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:30ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:225.3m Distance:141.5m HS:0.2m/s VS:2.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:31ms bitrate:50.4Mbps Height:225.7m Distance:141.4m HS:0.2m/s VS:2.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:32ms bitrate:50.4Mbps Height:226.2m Distance:141.4m HS:0.2m/s VS:2.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:27ms bitrate:50.4Mbps Height:226.2m Distance:141.4m HS:0.2m/s VS:2.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.8V delay:28ms bitrate:50.2Mbps Height:226.6m Distance:141.3m HS:0.2m/s VS:2.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.8V delay:28ms bitrate:50.0Mbps Height:226.9m Distance:141.3m HS:0.2m/s VS:2.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.8V delay:31ms bitrate:50.0Mbps Height:227.3m Distance:141.3m HS:0.2m/s VS:2.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.8V delay:25ms bitrate:50.2Mbps Height:227.3m Distance:141.3m HS:0.2m/s VS:2.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.8V delay:27ms bitrate:50.2Mbps Height:227.7m Distance:141.2m HS:0.1m/s VS:2.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.8V delay:28ms bitrate:50.3Mbps Height:228.1m Distance:141.2m HS:0.1m/s VS:2.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.8V delay:29ms bitrate:50.3Mbps Height:228.6m Distance:141.2m HS:0.0m/s VS:2.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.8V delay:31ms bitrate:50.2Mbps Height:228.6m Distance:141.2m HS:0.0m/s VS:2.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.8V delay:25ms bitrate:50.3Mbps Height:229.0m Distance:141.2m HS:0.0m/s VS:2.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.8V delay:33ms bitrate:50.3Mbps Height:229.3m Distance:141.2m HS:0.0m/s VS:2.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.8V delay:28ms bitrate:50.3Mbps Height:229.7m Distance:141.2m HS:0.0m/s VS:2.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.8V delay:29ms bitrate:50.3Mbps Height:229.7m Distance:141.2m HS:0.0m/s VS:2.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.8V delay:31ms bitrate:50.2Mbps Height:230.1m Distance:141.2m HS:0.0m/s VS:2.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.8V delay:32ms bitrate:50.3Mbps Height:230.5m Distance:141.2m HS:0.0m/s VS:2.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.9V delay:33ms bitrate:50.3Mbps Height:230.9m Distance:141.2m HS:0.0m/s VS:2.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.9V delay:25ms bitrate:50.4Mbps Height:230.9m Distance:141.2m HS:0.0m/s VS:2.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.9V delay:29ms bitrate:50.4Mbps Height:231.3m Distance:141.2m HS:0.1m/s VS:2.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.9V delay:30ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:231.7m Distance:141.2m HS:0.1m/s VS:2.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.9V delay:29ms bitrate:50.3Mbps Height:232.2m Distance:141.2m HS:0.1m/s VS:2.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.9V delay:36ms bitrate:50.3Mbps Height:232.2m Distance:141.2m HS:0.1m/s VS:2.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:38ms bitrate:47.6Mbps Height:232.6m Distance:141.1m HS:0.2m/s VS:2.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:29ms bitrate:47.6Mbps Height:233.0m Distance:141.1m HS:0.2m/s VS:2.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:30ms bitrate:46.1Mbps Height:233.4m Distance:141.1m HS:0.2m/s VS:2.3m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:35ms bitrate:46.0Mbps Height:233.4m Distance:141.1m HS:0.2m/s VS:2.3m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:26ms bitrate:46.0Mbps Height:233.9m Distance:141.1m HS:0.1m/s VS:2.6m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:34ms bitrate:43.0Mbps Height:234.4m Distance:141.1m HS:0.1m/s VS:2.8m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:36ms bitrate:43.0Mbps Height:235.0m Distance:141.1m HS:0.0m/s VS:2.8m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.9V delay:37ms bitrate:41.8Mbps Height:235.0m Distance:141.1m HS:0.0m/s VS:2.8m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.9V delay:24ms bitrate:41.4Mbps Height:235.5m Distance:141.1m HS:0.0m/s VS:2.9m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.9V delay:47ms bitrate:41.4Mbps Height:236.1m Distance:141.1m HS:0.0m/s VS:2.9m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.9V delay:37ms bitrate:42.6Mbps Height:236.7m Distance:141.1m HS:0.0m/s VS:3.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.9V delay:29ms bitrate:42.6Mbps Height:236.7m Distance:141.1m HS:0.0m/s VS:3.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.9V delay:28ms bitrate:43.3Mbps Height:237.3m Distance:141.1m HS:0.0m/s VS:3.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.9V delay:28ms bitrate:46.0Mbps Height:238.0m Distance:141.1m HS:0.1m/s VS:3.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.8V delay:29ms bitrate:46.0Mbps Height:238.6m Distance:141.1m HS:0.4m/s VS:3.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.8V delay:31ms bitrate:45.9Mbps Height:238.6m Distance:141.1m HS:0.4m/s VS:3.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.8V delay:32ms bitrate:45.9Mbps Height:239.3m Distance:141.3m HS:1.0m/s VS:3.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.8V delay:30ms bitrate:43.4Mbps Height:240.0m Distance:141.5m HS:1.5m/s VS:3.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.8V delay:39ms bitrate:41.1Mbps Height:240.6m Distance:141.9m HS:2.1m/s VS:3.3m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.8V delay:32ms bitrate:41.1Mbps Height:240.6m Distance:141.9m HS:2.1m/s VS:3.3m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:31ms bitrate:40.3Mbps Height:241.3m Distance:142.3m HS:2.7m/s VS:3.3m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:32ms bitrate:40.3Mbps Height:241.9m Distance:142.9m HS:3.1m/s VS:3.3m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:26ms bitrate:39.9Mbps Height:242.6m Distance:143.6m HS:3.6m/s VS:3.3m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:28ms bitrate:37.6Mbps Height:242.6m Distance:143.6m HS:3.6m/s VS:3.3m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:29ms bitrate:37.6Mbps Height:243.3m Distance:144.3m HS:4.0m/s VS:3.3m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:30ms bitrate:36.5Mbps Height:243.9m Distance:145.2m HS:4.5m/s VS:3.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:35ms bitrate:36.5Mbps Height:244.6m Distance:146.1m HS:4.9m/s VS:3.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:36ms bitrate:36.8Mbps Height:244.6m Distance:146.1m HS:4.9m/s VS:3.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:34ms bitrate:36.7Mbps Height:245.2m Distance:147.2m HS:5.4m/s VS:3.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:36ms bitrate:36.7Mbps Height:245.9m Distance:148.3m HS:5.7m/s VS:3.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:30ms bitrate:35.2Mbps Height:246.5m Distance:149.5m HS:6.1m/s VS:3.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:32ms bitrate:35.2Mbps Height:246.5m Distance:149.5m HS:6.1m/s VS:3.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:43ms bitrate:35.6Mbps Height:247.2m Distance:150.6m HS:6.4m/s VS:3.3m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:34ms bitrate:34.8Mbps Height:247.8m Distance:151.9m HS:6.7m/s VS:3.3m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:46ms bitrate:34.8Mbps Height:248.5m Distance:153.3m HS:7.0m/s VS:3.3m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:28ms bitrate:34.5Mbps Height:249.1m Distance:154.8m HS:7.2m/s VS:3.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:41ms bitrate:34.5Mbps Height:249.1m Distance:154.8m HS:7.2m/s VS:3.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:43ms bitrate:34.8Mbps Height:249.8m Distance:156.2m HS:7.6m/s VS:3.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:32ms bitrate:35.6Mbps Height:250.5m Distance:157.7m HS:7.9m/s VS:3.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:25ms bitrate:35.6Mbps Height:250.5m Distance:157.7m HS:7.9m/s VS:3.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:27ms bitrate:36.0Mbps Height:251.1m Distance:159.3m HS:8.1m/s VS:3.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:39ms bitrate:35.2Mbps Height:251.8m Distance:160.9m HS:8.5m/s VS:3.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:33ms bitrate:35.2Mbps Height:252.4m Distance:162.6m HS:8.7m/s VS:3.3m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:34ms bitrate:36.9Mbps Height:252.4m Distance:162.6m HS:8.7m/s VS:3.3m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:42ms bitrate:36.9Mbps Height:253.1m Distance:164.3m HS:8.9m/s VS:3.3m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:37ms bitrate:38.8Mbps Height:253.8m Distance:166.1m HS:9.1m/s VS:3.3m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:28ms bitrate:38.8Mbps Height:254.4m Distance:168.0m HS:9.4m/s VS:3.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:39ms bitrate:38.4Mbps Height:254.4m Distance:168.0m HS:9.4m/s VS:3.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:31ms bitrate:36.0Mbps Height:255.1m Distance:169.9m HS:9.6m/s VS:3.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:36ms bitrate:36.0Mbps Height:255.7m Distance:171.8m HS:9.7m/s VS:3.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:33ms bitrate:35.3Mbps Height:256.4m Distance:173.7m HS:9.4m/s VS:3.7m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:31ms bitrate:35.3Mbps Height:256.4m Distance:173.7m HS:9.4m/s VS:3.7m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:30ms bitrate:32.3Mbps Height:257.2m Distance:175.3m HS:7.7m/s VS:3.8m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.6V delay:40ms bitrate:33.8Mbps Height:257.8m Distance:176.7m HS:6.2m/s VS:3.5m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.6V delay:42ms bitrate:33.8Mbps Height:258.5m Distance:177.9m HS:4.8m/s VS:3.1m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.6V delay:43ms bitrate:32.9Mbps Height:258.5m Distance:177.9m HS:4.8m/s VS:3.1m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.6V delay:24ms bitrate:32.9Mbps Height:259.1m Distance:178.9m HS:3.4m/s VS:3.0m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.6V delay:32ms bitrate:32.0Mbps Height:259.7m Distance:179.4m HS:1.8m/s VS:2.9m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.6V delay:30ms bitrate:30.8Mbps Height:260.5m Distance:179.7m HS:0.4m/s VS:3.0m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.6V delay:25ms bitrate:30.8Mbps Height:260.5m Distance:179.7m HS:0.4m/s VS:3.0m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:33ms bitrate:33.4Mbps Height:261.1m Distance:179.7m HS:0.2m/s VS:2.9m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:34ms bitrate:33.4Mbps Height:261.7m Distance:179.7m HS:0.4m/s VS:2.9m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:26ms bitrate:37.3Mbps Height:262.3m Distance:179.6m HS:0.4m/s VS:2.9m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:30ms bitrate:41.5Mbps Height:262.3m Distance:179.6m HS:0.4m/s VS:2.9m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:31ms bitrate:41.5Mbps Height:262.8m Distance:179.5m HS:0.4m/s VS:2.9m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:26ms bitrate:44.3Mbps Height:263.4m Distance:179.3m HS:0.4m/s VS:3.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:34ms bitrate:44.3Mbps Height:264.0m Distance:179.2m HS:0.3m/s VS:3.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.7V delay:25ms bitrate:45.7Mbps Height:264.0m Distance:179.2m HS:0.3m/s VS:3.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.7V delay:27ms bitrate:44.0Mbps Height:264.6m Distance:179.1m HS:0.2m/s VS:3.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.7V delay:31ms bitrate:44.0Mbps Height:265.2m Distance:179.0m HS:0.2m/s VS:3.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.7V delay:40ms bitrate:42.8Mbps Height:265.8m Distance:179.0m HS:0.2m/s VS:3.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.7V delay:35ms bitrate:38.9Mbps Height:266.5m Distance:178.9m HS:0.2m/s VS:3.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.7V delay:32ms bitrate:38.9Mbps Height:266.5m Distance:178.9m HS:0.2m/s VS:3.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.9V delay:37ms bitrate:38.2Mbps Height:267.1m Distance:178.8m HS:0.2m/s VS:3.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.9V delay:33ms bitrate:38.4Mbps Height:267.8m Distance:178.8m HS:0.2m/s VS:3.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.9V delay:39ms bitrate:38.4Mbps Height:267.8m Distance:178.8m HS:0.2m/s VS:3.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.9V delay:31ms bitrate:38.4Mbps Height:268.5m Distance:178.7m HS:0.1m/s VS:3.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.9V delay:35ms bitrate:39.0Mbps Height:269.0m Distance:178.7m HS:0.0m/s VS:3.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.9V delay:26ms bitrate:41.3Mbps Height:269.6m Distance:178.7m HS:0.0m/s VS:3.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.9V delay:35ms bitrate:41.3Mbps Height:270.2m Distance:178.7m HS:0.0m/s VS:3.2m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:36ms bitrate:41.8Mbps Height:270.2m Distance:178.7m HS:0.0m/s VS:3.2m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:27ms bitrate:41.8Mbps Height:270.8m Distance:178.7m HS:0.0m/s VS:3.2m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:25ms bitrate:41.3Mbps Height:271.5m Distance:178.7m HS:0.1m/s VS:3.2m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:26ms bitrate:43.4Mbps Height:272.1m Distance:178.7m HS:0.1m/s VS:3.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:29ms bitrate:46.2Mbps Height:272.8m Distance:178.7m HS:0.1m/s VS:3.3m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:27ms bitrate:46.2Mbps Height:273.4m Distance:178.7m HS:0.1m/s VS:3.3m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:25ms bitrate:48.2Mbps Height:274.0m Distance:178.7m HS:0.1m/s VS:3.3m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:30ms bitrate:48.6Mbps Height:274.0m Distance:178.7m HS:0.1m/s VS:3.3m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:34ms bitrate:48.6Mbps Height:274.5m Distance:178.7m HS:0.1m/s VS:3.3m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:26ms bitrate:45.8Mbps Height:275.2m Distance:178.7m HS:0.1m/s VS:3.3m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:27ms bitrate:45.8Mbps Height:275.8m Distance:178.7m HS:0.1m/s VS:3.3m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:32ms bitrate:44.3Mbps Height:275.8m Distance:178.7m HS:0.1m/s VS:3.3m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.6V delay:34ms bitrate:40.8Mbps Height:276.4m Distance:178.7m HS:0.1m/s VS:3.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.6V delay:34ms bitrate:40.8Mbps Height:277.1m Distance:178.7m HS:0.0m/s VS:3.7m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.6V delay:36ms bitrate:36.0Mbps Height:277.8m Distance:178.6m HS:0.0m/s VS:3.3m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.6V delay:34ms bitrate:36.0Mbps Height:277.8m Distance:178.6m HS:0.0m/s VS:3.3m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.6V delay:25ms bitrate:33.2Mbps Height:278.3m Distance:178.6m HS:0.0m/s VS:3.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.6V delay:36ms bitrate:35.7Mbps Height:279.0m Distance:178.6m HS:0.0m/s VS:3.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.6V delay:28ms bitrate:35.7Mbps Height:279.6m Distance:178.6m HS:0.1m/s VS:3.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.6V delay:25ms bitrate:38.6Mbps Height:279.6m Distance:178.6m HS:0.1m/s VS:3.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.6V delay:38ms bitrate:37.5Mbps Height:280.2m Distance:178.6m HS:0.1m/s VS:3.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.6V delay:28ms bitrate:37.5Mbps Height:280.7m Distance:178.5m HS:0.2m/s VS:3.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.6V delay:26ms bitrate:37.1Mbps Height:281.3m Distance:178.5m HS:0.2m/s VS:3.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.6V delay:24ms bitrate:37.1Mbps Height:281.3m Distance:178.5m HS:0.2m/s VS:3.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.6V delay:25ms bitrate:36.2Mbps Height:281.9m Distance:178.5m HS:0.1m/s VS:3.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.6V delay:33ms bitrate:36.2Mbps Height:282.5m Distance:178.4m HS:0.1m/s VS:3.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.6V delay:35ms bitrate:35.1Mbps Height:283.1m Distance:178.4m HS:0.1m/s VS:3.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.6V delay:26ms bitrate:35.5Mbps Height:283.1m Distance:178.4m HS:0.1m/s VS:3.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.6V delay:31ms bitrate:35.5Mbps Height:283.8m Distance:178.4m HS:0.1m/s VS:3.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.6V delay:37ms bitrate:35.6Mbps Height:284.4m Distance:178.3m HS:0.1m/s VS:3.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.6V delay:30ms bitrate:35.9Mbps Height:285.0m Distance:178.3m HS:0.0m/s VS:3.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.6V delay:35ms bitrate:35.9Mbps Height:285.0m Distance:178.3m HS:0.0m/s VS:3.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:30ms bitrate:36.3Mbps Height:285.6m Distance:178.3m HS:0.0m/s VS:3.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:24ms bitrate:36.3Mbps Height:286.2m Distance:178.3m HS:0.0m/s VS:3.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:39ms bitrate:36.2Mbps Height:286.8m Distance:178.3m HS:0.0m/s VS:3.2m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:30ms bitrate:36.9Mbps Height:286.8m Distance:178.3m HS:0.0m/s VS:3.2m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:34ms bitrate:36.9Mbps Height:287.4m Distance:178.3m HS:0.0m/s VS:3.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:36ms bitrate:36.1Mbps Height:288.0m Distance:178.3m HS:0.0m/s VS:3.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:35ms bitrate:36.1Mbps Height:288.5m Distance:178.2m HS:0.0m/s VS:3.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.6V delay:38ms bitrate:36.1Mbps Height:288.5m Distance:178.2m HS:0.0m/s VS:3.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.6V delay:31ms bitrate:35.5Mbps Height:289.1m Distance:178.2m HS:0.0m/s VS:3.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.6V delay:31ms bitrate:35.5Mbps Height:289.7m Distance:178.2m HS:0.0m/s VS:3.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.6V delay:32ms bitrate:34.6Mbps Height:290.3m Distance:178.2m HS:0.0m/s VS:3.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.6V delay:34ms bitrate:34.6Mbps Height:290.3m Distance:178.2m HS:0.0m/s VS:3.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.6V delay:25ms bitrate:34.3Mbps Height:291.0m Distance:178.2m HS:0.0m/s VS:3.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.6V delay:36ms bitrate:35.4Mbps Height:291.6m Distance:178.2m HS:0.0m/s VS:3.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.5V delay:28ms bitrate:35.4Mbps Height:292.2m Distance:178.2m HS:0.0m/s VS:3.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.5V delay:29ms bitrate:34.2Mbps Height:292.2m Distance:178.2m HS:0.0m/s VS:3.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.5V delay:34ms bitrate:34.2Mbps Height:292.8m Distance:178.2m HS:0.0m/s VS:3.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.5V delay:25ms bitrate:32.1Mbps Height:293.4m Distance:178.3m HS:0.0m/s VS:3.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.5V delay:26ms bitrate:33.1Mbps Height:294.0m Distance:178.3m HS:0.0m/s VS:3.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.5V delay:21ms bitrate:33.1Mbps Height:294.0m Distance:178.3m HS:0.0m/s VS:3.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.7V delay:29ms bitrate:35.1Mbps Height:294.7m Distance:178.3m HS:0.0m/s VS:3.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.7V delay:30ms bitrate:35.1Mbps Height:295.3m Distance:178.3m HS:0.0m/s VS:3.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.7V delay:32ms bitrate:38.3Mbps Height:295.9m Distance:178.3m HS:0.0m/s VS:3.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.7V delay:22ms bitrate:41.5Mbps Height:295.9m Distance:178.3m HS:0.0m/s VS:3.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.7V delay:24ms bitrate:41.5Mbps Height:296.5m Distance:178.3m HS:0.0m/s VS:3.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.7V delay:22ms bitrate:44.8Mbps Height:297.1m Distance:178.3m HS:0.0m/s VS:3.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.7V delay:30ms bitrate:44.8Mbps Height:297.7m Distance:178.3m HS:0.0m/s VS:3.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:22ms bitrate:47.3Mbps Height:297.7m Distance:178.3m HS:0.0m/s VS:3.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:33ms bitrate:48.4Mbps Height:298.3m Distance:178.3m HS:0.0m/s VS:3.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:27ms bitrate:48.4Mbps Height:299.0m Distance:178.3m HS:0.0m/s VS:3.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:29ms bitrate:48.7Mbps Height:299.6m Distance:178.3m HS:0.0m/s VS:3.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:26ms bitrate:48.7Mbps Height:299.6m Distance:178.3m HS:0.0m/s VS:3.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:24ms bitrate:49.4Mbps Height:300.2m Distance:178.3m HS:0.0m/s VS:3.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:33ms bitrate:49.6Mbps Height:300.8m Distance:178.3m HS:0.0m/s VS:3.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:24ms bitrate:49.6Mbps Height:301.4m Distance:178.3m HS:0.0m/s VS:3.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:25ms bitrate:49.9Mbps Height:301.4m Distance:178.3m HS:0.0m/s VS:3.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:27ms bitrate:49.9Mbps Height:302.0m Distance:178.3m HS:0.0m/s VS:3.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:24ms bitrate:50.0Mbps Height:302.6m Distance:178.3m HS:0.0m/s VS:3.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:26ms bitrate:50.0Mbps Height:303.2m Distance:178.3m HS:0.0m/s VS:3.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:24ms bitrate:50.0Mbps Height:303.2m Distance:178.3m HS:0.0m/s VS:3.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.7V delay:25ms bitrate:49.8Mbps Height:303.9m Distance:178.3m HS:0.0m/s VS:3.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.7V delay:27ms bitrate:49.8Mbps Height:304.5m Distance:178.4m HS:0.0m/s VS:3.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.7V delay:32ms bitrate:47.8Mbps Height:305.1m Distance:178.4m HS:0.0m/s VS:3.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.7V delay:32ms bitrate:43.5Mbps Height:305.1m Distance:178.4m HS:0.0m/s VS:3.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.7V delay:34ms bitrate:43.5Mbps Height:305.7m Distance:178.4m HS:0.0m/s VS:3.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.7V delay:35ms bitrate:41.6Mbps Height:306.4m Distance:178.4m HS:0.0m/s VS:3.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.7V delay:26ms bitrate:41.6Mbps Height:307.0m Distance:178.4m HS:0.0m/s VS:3.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.7V delay:38ms bitrate:40.6Mbps Height:307.0m Distance:178.4m HS:0.0m/s VS:3.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.7V delay:29ms bitrate:41.3Mbps Height:307.6m Distance:178.4m HS:0.0m/s VS:3.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.7V delay:27ms bitrate:41.3Mbps Height:308.2m Distance:178.4m HS:0.0m/s VS:3.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.7V delay:25ms bitrate:44.7Mbps Height:308.9m Distance:178.4m HS:0.4m/s VS:3.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.7V delay:29ms bitrate:44.7Mbps Height:308.9m Distance:178.4m HS:0.4m/s VS:3.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.7V delay:31ms bitrate:45.2Mbps Height:309.5m Distance:178.5m HS:0.7m/s VS:3.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.7V delay:39ms bitrate:40.1Mbps Height:310.1m Distance:178.6m HS:0.4m/s VS:3.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.7V delay:33ms bitrate:40.1Mbps Height:310.8m Distance:178.6m HS:0.1m/s VS:3.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.7V delay:35ms bitrate:38.4Mbps Height:310.8m Distance:178.6m HS:0.1m/s VS:3.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.7V delay:36ms bitrate:38.4Mbps Height:311.4m Distance:178.6m HS:0.0m/s VS:3.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.7V delay:34ms bitrate:36.1Mbps Height:312.0m Distance:178.6m HS:0.0m/s VS:3.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.7V delay:36ms bitrate:35.4Mbps Height:312.7m Distance:178.6m HS:0.1m/s VS:3.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.7V delay:30ms bitrate:35.4Mbps Height:312.7m Distance:178.6m HS:0.1m/s VS:3.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:25ms bitrate:36.5Mbps Height:313.4m Distance:178.6m HS:0.0m/s VS:3.6m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:23ms bitrate:36.5Mbps Height:314.1m Distance:178.6m HS:0.0m/s VS:3.7m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:34ms bitrate:37.7Mbps Height:314.8m Distance:178.6m HS:0.0m/s VS:3.7m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:35ms bitrate:34.2Mbps Height:314.8m Distance:178.6m HS:0.0m/s VS:3.7m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:23ms bitrate:34.2Mbps Height:315.5m Distance:178.6m HS:0.0m/s VS:3.8m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:24ms bitrate:32.8Mbps Height:316.3m Distance:178.6m HS:0.1m/s VS:3.8m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:23ms bitrate:32.8Mbps Height:317.1m Distance:178.6m HS:0.1m/s VS:3.8m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:28ms bitrate:32.4Mbps Height:317.8m Distance:178.6m HS:0.1m/s VS:3.8m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:25ms bitrate:31.9Mbps Height:317.8m Distance:178.6m HS:0.1m/s VS:3.8m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:27ms bitrate:31.9Mbps Height:318.6m Distance:178.6m HS:0.1m/s VS:3.8m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:31ms bitrate:34.9Mbps Height:319.3m Distance:178.5m HS:0.1m/s VS:3.8m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:32ms bitrate:34.9Mbps Height:319.3m Distance:178.5m HS:0.1m/s VS:3.8m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:34ms bitrate:35.8Mbps Height:320.1m Distance:178.5m HS:0.1m/s VS:3.8m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:9.0V delay:25ms bitrate:34.7Mbps Height:320.8m Distance:178.5m HS:0.1m/s VS:3.8m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:9.0V delay:30ms bitrate:34.7Mbps Height:321.6m Distance:178.5m HS:0.1m/s VS:3.8m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:9.0V delay:31ms bitrate:34.2Mbps Height:321.6m Distance:178.5m HS:0.1m/s VS:3.8m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:9.0V delay:32ms bitrate:34.2Mbps Height:322.3m Distance:178.5m HS:0.0m/s VS:3.8m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:9.0V delay:34ms bitrate:34.3Mbps Height:323.1m Distance:178.5m HS:0.0m/s VS:3.8m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:9.0V delay:22ms bitrate:34.2Mbps Height:323.8m Distance:178.5m HS:0.0m/s VS:3.8m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:9.0V delay:26ms bitrate:34.2Mbps Height:323.8m Distance:178.5m HS:0.0m/s VS:3.8m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:28ms bitrate:35.4Mbps Height:324.5m Distance:178.5m HS:0.0m/s VS:3.8m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:32ms bitrate:35.4Mbps Height:325.2m Distance:178.5m HS:0.0m/s VS:3.8m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:33ms bitrate:35.7Mbps Height:326.0m Distance:178.5m HS:0.0m/s VS:3.8m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:32ms bitrate:36.7Mbps Height:326.0m Distance:178.5m HS:0.0m/s VS:3.8m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:29ms bitrate:36.7Mbps Height:326.7m Distance:178.4m HS:0.0m/s VS:4.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:24ms bitrate:38.0Mbps Height:327.7m Distance:178.5m HS:0.0m/s VS:5.4m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:36ms bitrate:38.0Mbps Height:328.8m Distance:178.5m HS:0.1m/s VS:6.6m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.2V delay:33ms bitrate:37.5Mbps Height:330.2m Distance:178.5m HS:0.0m/s VS:7.3m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.2V delay:35ms bitrate:37.6Mbps Height:330.2m Distance:178.5m HS:0.0m/s VS:7.3m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.2V delay:34ms bitrate:37.6Mbps Height:331.7m Distance:178.5m HS:0.0m/s VS:7.6m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.2V delay:34ms bitrate:37.6Mbps Height:333.3m Distance:178.5m HS:0.0m/s VS:7.8m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.2V delay:25ms bitrate:37.6Mbps Height:334.9m Distance:178.5m HS:0.0m/s VS:7.9m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.2V delay:31ms bitrate:38.1Mbps Height:334.9m Distance:178.5m HS:0.0m/s VS:7.9m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.5V delay:28ms bitrate:36.4Mbps Height:336.4m Distance:178.5m HS:0.1m/s VS:7.3m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.5V delay:23ms bitrate:36.4Mbps Height:337.8m Distance:178.5m HS:0.1m/s VS:6.3m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.5V delay:24ms bitrate:36.1Mbps Height:339.0m Distance:178.5m HS:0.1m/s VS:5.4m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.5V delay:25ms bitrate:36.1Mbps Height:339.0m Distance:178.5m HS:0.1m/s VS:5.4m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.5V delay:27ms bitrate:35.9Mbps Height:340.0m Distance:178.5m HS:0.1m/s VS:4.7m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.5V delay:28ms bitrate:35.5Mbps Height:341.0m Distance:178.5m HS:0.0m/s VS:4.4m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.5V delay:26ms bitrate:35.5Mbps Height:341.8m Distance:178.5m HS:0.0m/s VS:4.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.4V delay:35ms bitrate:34.9Mbps Height:341.8m Distance:178.5m HS:0.0m/s VS:4.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.4V delay:25ms bitrate:34.9Mbps Height:342.6m Distance:178.5m HS:0.0m/s VS:4.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.4V delay:26ms bitrate:35.2Mbps Height:343.4m Distance:178.5m HS:0.0m/s VS:3.8m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.4V delay:28ms bitrate:34.5Mbps Height:344.1m Distance:178.5m HS:0.0m/s VS:3.7m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.4V delay:29ms bitrate:34.5Mbps Height:344.1m Distance:178.5m HS:0.0m/s VS:3.7m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.4V delay:34ms bitrate:34.4Mbps Height:344.8m Distance:178.5m HS:0.0m/s VS:3.7m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.4V delay:32ms bitrate:34.4Mbps Height:345.5m Distance:178.5m HS:0.2m/s VS:3.6m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.4V delay:33ms bitrate:33.9Mbps Height:346.2m Distance:178.6m HS:0.5m/s VS:3.6m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.4V delay:38ms bitrate:35.5Mbps Height:346.2m Distance:178.6m HS:0.5m/s VS:3.6m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.4V delay:32ms bitrate:35.5Mbps Height:346.8m Distance:178.8m HS:0.9m/s VS:3.4m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.4V delay:33ms bitrate:34.3Mbps Height:347.5m Distance:179.0m HS:1.4m/s VS:3.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.4V delay:35ms bitrate:34.3Mbps Height:348.1m Distance:179.3m HS:1.7m/s VS:3.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.4V delay:33ms bitrate:35.5Mbps Height:348.1m Distance:179.3m HS:1.7m/s VS:3.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:27ms bitrate:34.0Mbps Height:348.7m Distance:179.6m HS:2.0m/s VS:3.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:36ms bitrate:34.0Mbps Height:349.4m Distance:180.0m HS:2.2m/s VS:3.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:26ms bitrate:33.7Mbps Height:350.0m Distance:180.4m HS:2.2m/s VS:2.8m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:31ms bitrate:33.7Mbps Height:350.0m Distance:180.4m HS:2.2m/s VS:2.8m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:29ms bitrate:34.6Mbps Height:350.5m Distance:180.9m HS:2.2m/s VS:2.6m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:34ms bitrate:34.0Mbps Height:351.0m Distance:181.3m HS:2.1m/s VS:2.5m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:29ms bitrate:34.0Mbps Height:351.5m Distance:181.7m HS:2.1m/s VS:2.4m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:40ms bitrate:34.8Mbps Height:351.5m Distance:181.7m HS:2.1m/s VS:2.4m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:34ms bitrate:34.8Mbps Height:351.9m Distance:182.1m HS:1.9m/s VS:2.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:43ms bitrate:31.9Mbps Height:352.3m Distance:182.4m HS:1.1m/s VS:2.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:27ms bitrate:32.6Mbps Height:352.8m Distance:182.6m HS:0.5m/s VS:1.9m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:25ms bitrate:32.6Mbps Height:352.8m Distance:182.6m HS:0.5m/s VS:1.9m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:27ms bitrate:33.1Mbps Height:353.1m Distance:182.7m HS:0.1m/s VS:1.6m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:24ms bitrate:33.1Mbps Height:353.4m Distance:182.8m HS:0.1m/s VS:1.5m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.4V delay:29ms bitrate:33.4Mbps Height:353.8m Distance:182.7m HS:0.2m/s VS:1.3m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.4V delay:27ms bitrate:33.6Mbps Height:353.8m Distance:182.7m HS:0.2m/s VS:1.3m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.4V delay:25ms bitrate:33.6Mbps Height:354.0m Distance:182.7m HS:0.2m/s VS:1.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.4V delay:26ms bitrate:33.9Mbps Height:354.2m Distance:182.6m HS:0.2m/s VS:1.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.4V delay:31ms bitrate:33.3Mbps Height:354.4m Distance:182.5m HS:0.2m/s VS:0.7m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.4V delay:29ms bitrate:33.3Mbps Height:354.4m Distance:182.5m HS:0.2m/s VS:0.7m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.0V delay:31ms bitrate:33.1Mbps Height:354.5m Distance:182.5m HS:0.1m/s VS:0.5m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.0V delay:25ms bitrate:33.1Mbps Height:354.5m Distance:182.4m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.4m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.0V delay:33ms bitrate:33.4Mbps Height:354.6m Distance:182.4m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.0V delay:41ms bitrate:33.4Mbps Height:354.6m Distance:182.4m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.0V delay:25ms bitrate:32.5Mbps Height:354.5m Distance:182.4m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.0V delay:30ms bitrate:32.7Mbps Height:354.5m Distance:182.4m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.0V delay:32ms bitrate:32.7Mbps Height:354.5m Distance:182.4m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:33ms bitrate:34.0Mbps Height:354.5m Distance:182.4m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:27ms bitrate:33.1Mbps Height:354.4m Distance:182.5m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:36ms bitrate:33.1Mbps Height:354.4m Distance:182.5m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:30ms bitrate:33.3Mbps Height:354.4m Distance:182.5m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:35ms bitrate:33.3Mbps Height:354.4m Distance:182.5m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:26ms bitrate:33.3Mbps Height:354.3m Distance:182.5m HS:0.1m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:27ms bitrate:33.6Mbps Height:354.3m Distance:182.6m HS:0.3m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:36ms bitrate:33.6Mbps Height:354.3m Distance:182.7m HS:0.9m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:27ms bitrate:35.7Mbps Height:354.3m Distance:182.7m HS:0.9m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:28ms bitrate:35.7Mbps Height:354.3m Distance:183.0m HS:1.4m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:30ms bitrate:35.2Mbps Height:354.3m Distance:183.3m HS:1.8m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:24ms bitrate:34.9Mbps Height:354.3m Distance:183.7m HS:2.3m/s VS:0.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:35ms bitrate:34.9Mbps Height:354.3m Distance:183.7m HS:2.3m/s VS:0.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.0V delay:31ms bitrate:34.7Mbps Height:354.3m Distance:184.1m HS:2.8m/s VS:0.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.0V delay:34ms bitrate:34.7Mbps Height:354.3m Distance:184.7m HS:3.2m/s VS:0.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.0V delay:29ms bitrate:34.3Mbps Height:354.3m Distance:185.3m HS:3.6m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.0V delay:34ms bitrate:34.5Mbps Height:354.3m Distance:185.3m HS:3.6m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.0V delay:32ms bitrate:34.5Mbps Height:354.3m Distance:186.0m HS:4.0m/s VS:0.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.0V delay:40ms bitrate:34.3Mbps Height:354.3m Distance:186.8m HS:4.3m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.0V delay:38ms bitrate:34.3Mbps Height:354.3m Distance:187.7m HS:4.7m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.9V delay:42ms bitrate:34.2Mbps Height:354.3m Distance:187.7m HS:4.7m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.9V delay:32ms bitrate:32.1Mbps Height:354.3m Distance:188.6m HS:5.0m/s VS:0.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.9V delay:42ms bitrate:32.1Mbps Height:354.3m Distance:189.5m HS:5.3m/s VS:0.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.9V delay:33ms bitrate:30.7Mbps Height:354.3m Distance:190.5m HS:5.7m/s VS:0.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.9V delay:39ms bitrate:30.7Mbps Height:354.4m Distance:191.6m HS:5.9m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.9V delay:26ms bitrate:30.8Mbps Height:354.4m Distance:191.6m HS:5.9m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.9V delay:37ms bitrate:30.3Mbps Height:354.4m Distance:192.7m HS:6.2m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.1V delay:37ms bitrate:30.3Mbps Height:354.4m Distance:193.9m HS:6.4m/s VS:0.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.1V delay:23ms bitrate:29.6Mbps Height:354.4m Distance:193.9m HS:6.4m/s VS:0.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.1V delay:24ms bitrate:29.6Mbps Height:354.4m Distance:195.1m HS:6.7m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.1V delay:26ms bitrate:29.6Mbps Height:354.4m Distance:196.4m HS:7.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.1V delay:27ms bitrate:31.8Mbps Height:354.4m Distance:197.8m HS:7.2m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.1V delay:28ms bitrate:31.8Mbps Height:354.4m Distance:197.8m HS:7.2m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:26ms bitrate:33.0Mbps Height:354.4m Distance:199.1m HS:7.4m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:34ms bitrate:33.0Mbps Height:354.4m Distance:200.5m HS:7.5m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:39ms bitrate:32.0Mbps Height:354.4m Distance:201.9m HS:7.7m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:33ms bitrate:32.0Mbps Height:354.4m Distance:201.9m HS:7.7m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:38ms bitrate:32.0Mbps Height:354.4m Distance:203.4m HS:7.9m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:30ms bitrate:30.6Mbps Height:354.4m Distance:204.8m HS:8.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:44ms bitrate:30.6Mbps Height:354.4m Distance:206.3m HS:8.2m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.2V delay:35ms bitrate:31.4Mbps Height:354.4m Distance:206.3m HS:8.2m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.2V delay:37ms bitrate:31.9Mbps Height:354.4m Distance:207.9m HS:8.3m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.2V delay:28ms bitrate:31.9Mbps Height:354.3m Distance:209.4m HS:8.5m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.2V delay:29ms bitrate:33.4Mbps Height:354.4m Distance:211.0m HS:8.6m/s VS:0.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.2V delay:31ms bitrate:33.4Mbps Height:354.4m Distance:211.0m HS:8.6m/s VS:0.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.2V delay:35ms bitrate:36.3Mbps Height:354.4m Distance:212.6m HS:8.7m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.9V delay:33ms bitrate:32.7Mbps Height:354.4m Distance:214.3m HS:8.4m/s VS:0.4m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.9V delay:28ms bitrate:32.7Mbps Height:354.4m Distance:215.7m HS:7.2m/s VS:0.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.9V delay:26ms bitrate:32.7Mbps Height:354.4m Distance:215.7m HS:7.2m/s VS:0.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.9V delay:31ms bitrate:32.7Mbps Height:354.5m Distance:216.9m HS:5.8m/s VS:0.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.9V delay:35ms bitrate:32.6Mbps Height:354.5m Distance:218.0m HS:4.5m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.9V delay:43ms bitrate:30.7Mbps Height:354.5m Distance:218.9m HS:3.3m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.9V delay:32ms bitrate:30.7Mbps Height:354.5m Distance:219.5m HS:2.1m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.2V delay:26ms bitrate:29.7Mbps Height:354.5m Distance:219.5m HS:2.1m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.2V delay:27ms bitrate:29.7Mbps Height:354.5m Distance:219.8m HS:0.9m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.2V delay:29ms bitrate:29.9Mbps Height:354.5m Distance:219.9m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.2V delay:33ms bitrate:31.8Mbps Height:354.5m Distance:219.9m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.2V delay:28ms bitrate:31.8Mbps Height:354.5m Distance:219.9m HS:0.2m/s VS:0.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.2V delay:26ms bitrate:31.9Mbps Height:354.6m Distance:219.8m HS:0.3m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.2V delay:30ms bitrate:31.9Mbps Height:354.5m Distance:219.7m HS:0.4m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:25ms bitrate:34.1Mbps Height:354.5m Distance:219.7m HS:0.4m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:26ms bitrate:32.3Mbps Height:354.5m Distance:219.5m HS:0.4m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:34ms bitrate:32.3Mbps Height:354.5m Distance:219.4m HS:0.4m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:36ms bitrate:32.4Mbps Height:354.5m Distance:219.2m HS:0.4m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:37ms bitrate:32.4Mbps Height:354.5m Distance:219.2m HS:0.4m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:38ms bitrate:31.8Mbps Height:354.5m Distance:219.1m HS:0.3m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.3V delay:40ms bitrate:32.3Mbps Height:354.5m Distance:219.0m HS:0.3m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.3V delay:31ms bitrate:32.3Mbps Height:354.4m Distance:218.8m HS:0.3m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.3V delay:32ms bitrate:33.6Mbps Height:354.4m Distance:218.8m HS:0.3m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.3V delay:34ms bitrate:33.6Mbps Height:354.4m Distance:218.8m HS:0.2m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.3V delay:25ms bitrate:33.1Mbps Height:354.4m Distance:218.7m HS:0.2m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.3V delay:33ms bitrate:33.2Mbps Height:354.4m Distance:218.6m HS:0.2m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.3V delay:44ms bitrate:33.2Mbps Height:354.4m Distance:218.5m HS:0.2m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.2V delay:25ms bitrate:33.4Mbps Height:354.4m Distance:218.5m HS:0.2m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.2V delay:35ms bitrate:33.7Mbps Height:354.4m Distance:218.5m HS:0.2m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.2V delay:45ms bitrate:33.7Mbps Height:354.4m Distance:218.4m HS:0.1m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.2V delay:36ms bitrate:33.5Mbps Height:354.4m Distance:218.4m HS:0.1m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.2V delay:31ms bitrate:33.5Mbps Height:354.4m Distance:218.4m HS:0.1m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.2V delay:25ms bitrate:32.8Mbps Height:354.4m Distance:218.3m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.2V delay:26ms bitrate:32.8Mbps Height:354.3m Distance:218.3m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.3V delay:38ms bitrate:33.3Mbps Height:354.3m Distance:218.3m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.3V delay:39ms bitrate:33.4Mbps Height:354.3m Distance:218.3m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.3V delay:37ms bitrate:33.4Mbps Height:354.4m Distance:218.3m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.3V delay:35ms bitrate:33.8Mbps Height:354.3m Distance:218.3m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.3V delay:43ms bitrate:33.8Mbps Height:354.4m Distance:218.3m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.3V delay:31ms bitrate:33.1Mbps Height:354.4m Distance:218.3m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.2V delay:36ms bitrate:34.4Mbps Height:354.4m Distance:218.3m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.2V delay:27ms bitrate:34.4Mbps Height:354.4m Distance:218.3m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.2V delay:29ms bitrate:34.4Mbps Height:354.4m Distance:218.3m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.2V delay:33ms bitrate:34.4Mbps Height:354.4m Distance:218.3m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.2V delay:34ms bitrate:33.4Mbps Height:354.4m Distance:218.3m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.2V delay:36ms bitrate:33.2Mbps Height:354.4m Distance:218.3m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.2V delay:27ms bitrate:33.2Mbps Height:354.4m Distance:218.4m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.2V delay:31ms bitrate:33.7Mbps Height:354.4m Distance:218.4m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.2V delay:30ms bitrate:33.7Mbps Height:354.4m Distance:218.4m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.2V delay:31ms bitrate:32.7Mbps Height:354.4m Distance:218.4m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.2V delay:34ms bitrate:33.1Mbps Height:354.4m Distance:218.4m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.2V delay:37ms bitrate:33.1Mbps Height:354.4m Distance:218.4m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.2V delay:38ms bitrate:32.3Mbps Height:354.4m Distance:218.4m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.2V delay:34ms bitrate:33.0Mbps Height:354.4m Distance:218.4m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.2V delay:31ms bitrate:33.0Mbps Height:354.4m Distance:218.4m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.2V delay:35ms bitrate:34.6Mbps Height:354.4m Distance:218.4m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.2V delay:37ms bitrate:34.6Mbps Height:354.4m Distance:218.4m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.2V delay:38ms bitrate:33.1Mbps Height:354.4m Distance:218.4m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.2V delay:29ms bitrate:33.1Mbps Height:354.4m Distance:218.5m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.2V delay:41ms bitrate:33.1Mbps Height:354.4m Distance:218.5m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.1V delay:32ms bitrate:32.4Mbps Height:354.4m Distance:218.5m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.1V delay:33ms bitrate:32.4Mbps Height:354.4m Distance:218.5m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.1V delay:35ms bitrate:33.0Mbps Height:354.4m Distance:218.5m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.1V delay:39ms bitrate:33.0Mbps Height:354.4m Distance:218.5m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.1V delay:41ms bitrate:33.3Mbps Height:354.4m Distance:218.5m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.1V delay:28ms bitrate:32.8Mbps Height:354.4m Distance:218.5m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.1V delay:33ms bitrate:32.8Mbps Height:354.4m Distance:218.5m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:38ms bitrate:32.9Mbps Height:354.4m Distance:218.5m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:39ms bitrate:32.9Mbps Height:354.4m Distance:218.5m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:33ms bitrate:32.4Mbps Height:354.4m Distance:218.5m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:42ms bitrate:33.4Mbps Height:354.4m Distance:218.5m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:43ms bitrate:33.4Mbps Height:354.4m Distance:218.5m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:34ms bitrate:33.9Mbps Height:354.4m Distance:218.5m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:26ms bitrate:33.9Mbps Height:354.4m Distance:218.5m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:47ms bitrate:33.6Mbps Height:354.4m Distance:218.6m HS:0.4m/s VS:0.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:38ms bitrate:32.0Mbps Height:354.4m Distance:218.6m HS:0.4m/s VS:0.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:43ms bitrate:32.0Mbps Height:354.4m Distance:218.8m HS:1.9m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:34ms bitrate:31.8Mbps Height:354.5m Distance:219.2m HS:3.4m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:36ms bitrate:31.8Mbps Height:354.4m Distance:219.9m HS:4.5m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:37ms bitrate:33.2Mbps Height:354.4m Distance:219.9m HS:4.5m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.1V delay:28ms bitrate:33.7Mbps Height:354.4m Distance:220.7m HS:5.6m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.1V delay:30ms bitrate:33.7Mbps Height:354.4m Distance:221.7m HS:6.8m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.1V delay:31ms bitrate:34.2Mbps Height:354.4m Distance:223.0m HS:7.8m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.1V delay:32ms bitrate:34.2Mbps Height:354.4m Distance:223.0m HS:7.8m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.1V delay:34ms bitrate:35.7Mbps Height:354.4m Distance:224.4m HS:8.7m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.1V delay:35ms bitrate:35.4Mbps Height:354.4m Distance:226.0m HS:9.5m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.1V delay:29ms bitrate:35.4Mbps Height:354.4m Distance:227.7m HS:10.3m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.1V delay:41ms bitrate:34.7Mbps Height:354.4m Distance:227.7m HS:10.3m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.1V delay:38ms bitrate:34.7Mbps Height:354.4m Distance:229.5m HS:11.1m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.1V delay:33ms bitrate:33.3Mbps Height:354.4m Distance:231.6m HS:11.8m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.1V delay:35ms bitrate:33.4Mbps Height:354.4m Distance:233.7m HS:12.4m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.1V delay:26ms bitrate:33.4Mbps Height:354.4m Distance:233.7m HS:12.4m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.1V delay:41ms bitrate:31.5Mbps Height:354.4m Distance:235.9m HS:13.1m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.1V delay:25ms bitrate:31.5Mbps Height:354.4m Distance:238.2m HS:13.6m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.3V delay:26ms bitrate:32.7Mbps Height:354.5m Distance:240.8m HS:14.2m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.3V delay:38ms bitrate:35.7Mbps Height:354.5m Distance:240.8m HS:14.2m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.3V delay:36ms bitrate:35.7Mbps Height:354.5m Distance:243.2m HS:14.7m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.3V delay:30ms bitrate:33.9Mbps Height:354.5m Distance:245.9m HS:15.2m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.3V delay:35ms bitrate:33.9Mbps Height:354.5m Distance:248.6m HS:15.7m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.3V delay:26ms bitrate:32.7Mbps Height:354.5m Distance:248.6m HS:15.7m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.2V delay:34ms bitrate:34.1Mbps Height:354.6m Distance:251.5m HS:16.1m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.2V delay:39ms bitrate:34.1Mbps Height:354.6m Distance:254.3m HS:16.5m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.2V delay:40ms bitrate:33.1Mbps Height:354.6m Distance:257.3m HS:16.9m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.2V delay:42ms bitrate:32.0Mbps Height:354.6m Distance:257.3m HS:16.9m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.2V delay:26ms bitrate:32.0Mbps Height:354.6m Distance:260.4m HS:17.4m/s VS:0.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.2V delay:27ms bitrate:32.2Mbps Height:354.7m Distance:263.5m HS:17.7m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.2V delay:26ms bitrate:32.2Mbps Height:354.7m Distance:266.7m HS:18.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:27ms bitrate:35.3Mbps Height:354.7m Distance:266.7m HS:18.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:38ms bitrate:35.3Mbps Height:354.8m Distance:270.0m HS:18.3m/s VS:0.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:33ms bitrate:34.2Mbps Height:354.8m Distance:273.3m HS:18.6m/s VS:0.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:24ms bitrate:32.5Mbps Height:354.8m Distance:276.6m HS:18.8m/s VS:0.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:35ms bitrate:32.5Mbps Height:354.8m Distance:276.6m HS:18.8m/s VS:0.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:27ms bitrate:30.6Mbps Height:354.9m Distance:280.2m HS:19.0m/s VS:0.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:28ms bitrate:32.3Mbps Height:354.9m Distance:283.5m HS:19.3m/s VS:0.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.9V delay:40ms bitrate:32.3Mbps Height:354.9m Distance:287.0m HS:19.5m/s VS:0.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.9V delay:41ms bitrate:33.0Mbps Height:354.9m Distance:287.0m HS:19.5m/s VS:0.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.9V delay:25ms bitrate:33.0Mbps Height:354.9m Distance:290.5m HS:19.7m/s VS:0.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.9V delay:27ms bitrate:33.9Mbps Height:354.9m Distance:294.1m HS:19.9m/s VS:0.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.9V delay:35ms bitrate:33.3Mbps Height:354.9m Distance:297.7m HS:20.1m/s VS:0.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.9V delay:26ms bitrate:33.3Mbps Height:354.9m Distance:297.7m HS:20.1m/s VS:0.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:34ms bitrate:33.8Mbps Height:354.9m Distance:301.4m HS:20.2m/s VS:0.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:42ms bitrate:33.8Mbps Height:355.0m Distance:305.1m HS:20.3m/s VS:0.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:36ms bitrate:32.1Mbps Height:354.9m Distance:308.8m HS:20.5m/s VS:0.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:36ms bitrate:31.6Mbps Height:354.9m Distance:312.6m HS:20.5m/s VS:0.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:26ms bitrate:31.6Mbps Height:354.9m Distance:312.6m HS:20.5m/s VS:0.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:30ms bitrate:31.8Mbps Height:354.9m Distance:316.3m HS:20.5m/s VS:0.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:32ms bitrate:31.8Mbps Height:354.9m Distance:320.1m HS:20.6m/s VS:0.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:43ms bitrate:34.4Mbps Height:354.9m Distance:320.1m HS:20.6m/s VS:0.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:28ms bitrate:33.4Mbps Height:354.9m Distance:323.9m HS:20.6m/s VS:0.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:36ms bitrate:33.4Mbps Height:354.9m Distance:327.9m HS:20.4m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:37ms bitrate:33.3Mbps Height:354.9m Distance:331.4m HS:20.0m/s VS:0.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:39ms bitrate:33.3Mbps Height:354.9m Distance:331.4m HS:20.0m/s VS:0.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:30ms bitrate:29.0Mbps Height:355.0m Distance:335.3m HS:19.6m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.0V delay:41ms bitrate:27.9Mbps Height:355.0m Distance:338.8m HS:18.7m/s VS:0.4m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.0V delay:26ms bitrate:27.9Mbps Height:355.1m Distance:342.1m HS:16.5m/s VS:0.4m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.0V delay:37ms bitrate:22.6Mbps Height:355.1m Distance:342.1m HS:16.5m/s VS:0.4m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.0V delay:38ms bitrate:22.6Mbps Height:355.1m Distance:345.0m HS:14.5m/s VS:0.4m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.0V delay:30ms bitrate:20.7Mbps Height:355.0m Distance:347.6m HS:11.8m/s VS:0.4m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.0V delay:44ms bitrate:19.2Mbps Height:355.0m Distance:349.7m HS:9.1m/s VS:0.3m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.0V delay:35ms bitrate:19.2Mbps Height:355.0m Distance:349.7m HS:9.1m/s VS:0.3m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.9V delay:24ms bitrate:14.8Mbps Height:355.0m Distance:351.3m HS:6.8m/s VS:0.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.9V delay:28ms bitrate:14.8Mbps Height:355.0m Distance:352.4m HS:4.9m/s VS:0.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.9V delay:37ms bitrate:14.1Mbps Height:355.0m Distance:353.4m HS:3.2m/s VS:0.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.9V delay:31ms bitrate:14.7Mbps Height:355.0m Distance:353.4m HS:3.2m/s VS:0.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.9V delay:25ms bitrate:14.7Mbps Height:355.0m Distance:353.9m HS:1.5m/s VS:0.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.9V delay:27ms bitrate:16.8Mbps Height:355.0m Distance:354.1m HS:0.3m/s VS:0.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.9V delay:28ms bitrate:16.8Mbps Height:354.9m Distance:354.1m HS:0.2m/s VS:0.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.1V delay:36ms bitrate:19.8Mbps Height:354.9m Distance:354.1m HS:0.2m/s VS:0.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.1V delay:41ms bitrate:21.7Mbps Height:354.9m Distance:354.1m HS:0.4m/s VS:0.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.1V delay:35ms bitrate:21.7Mbps Height:354.8m Distance:353.9m HS:0.4m/s VS:0.3m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.1V delay:25ms bitrate:20.5Mbps Height:354.7m Distance:353.8m HS:0.4m/s VS:0.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.1V delay:28ms bitrate:20.5Mbps Height:354.7m Distance:353.8m HS:0.4m/s VS:0.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.1V delay:26ms bitrate:22.1Mbps Height:354.7m Distance:353.6m HS:0.4m/s VS:0.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:27ms bitrate:22.9Mbps Height:354.6m Distance:353.5m HS:0.4m/s VS:0.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:29ms bitrate:22.9Mbps Height:354.6m Distance:353.3m HS:0.3m/s VS:0.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:30ms bitrate:22.9Mbps Height:354.6m Distance:353.3m HS:0.3m/s VS:0.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:28ms bitrate:22.9Mbps Height:354.6m Distance:353.2m HS:0.3m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:29ms bitrate:23.2Mbps Height:354.5m Distance:353.1m HS:0.3m/s VS:0.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:37ms bitrate:23.1Mbps Height:354.4m Distance:353.1m HS:0.2m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:39ms bitrate:23.1Mbps Height:354.4m Distance:353.1m HS:0.2m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:30ms bitrate:22.6Mbps Height:354.3m Distance:353.0m HS:0.2m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:31ms bitrate:22.6Mbps Height:354.3m Distance:352.9m HS:0.2m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:26ms bitrate:22.9Mbps Height:354.2m Distance:352.9m HS:0.2m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:27ms bitrate:23.0Mbps Height:354.2m Distance:352.8m HS:0.2m/s VS:0.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:25ms bitrate:23.0Mbps Height:354.2m Distance:352.8m HS:0.2m/s VS:0.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:30ms bitrate:22.8Mbps Height:354.1m Distance:352.8m HS:0.2m/s VS:0.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:31ms bitrate:22.8Mbps Height:354.1m Distance:352.8m HS:0.1m/s VS:0.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.0V delay:26ms bitrate:23.1Mbps Height:354.0m Distance:352.7m HS:0.1m/s VS:0.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.0V delay:34ms bitrate:23.0Mbps Height:354.0m Distance:352.7m HS:0.1m/s VS:0.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.0V delay:35ms bitrate:23.0Mbps Height:354.0m Distance:352.7m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.0V delay:27ms bitrate:22.0Mbps Height:354.0m Distance:352.7m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.0V delay:28ms bitrate:22.0Mbps Height:354.0m Distance:352.7m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.0V delay:25ms bitrate:22.1Mbps Height:354.0m Distance:352.7m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.3V delay:32ms bitrate:21.9Mbps Height:354.0m Distance:352.7m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.3V delay:28ms bitrate:21.9Mbps Height:354.0m Distance:352.8m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.3V delay:29ms bitrate:21.4Mbps Height:354.0m Distance:352.8m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.3V delay:31ms bitrate:21.4Mbps Height:354.0m Distance:352.8m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.3V delay:29ms bitrate:21.9Mbps Height:354.0m Distance:352.8m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.3V delay:30ms bitrate:21.7Mbps Height:353.9m Distance:352.8m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.3V delay:28ms bitrate:21.7Mbps Height:353.9m Distance:352.8m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:29ms bitrate:21.9Mbps Height:353.9m Distance:352.8m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:31ms bitrate:21.9Mbps Height:353.9m Distance:352.9m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.3m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:29ms bitrate:22.4Mbps Height:353.8m Distance:352.9m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.3m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:33ms bitrate:22.4Mbps Height:353.8m Distance:352.9m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.3m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:33ms bitrate:22.7Mbps Height:353.8m Distance:352.9m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.3m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:34ms bitrate:22.7Mbps Height:353.8m Distance:352.9m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.3m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:39ms bitrate:22.9Mbps Height:353.9m Distance:352.9m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.3m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:40ms bitrate:22.5Mbps Height:353.9m Distance:352.9m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.3m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:41ms bitrate:22.5Mbps Height:353.9m Distance:352.9m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.3m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:36ms bitrate:21.9Mbps Height:353.9m Distance:352.9m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.3m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:34ms bitrate:21.9Mbps Height:353.9m Distance:352.9m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.3m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:25ms bitrate:22.2Mbps Height:353.9m Distance:352.9m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.3m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.3V delay:30ms bitrate:22.1Mbps Height:353.9m Distance:352.9m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.3m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.3V delay:31ms bitrate:22.1Mbps Height:353.9m Distance:352.9m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.3m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.3V delay:32ms bitrate:21.6Mbps Height:353.9m Distance:352.9m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.3V delay:27ms bitrate:21.6Mbps Height:353.9m Distance:352.9m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.3V delay:28ms bitrate:22.4Mbps Height:354.0m Distance:352.9m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.3V delay:30ms bitrate:22.7Mbps Height:354.1m Distance:353.0m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.3V delay:28ms bitrate:22.7Mbps Height:354.1m Distance:353.0m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.4V delay:25ms bitrate:22.6Mbps Height:354.1m Distance:353.0m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.4V delay:24ms bitrate:23.1Mbps Height:354.1m Distance:353.0m HS:0.1m/s VS:0.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.4V delay:25ms bitrate:23.1Mbps Height:354.1m Distance:353.0m HS:0.1m/s VS:0.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.4V delay:26ms bitrate:22.5Mbps Height:354.1m Distance:353.0m HS:0.1m/s VS:0.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.4V delay:28ms bitrate:22.5Mbps Height:354.1m Distance:353.0m HS:0.1m/s VS:0.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.4V delay:25ms bitrate:22.6Mbps Height:354.1m Distance:353.1m HS:0.1m/s VS:0.5m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.4V delay:27ms bitrate:22.6Mbps Height:353.8m Distance:353.1m HS:0.1m/s VS:1.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:35ms bitrate:23.3Mbps Height:353.5m Distance:353.1m HS:0.1m/s VS:1.5m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:26ms bitrate:22.6Mbps Height:353.5m Distance:353.1m HS:0.1m/s VS:1.5m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:27ms bitrate:22.6Mbps Height:353.2m Distance:353.1m HS:0.1m/s VS:1.6m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:29ms bitrate:21.4Mbps Height:352.9m Distance:353.0m HS:0.1m/s VS:1.7m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:40ms bitrate:21.4Mbps Height:352.5m Distance:353.0m HS:0.1m/s VS:1.7m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:25ms bitrate:22.7Mbps Height:352.5m Distance:353.0m HS:0.1m/s VS:1.7m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.4V delay:26ms bitrate:23.7Mbps Height:352.2m Distance:353.0m HS:0.1m/s VS:1.7m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.4V delay:27ms bitrate:23.7Mbps Height:351.8m Distance:353.0m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.7m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.4V delay:29ms bitrate:25.7Mbps Height:351.4m Distance:353.0m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.8m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.4V delay:40ms bitrate:25.7Mbps Height:351.4m Distance:353.0m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.8m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.4V delay:41ms bitrate:26.4Mbps Height:351.0m Distance:353.0m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.8m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.4V delay:36ms bitrate:26.4Mbps Height:350.7m Distance:353.0m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.8m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.4V delay:37ms bitrate:26.4Mbps Height:350.3m Distance:353.0m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.8m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.5V delay:28ms bitrate:25.4Mbps Height:350.3m Distance:353.0m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.8m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.5V delay:37ms bitrate:25.3Mbps Height:349.9m Distance:353.0m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.5m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.5V delay:24ms bitrate:25.3Mbps Height:349.6m Distance:353.1m HS:0.1m/s VS:1.4m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.5V delay:26ms bitrate:24.6Mbps Height:349.3m Distance:353.1m HS:0.1m/s VS:1.4m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.5V delay:24ms bitrate:24.6Mbps Height:349.3m Distance:353.1m HS:0.1m/s VS:1.4m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.5V delay:25ms bitrate:24.9Mbps Height:349.0m Distance:353.1m HS:0.1m/s VS:1.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.5V delay:30ms bitrate:24.9Mbps Height:348.7m Distance:353.1m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.8V delay:41ms bitrate:24.0Mbps Height:348.5m Distance:353.1m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.8V delay:32ms bitrate:23.5Mbps Height:348.5m Distance:353.1m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.8V delay:27ms bitrate:23.5Mbps Height:348.2m Distance:353.1m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.8V delay:45ms bitrate:23.1Mbps Height:348.0m Distance:353.1m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.8V delay:36ms bitrate:23.1Mbps Height:347.8m Distance:353.0m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.8V delay:38ms bitrate:21.7Mbps Height:347.8m Distance:353.0m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:42ms bitrate:22.2Mbps Height:347.7m Distance:353.0m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.5m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:33ms bitrate:22.2Mbps Height:347.6m Distance:353.0m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:35ms bitrate:21.3Mbps Height:347.5m Distance:353.1m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:36ms bitrate:21.3Mbps Height:347.5m Distance:353.1m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:28ms bitrate:22.7Mbps Height:347.5m Distance:353.1m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:32ms bitrate:24.1Mbps Height:347.5m Distance:353.1m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:40ms bitrate:24.1Mbps Height:347.5m Distance:353.1m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:45ms bitrate:23.9Mbps Height:347.5m Distance:353.1m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:36ms bitrate:23.9Mbps Height:347.5m Distance:353.1m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:37ms bitrate:23.1Mbps Height:347.5m Distance:353.0m HS:0.1m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:39ms bitrate:23.3Mbps Height:347.5m Distance:353.0m HS:0.1m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:33ms bitrate:23.3Mbps Height:347.5m Distance:353.0m HS:0.1m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:35ms bitrate:22.8Mbps Height:347.5m Distance:353.0m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:26ms bitrate:22.8Mbps Height:347.5m Distance:353.0m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.8V delay:24ms bitrate:23.2Mbps Height:347.5m Distance:353.0m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.8V delay:25ms bitrate:24.6Mbps Height:347.5m Distance:353.0m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.8V delay:27ms bitrate:24.6Mbps Height:347.5m Distance:353.0m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.8V delay:31ms bitrate:25.3Mbps Height:347.5m Distance:353.0m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.8V delay:33ms bitrate:25.3Mbps Height:347.5m Distance:353.0m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.8V delay:34ms bitrate:25.1Mbps Height:347.5m Distance:353.0m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.9V delay:25ms bitrate:25.2Mbps Height:347.5m Distance:352.9m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.9V delay:27ms bitrate:25.2Mbps Height:347.5m Distance:353.0m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.9V delay:29ms bitrate:25.3Mbps Height:347.5m Distance:353.0m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.9V delay:29ms bitrate:25.4Mbps Height:347.5m Distance:353.0m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.9V delay:24ms bitrate:25.4Mbps Height:347.5m Distance:353.0m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.9V delay:25ms bitrate:26.1Mbps Height:347.5m Distance:353.0m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.9V delay:33ms bitrate:26.1Mbps Height:347.5m Distance:353.0m HS:0.3m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:26ms bitrate:26.7Mbps Height:347.5m Distance:353.1m HS:0.5m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:29ms bitrate:28.0Mbps Height:347.5m Distance:353.1m HS:0.5m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:30ms bitrate:28.0Mbps Height:347.4m Distance:353.3m HS:0.9m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:35ms bitrate:30.9Mbps Height:347.4m Distance:353.5m HS:1.4m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:36ms bitrate:30.9Mbps Height:347.4m Distance:353.5m HS:1.4m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:38ms bitrate:30.5Mbps Height:347.4m Distance:353.8m HS:1.7m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.8V delay:35ms bitrate:28.5Mbps Height:347.4m Distance:354.2m HS:2.1m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.8V delay:23ms bitrate:28.5Mbps Height:347.4m Distance:354.7m HS:2.1m/s VS:0.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.8V delay:32ms bitrate:27.4Mbps Height:347.4m Distance:354.7m HS:2.1m/s VS:0.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.8V delay:26ms bitrate:27.4Mbps Height:347.5m Distance:355.0m HS:1.5m/s VS:0.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.8V delay:24ms bitrate:26.1Mbps Height:347.5m Distance:355.3m HS:0.7m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.8V delay:25ms bitrate:26.0Mbps Height:347.5m Distance:355.5m HS:0.3m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.8V delay:26ms bitrate:26.0Mbps Height:347.5m Distance:355.5m HS:0.3m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.0V delay:28ms bitrate:25.0Mbps Height:347.5m Distance:355.5m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.0V delay:35ms bitrate:25.0Mbps Height:347.5m Distance:355.6m HS:0.1m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.0V delay:33ms bitrate:24.4Mbps Height:347.5m Distance:355.5m HS:0.2m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.0V delay:38ms bitrate:23.7Mbps Height:347.5m Distance:355.5m HS:0.2m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.0V delay:36ms bitrate:23.7Mbps Height:347.5m Distance:355.5m HS:0.3m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.0V delay:37ms bitrate:24.0Mbps Height:347.5m Distance:355.4m HS:0.4m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.0V delay:28ms bitrate:24.0Mbps Height:347.5m Distance:355.4m HS:0.1m/s VS:0.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.7V delay:40ms bitrate:25.6Mbps Height:347.5m Distance:355.4m HS:0.1m/s VS:0.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.7V delay:31ms bitrate:27.0Mbps Height:347.5m Distance:355.4m HS:0.8m/s VS:0.3m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.7V delay:36ms bitrate:27.0Mbps Height:347.5m Distance:355.7m HS:2.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.7V delay:37ms bitrate:26.3Mbps Height:347.4m Distance:356.2m HS:2.8m/s VS:0.7m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.7V delay:31ms bitrate:26.3Mbps Height:347.4m Distance:356.2m HS:2.8m/s VS:0.7m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.7V delay:27ms bitrate:27.0Mbps Height:347.2m Distance:356.8m HS:3.9m/s VS:1.3m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.5V delay:31ms bitrate:29.2Mbps Height:346.9m Distance:357.6m HS:4.9m/s VS:1.8m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.5V delay:32ms bitrate:29.2Mbps Height:346.5m Distance:358.6m HS:5.9m/s VS:2.4m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.5V delay:27ms bitrate:30.3Mbps Height:346.0m Distance:359.8m HS:6.9m/s VS:3.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.5V delay:35ms bitrate:30.3Mbps Height:346.0m Distance:359.8m HS:6.9m/s VS:3.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.5V delay:37ms bitrate:30.3Mbps Height:345.3m Distance:361.2m HS:8.0m/s VS:3.8m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.5V delay:24ms bitrate:30.2Mbps Height:344.6m Distance:362.8m HS:9.7m/s VS:3.8m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.5V delay:25ms bitrate:30.2Mbps Height:343.8m Distance:364.7m HS:11.3m/s VS:3.9m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:28ms bitrate:32.2Mbps Height:343.8m Distance:364.7m HS:11.3m/s VS:3.9m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:35ms bitrate:32.2Mbps Height:343.0m Distance:366.8m HS:12.9m/s VS:4.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:26ms bitrate:29.9Mbps Height:342.0m Distance:369.1m HS:14.4m/s VS:4.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:28ms bitrate:29.0Mbps Height:341.2m Distance:371.7m HS:15.9m/s VS:4.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:25ms bitrate:29.0Mbps Height:341.2m Distance:371.7m HS:15.9m/s VS:4.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:36ms bitrate:29.1Mbps Height:340.2m Distance:374.4m HS:17.0m/s VS:4.4m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:25ms bitrate:29.1Mbps Height:339.3m Distance:377.4m HS:18.0m/s VS:4.7m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:26ms bitrate:29.0Mbps Height:338.3m Distance:380.4m HS:18.8m/s VS:5.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:37ms bitrate:29.9Mbps Height:338.3m Distance:380.4m HS:18.8m/s VS:5.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:35ms bitrate:29.9Mbps Height:337.3m Distance:383.7m HS:19.8m/s VS:5.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:23ms bitrate:31.7Mbps Height:336.3m Distance:386.9m HS:20.6m/s VS:5.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:41ms bitrate:31.7Mbps Height:335.3m Distance:390.2m HS:21.3m/s VS:5.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:36ms bitrate:28.7Mbps Height:335.3m Distance:390.2m HS:21.3m/s VS:5.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.6V delay:37ms bitrate:28.3Mbps Height:334.2m Distance:393.4m HS:21.9m/s VS:5.3m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.6V delay:25ms bitrate:28.3Mbps Height:333.1m Distance:396.7m HS:23.0m/s VS:5.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.6V delay:33ms bitrate:25.9Mbps Height:332.2m Distance:400.1m HS:24.0m/s VS:4.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.6V delay:24ms bitrate:25.9Mbps Height:332.2m Distance:400.1m HS:24.0m/s VS:4.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.6V delay:33ms bitrate:27.5Mbps Height:331.4m Distance:403.5m HS:24.7m/s VS:3.3m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.6V delay:24ms bitrate:23.4Mbps Height:330.8m Distance:406.8m HS:25.1m/s VS:2.6m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.6V delay:25ms bitrate:23.4Mbps Height:330.3m Distance:410.2m HS:25.5m/s VS:1.9m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.4V delay:27ms bitrate:21.4Mbps Height:330.3m Distance:410.2m HS:25.5m/s VS:1.9m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.4V delay:34ms bitrate:21.4Mbps Height:330.0m Distance:413.5m HS:25.5m/s VS:1.7m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.4V delay:25ms bitrate:20.7Mbps Height:329.6m Distance:416.8m HS:25.4m/s VS:1.8m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.4V delay:37ms bitrate:20.9Mbps Height:329.2m Distance:420.1m HS:25.4m/s VS:1.8m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.4V delay:25ms bitrate:20.9Mbps Height:329.2m Distance:420.1m HS:25.4m/s VS:1.8m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.4V delay:26ms bitrate:20.7Mbps Height:328.9m Distance:423.4m HS:25.4m/s VS:1.7m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.4V delay:28ms bitrate:20.7Mbps Height:328.6m Distance:426.6m HS:25.2m/s VS:1.7m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:29ms bitrate:21.1Mbps Height:328.3m Distance:429.7m HS:24.9m/s VS:1.7m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:30ms bitrate:24.8Mbps Height:328.3m Distance:429.7m HS:24.9m/s VS:1.7m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:25ms bitrate:24.8Mbps Height:327.9m Distance:433.0m HS:24.5m/s VS:1.7m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:33ms bitrate:29.6Mbps Height:327.6m Distance:436.3m HS:24.1m/s VS:1.7m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:29ms bitrate:30.8Mbps Height:327.3m Distance:439.7m HS:23.4m/s VS:1.6m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:36ms bitrate:30.8Mbps Height:327.3m Distance:439.7m HS:23.4m/s VS:1.6m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.6V delay:37ms bitrate:29.7Mbps Height:326.9m Distance:443.2m HS:22.5m/s VS:1.5m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.6V delay:42ms bitrate:29.7Mbps Height:326.6m Distance:446.6m HS:21.5m/s VS:1.5m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.6V delay:33ms bitrate:27.4Mbps Height:326.3m Distance:450.1m HS:20.6m/s VS:1.6m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.6V delay:34ms bitrate:27.4Mbps Height:326.3m Distance:450.1m HS:20.6m/s VS:1.6m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.6V delay:26ms bitrate:25.6Mbps Height:326.0m Distance:453.7m HS:19.4m/s VS:1.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.6V delay:30ms bitrate:23.1Mbps Height:325.9m Distance:457.2m HS:18.3m/s VS:0.3m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.6V delay:25ms bitrate:23.1Mbps Height:325.8m Distance:460.9m HS:17.7m/s VS:0.3m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.5V delay:30ms bitrate:22.0Mbps Height:325.8m Distance:460.9m HS:17.7m/s VS:0.3m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.5V delay:34ms bitrate:22.0Mbps Height:325.7m Distance:464.4m HS:17.1m/s VS:0.5m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.5V delay:25ms bitrate:22.1Mbps Height:325.5m Distance:467.9m HS:16.7m/s VS:0.8m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.5V delay:24ms bitrate:22.0Mbps Height:325.3m Distance:471.2m HS:16.3m/s VS:1.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.5V delay:38ms bitrate:22.0Mbps Height:325.3m Distance:471.2m HS:16.3m/s VS:1.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.5V delay:23ms bitrate:19.1Mbps Height:325.1m Distance:474.4m HS:16.1m/s VS:1.3m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.5V delay:24ms bitrate:19.1Mbps Height:324.8m Distance:477.7m HS:15.7m/s VS:1.4m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.9V delay:32ms bitrate:17.2Mbps Height:324.5m Distance:480.7m HS:15.3m/s VS:1.5m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.9V delay:23ms bitrate:16.7Mbps Height:324.5m Distance:480.7m HS:15.3m/s VS:1.5m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.9V delay:35ms bitrate:16.7Mbps Height:324.2m Distance:483.7m HS:14.9m/s VS:1.7m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.9V delay:26ms bitrate:16.7Mbps Height:323.9m Distance:486.4m HS:14.6m/s VS:1.7m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.9V delay:31ms bitrate:16.7Mbps Height:323.6m Distance:489.0m HS:14.1m/s VS:1.8m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.9V delay:29ms bitrate:17.3Mbps Height:323.6m Distance:489.0m HS:14.1m/s VS:1.8m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:30ms bitrate:18.8Mbps Height:323.3m Distance:491.1m HS:13.7m/s VS:2.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:25ms bitrate:18.8Mbps Height:322.9m Distance:492.9m HS:13.3m/s VS:2.3m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:40ms bitrate:21.6Mbps Height:322.4m Distance:494.4m HS:13.2m/s VS:2.6m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:27ms bitrate:21.6Mbps Height:322.4m Distance:494.4m HS:13.2m/s VS:2.6m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:22ms bitrate:26.5Mbps Height:321.9m Distance:495.8m HS:13.3m/s VS:3.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:27ms bitrate:32.4Mbps Height:321.2m Distance:496.5m HS:13.6m/s VS:3.7m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:31ms bitrate:32.4Mbps Height:320.4m Distance:496.8m HS:14.0m/s VS:4.3m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:26ms bitrate:32.8Mbps Height:320.4m Distance:496.8m HS:14.0m/s VS:4.3m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:37ms bitrate:32.8Mbps Height:319.5m Distance:496.6m HS:14.5m/s VS:4.8m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:39ms bitrate:29.8Mbps Height:318.5m Distance:495.9m HS:15.2m/s VS:5.4m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:30ms bitrate:25.5Mbps Height:317.4m Distance:494.6m HS:16.2m/s VS:5.8m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:21ms bitrate:25.5Mbps Height:317.4m Distance:494.6m HS:16.2m/s VS:5.8m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:23ms bitrate:25.7Mbps Height:316.3m Distance:492.8m HS:17.2m/s VS:6.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.7V delay:24ms bitrate:25.3Mbps Height:315.1m Distance:490.5m HS:18.3m/s VS:6.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.7V delay:28ms bitrate:25.3Mbps Height:313.8m Distance:487.7m HS:19.3m/s VS:6.4m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.7V delay:23ms bitrate:29.0Mbps Height:313.8m Distance:487.7m HS:19.3m/s VS:6.4m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.7V delay:41ms bitrate:29.0Mbps Height:312.6m Distance:484.5m HS:20.4m/s VS:6.3m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.7V delay:32ms bitrate:32.4Mbps Height:311.3m Distance:480.7m HS:21.7m/s VS:6.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.7V delay:34ms bitrate:31.2Mbps Height:310.1m Distance:476.8m HS:23.1m/s VS:6.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.7V delay:25ms bitrate:31.2Mbps Height:310.1m Distance:476.8m HS:23.1m/s VS:6.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.7V delay:26ms bitrate:32.0Mbps Height:308.8m Distance:472.1m HS:24.3m/s VS:6.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.7V delay:24ms bitrate:32.0Mbps Height:307.6m Distance:467.4m HS:25.3m/s VS:6.5m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.7V delay:27ms bitrate:33.8Mbps Height:306.3m Distance:462.1m HS:26.0m/s VS:6.9m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.7V delay:34ms bitrate:34.0Mbps Height:306.3m Distance:462.1m HS:26.0m/s VS:6.9m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.7V delay:25ms bitrate:34.0Mbps Height:304.8m Distance:456.8m HS:26.8m/s VS:7.4m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.7V delay:37ms bitrate:31.8Mbps Height:303.3m Distance:451.5m HS:27.4m/s VS:8.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.7V delay:28ms bitrate:31.8Mbps Height:301.6m Distance:446.0m HS:27.7m/s VS:9.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.2V delay:22ms bitrate:27.8Mbps Height:301.6m Distance:446.0m HS:27.7m/s VS:9.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.2V delay:34ms bitrate:26.8Mbps Height:299.7m Distance:440.5m HS:27.9m/s VS:10.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.2V delay:35ms bitrate:26.8Mbps Height:297.6m Distance:434.9m HS:28.1m/s VS:11.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.2V delay:26ms bitrate:25.0Mbps Height:295.2m Distance:429.1m HS:28.5m/s VS:12.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.2V delay:27ms bitrate:25.0Mbps Height:295.2m Distance:429.1m HS:28.5m/s VS:12.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.2V delay:29ms bitrate:26.3Mbps Height:292.8m Distance:423.5m HS:28.8m/s VS:13.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.7V delay:30ms bitrate:28.4Mbps Height:290.1m Distance:417.7m HS:29.2m/s VS:13.7m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.7V delay:25ms bitrate:28.4Mbps Height:287.3m Distance:411.9m HS:29.5m/s VS:14.4m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.7V delay:23ms bitrate:29.5Mbps Height:287.3m Distance:411.9m HS:29.5m/s VS:14.4m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.7V delay:24ms bitrate:29.5Mbps Height:284.3m Distance:405.8m HS:29.9m/s VS:14.9m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.7V delay:29ms bitrate:33.6Mbps Height:281.4m Distance:399.8m HS:30.5m/s VS:15.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.7V delay:40ms bitrate:35.3Mbps Height:278.5m Distance:394.0m HS:31.4m/s VS:14.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.7V delay:33ms bitrate:35.3Mbps Height:275.7m Distance:387.6m HS:32.2m/s VS:13.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.6V delay:26ms bitrate:36.4Mbps Height:275.7m Distance:387.6m HS:32.2m/s VS:13.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.6V delay:35ms bitrate:37.2Mbps Height:273.0m Distance:381.0m HS:32.9m/s VS:12.3m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.6V delay:25ms bitrate:37.2Mbps Height:270.6m Distance:374.3m HS:33.5m/s VS:11.4m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.6V delay:30ms bitrate:36.2Mbps Height:268.4m Distance:367.9m HS:34.0m/s VS:10.6m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.6V delay:24ms bitrate:36.2Mbps Height:268.4m Distance:367.9m HS:34.0m/s VS:10.6m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.6V delay:36ms bitrate:38.4Mbps Height:266.4m Distance:361.1m HS:34.2m/s VS:10.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.6V delay:27ms bitrate:38.4Mbps Height:264.4m Distance:354.3m HS:34.0m/s VS:9.9m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:25ms bitrate:35.6Mbps Height:262.4m Distance:347.6m HS:33.8m/s VS:9.8m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:26ms bitrate:35.6Mbps Height:262.4m Distance:347.6m HS:33.8m/s VS:9.8m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:41ms bitrate:35.6Mbps Height:260.6m Distance:340.9m HS:33.6m/s VS:9.3m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:35ms bitrate:35.2Mbps Height:258.7m Distance:334.3m HS:33.6m/s VS:8.9m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:24ms bitrate:35.2Mbps Height:257.0m Distance:327.7m HS:33.3m/s VS:8.4m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:28ms bitrate:34.4Mbps Height:257.0m Distance:327.7m HS:33.3m/s VS:8.4m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.6V delay:29ms bitrate:35.8Mbps Height:255.4m Distance:321.2m HS:33.1m/s VS:7.8m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.6V delay:28ms bitrate:35.8Mbps Height:253.9m Distance:314.7m HS:33.0m/s VS:6.9m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.6V delay:25ms bitrate:35.3Mbps Height:252.6m Distance:308.3m HS:32.7m/s VS:5.9m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.6V delay:30ms bitrate:35.3Mbps Height:252.6m Distance:308.3m HS:32.7m/s VS:5.9m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.6V delay:35ms bitrate:38.1Mbps Height:251.5m Distance:302.0m HS:32.3m/s VS:5.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.6V delay:26ms bitrate:39.7Mbps Height:250.5m Distance:295.7m HS:32.0m/s VS:4.3m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.6V delay:27ms bitrate:39.7Mbps Height:249.7m Distance:289.3m HS:31.8m/s VS:4.3m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:29ms bitrate:42.4Mbps Height:249.7m Distance:289.3m HS:31.8m/s VS:4.3m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:28ms bitrate:42.4Mbps Height:248.8m Distance:283.4m HS:31.5m/s VS:4.9m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:25ms bitrate:46.1Mbps Height:247.8m Distance:277.4m HS:31.1m/s VS:5.9m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:33ms bitrate:47.4Mbps Height:246.6m Distance:271.4m HS:30.8m/s VS:6.8m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:24ms bitrate:47.4Mbps Height:246.6m Distance:271.4m HS:30.8m/s VS:6.8m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:29ms bitrate:44.3Mbps Height:245.2m Distance:265.6m HS:30.7m/s VS:7.3m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:30ms bitrate:44.3Mbps Height:243.6m Distance:259.6m HS:30.7m/s VS:7.9m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:24ms bitrate:45.1Mbps Height:242.1m Distance:253.9m HS:30.6m/s VS:8.3m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:33ms bitrate:47.8Mbps Height:242.1m Distance:253.9m HS:30.6m/s VS:8.3m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:27ms bitrate:47.8Mbps Height:240.4m Distance:247.9m HS:30.6m/s VS:8.6m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:28ms bitrate:49.1Mbps Height:238.6m Distance:241.9m HS:30.5m/s VS:8.8m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:26ms bitrate:49.1Mbps Height:236.8m Distance:236.1m HS:30.6m/s VS:8.7m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:31ms bitrate:49.4Mbps Height:236.8m Distance:236.1m HS:30.6m/s VS:8.7m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.8V delay:26ms bitrate:49.5Mbps Height:235.1m Distance:230.5m HS:30.7m/s VS:8.5m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.8V delay:27ms bitrate:49.5Mbps Height:233.4m Distance:225.0m HS:30.7m/s VS:8.4m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.8V delay:30ms bitrate:49.8Mbps Height:231.7m Distance:219.3m HS:30.7m/s VS:8.4m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.8V delay:31ms bitrate:50.1Mbps Height:230.0m Distance:213.3m HS:30.7m/s VS:8.5m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.8V delay:27ms bitrate:49.3Mbps Height:228.3m Distance:207.9m HS:30.6m/s VS:8.5m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.8V delay:27ms bitrate:49.3Mbps Height:226.6m Distance:202.3m HS:30.4m/s VS:8.5m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.7V delay:31ms bitrate:49.7Mbps Height:226.6m Distance:202.3m HS:30.4m/s VS:8.5m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.7V delay:30ms bitrate:49.7Mbps Height:224.9m Distance:196.7m HS:30.4m/s VS:8.5m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.7V delay:31ms bitrate:47.7Mbps Height:223.2m Distance:191.2m HS:30.2m/s VS:8.6m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.7V delay:25ms bitrate:48.8Mbps Height:221.4m Distance:185.7m HS:30.2m/s VS:8.7m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.7V delay:27ms bitrate:48.8Mbps Height:221.4m Distance:185.7m HS:30.2m/s VS:8.7m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.7V delay:25ms bitrate:49.4Mbps Height:219.7m Distance:180.4m HS:30.1m/s VS:8.7m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.7V delay:26ms bitrate:49.4Mbps Height:218.0m Distance:175.1m HS:30.0m/s VS:8.8m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:24ms bitrate:49.6Mbps Height:216.2m Distance:169.8m HS:29.8m/s VS:9.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:25ms bitrate:50.0Mbps Height:216.2m Distance:169.8m HS:29.8m/s VS:9.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:27ms bitrate:50.0Mbps Height:214.3m Distance:164.5m HS:29.8m/s VS:9.3m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:25ms bitrate:50.1Mbps Height:212.4m Distance:159.4m HS:29.7m/s VS:9.6m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:26ms bitrate:50.1Mbps Height:210.5m Distance:154.6m HS:29.5m/s VS:9.9m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:29ms bitrate:50.3Mbps Height:208.5m Distance:149.7m HS:29.5m/s VS:10.3m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.7V delay:32ms bitrate:50.2Mbps Height:208.5m Distance:149.7m HS:29.5m/s VS:10.3m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.7V delay:26ms bitrate:50.2Mbps Height:206.4m Distance:144.6m HS:29.3m/s VS:10.7m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.7V delay:24ms bitrate:50.2Mbps Height:204.2m Distance:140.1m HS:29.1m/s VS:11.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.7V delay:26ms bitrate:50.2Mbps Height:204.2m Distance:140.1m HS:29.1m/s VS:11.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.7V delay:27ms bitrate:50.3Mbps Height:202.0m Distance:135.4m HS:28.9m/s VS:11.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.7V delay:28ms bitrate:50.5Mbps Height:199.7m Distance:130.8m HS:28.7m/s VS:11.3m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.7V delay:26ms bitrate:50.5Mbps Height:197.5m Distance:126.2m HS:28.4m/s VS:11.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.6V delay:27ms bitrate:50.5Mbps Height:197.5m Distance:126.2m HS:28.4m/s VS:11.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.6V delay:26ms bitrate:50.5Mbps Height:195.2m Distance:121.8m HS:28.0m/s VS:11.3m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.6V delay:27ms bitrate:50.5Mbps Height:192.9m Distance:117.1m HS:27.4m/s VS:11.4m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.6V delay:28ms bitrate:50.5Mbps Height:190.6m Distance:112.5m HS:26.9m/s VS:11.6m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.6V delay:30ms bitrate:50.5Mbps Height:190.6m Distance:112.5m HS:26.9m/s VS:11.6m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.6V delay:24ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:188.2m Distance:108.0m HS:26.5m/s VS:11.6m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.6V delay:25ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:185.9m Distance:103.5m HS:26.1m/s VS:11.3m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:9.0V delay:27ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:183.7m Distance:99.0m HS:25.7m/s VS:10.6m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:9.0V delay:28ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:183.7m Distance:99.0m HS:25.7m/s VS:10.6m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:9.0V delay:24ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:181.6m Distance:94.4m HS:25.1m/s VS:9.4m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:9.0V delay:31ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:179.8m Distance:89.8m HS:24.4m/s VS:8.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:9.0V delay:32ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:178.3m Distance:85.3m HS:23.8m/s VS:6.7m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:9.0V delay:27ms bitrate:50.5Mbps Height:178.3m Distance:85.3m HS:23.8m/s VS:6.7m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:28ms bitrate:50.3Mbps Height:177.1m Distance:81.1m HS:23.2m/s VS:5.6m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:29ms bitrate:50.3Mbps Height:176.0m Distance:76.9m HS:22.6m/s VS:4.6m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:31ms bitrate:50.3Mbps Height:175.1m Distance:72.4m HS:22.1m/s VS:3.8m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:32ms bitrate:50.3Mbps Height:175.1m Distance:72.4m HS:22.1m/s VS:3.8m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:30ms bitrate:50.3Mbps Height:174.3m Distance:68.1m HS:21.5m/s VS:3.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:25ms bitrate:50.4Mbps Height:173.8m Distance:64.0m HS:21.0m/s VS:2.5m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:26ms bitrate:50.4Mbps Height:173.2m Distance:60.0m HS:20.5m/s VS:2.3m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:27ms bitrate:50.3Mbps Height:173.2m Distance:60.0m HS:20.5m/s VS:2.3m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:25ms bitrate:50.3Mbps Height:172.7m Distance:56.0m HS:20.1m/s VS:2.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:26ms bitrate:50.5Mbps Height:172.2m Distance:52.0m HS:19.6m/s VS:2.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:24ms bitrate:50.5Mbps Height:171.8m Distance:48.1m HS:19.1m/s VS:2.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:26ms bitrate:50.5Mbps Height:171.8m Distance:48.1m HS:19.1m/s VS:2.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:27ms bitrate:50.4Mbps Height:171.3m Distance:44.4m HS:18.7m/s VS:2.3m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:29ms bitrate:50.4Mbps Height:170.9m Distance:40.7m HS:18.3m/s VS:2.4m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.6V delay:30ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:170.4m Distance:37.2m HS:18.0m/s VS:2.3m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.6V delay:24ms bitrate:50.4Mbps Height:170.4m Distance:37.2m HS:18.0m/s VS:2.3m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.6V delay:33ms bitrate:50.4Mbps Height:169.9m Distance:33.3m HS:17.4m/s VS:2.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.6V delay:44ms bitrate:49.3Mbps Height:169.4m Distance:29.8m HS:16.8m/s VS:2.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.6V delay:39ms bitrate:37.7Mbps Height:169.0m Distance:26.7m HS:16.2m/s VS:2.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.6V delay:33ms bitrate:37.7Mbps Height:169.0m Distance:26.7m HS:16.2m/s VS:2.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:24ms bitrate:33.6Mbps Height:168.6m Distance:23.5m HS:15.5m/s VS:1.9m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:36ms bitrate:33.6Mbps Height:168.3m Distance:20.5m HS:14.8m/s VS:1.5m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:37ms bitrate:32.8Mbps Height:168.0m Distance:17.8m HS:13.9m/s VS:1.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:28ms bitrate:32.8Mbps Height:168.0m Distance:17.8m HS:13.9m/s VS:1.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:30ms bitrate:31.2Mbps Height:167.8m Distance:15.1m HS:13.2m/s VS:0.9m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:24ms bitrate:31.2Mbps Height:167.6m Distance:12.9m HS:12.2m/s VS:0.8m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:32ms bitrate:31.2Mbps Height:167.5m Distance:11.2m HS:11.3m/s VS:0.6m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:27ms bitrate:32.7Mbps Height:167.5m Distance:11.2m HS:11.3m/s VS:0.6m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:25ms bitrate:32.7Mbps Height:167.4m Distance:10.1m HS:10.2m/s VS:0.4m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:36ms bitrate:36.3Mbps Height:167.4m Distance:9.6m HS:9.1m/s VS:0.3m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:34ms bitrate:39.3Mbps Height:167.2m Distance:9.9m HS:8.0m/s VS:0.4m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:25ms bitrate:39.3Mbps Height:167.2m Distance:9.9m HS:8.0m/s VS:0.4m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:23ms bitrate:41.4Mbps Height:167.1m Distance:10.6m HS:7.0m/s VS:0.5m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:25ms bitrate:41.4Mbps Height:167.0m Distance:11.7m HS:6.4m/s VS:0.7m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:29ms bitrate:37.4Mbps Height:166.9m Distance:12.9m HS:6.2m/s VS:0.9m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:27ms bitrate:37.7Mbps Height:166.9m Distance:12.9m HS:6.2m/s VS:0.9m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:32ms bitrate:37.7Mbps Height:166.8m Distance:14.2m HS:6.4m/s VS:1.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:34ms bitrate:37.6Mbps Height:166.6m Distance:15.6m HS:7.1m/s VS:1.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:35ms bitrate:37.6Mbps Height:166.4m Distance:17.0m HS:8.1m/s VS:1.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:36ms bitrate:35.7Mbps Height:166.4m Distance:17.0m HS:8.1m/s VS:1.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.2V delay:37ms bitrate:30.1Mbps Height:166.2m Distance:18.5m HS:9.1m/s VS:1.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.2V delay:29ms bitrate:30.1Mbps Height:165.9m Distance:20.1m HS:10.0m/s VS:1.5m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.2V delay:30ms bitrate:28.8Mbps Height:165.6m Distance:21.8m HS:10.9m/s VS:1.8m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.2V delay:39ms bitrate:30.8Mbps Height:165.3m Distance:23.6m HS:11.8m/s VS:2.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.2V delay:29ms bitrate:30.8Mbps Height:165.3m Distance:23.6m HS:11.8m/s VS:2.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.2V delay:34ms bitrate:29.3Mbps Height:164.8m Distance:25.5m HS:12.7m/s VS:2.4m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.2V delay:28ms bitrate:29.3Mbps Height:164.4m Distance:27.6m HS:13.5m/s VS:2.7m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:33ms bitrate:30.4Mbps Height:164.4m Distance:27.6m HS:13.5m/s VS:2.7m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:24ms bitrate:30.4Mbps Height:163.9m Distance:29.7m HS:14.2m/s VS:2.9m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:22ms bitrate:28.8Mbps Height:163.3m Distance:32.0m HS:14.9m/s VS:3.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:27ms bitrate:33.0Mbps Height:162.6m Distance:34.5m HS:15.4m/s VS:3.6m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:35ms bitrate:33.0Mbps Height:162.6m Distance:34.5m HS:15.4m/s VS:3.6m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:36ms bitrate:33.9Mbps Height:161.8m Distance:36.7m HS:15.7m/s VS:4.3m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.9V delay:31ms bitrate:33.9Mbps Height:160.8m Distance:39.2m HS:16.1m/s VS:5.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.9V delay:24ms bitrate:34.2Mbps Height:159.8m Distance:41.7m HS:16.6m/s VS:5.3m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.9V delay:27ms bitrate:38.7Mbps Height:159.8m Distance:41.7m HS:16.6m/s VS:5.3m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.9V delay:25ms bitrate:38.7Mbps Height:158.7m Distance:44.3m HS:17.0m/s VS:5.4m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.9V delay:26ms bitrate:44.0Mbps Height:157.6m Distance:46.8m HS:17.4m/s VS:5.6m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.9V delay:28ms bitrate:44.0Mbps Height:156.4m Distance:49.1m HS:18.0m/s VS:5.8m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.9V delay:25ms bitrate:47.7Mbps Height:156.4m Distance:49.1m HS:18.0m/s VS:5.8m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:23ms bitrate:49.3Mbps Height:155.3m Distance:51.3m HS:19.0m/s VS:5.9m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:25ms bitrate:49.3Mbps Height:154.1m Distance:53.3m HS:20.1m/s VS:6.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:24ms bitrate:50.0Mbps Height:152.9m Distance:55.1m HS:21.1m/s VS:6.9m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:27ms bitrate:50.2Mbps Height:152.9m Distance:55.1m HS:21.1m/s VS:6.9m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:22ms bitrate:50.2Mbps Height:151.5m Distance:56.7m HS:22.1m/s VS:7.7m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:23ms bitrate:50.4Mbps Height:149.9m Distance:58.1m HS:23.3m/s VS:8.5m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:25ms bitrate:50.4Mbps Height:148.2m Distance:59.4m HS:24.7m/s VS:9.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:26ms bitrate:50.4Mbps Height:148.2m Distance:59.4m HS:24.7m/s VS:9.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:27ms bitrate:50.5Mbps Height:146.3m Distance:60.6m HS:25.9m/s VS:9.3m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:29ms bitrate:50.5Mbps Height:144.5m Distance:61.8m HS:27.0m/s VS:9.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:30ms bitrate:50.5Mbps Height:142.6m Distance:63.1m HS:28.1m/s VS:8.5m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:31ms bitrate:50.5Mbps Height:142.6m Distance:63.1m HS:28.1m/s VS:8.5m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:36ms bitrate:48.9Mbps Height:141.0m Distance:64.4m HS:28.8m/s VS:7.4m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.9V delay:27ms bitrate:40.7Mbps Height:139.6m Distance:65.7m HS:29.1m/s VS:6.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.9V delay:30ms bitrate:40.7Mbps Height:138.4m Distance:67.1m HS:29.3m/s VS:5.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.9V delay:30ms bitrate:42.1Mbps Height:137.4m Distance:68.6m HS:29.4m/s VS:4.4m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.9V delay:34ms bitrate:42.1Mbps Height:137.4m Distance:68.6m HS:29.4m/s VS:4.4m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.9V delay:22ms bitrate:42.8Mbps Height:136.6m Distance:70.1m HS:29.7m/s VS:3.4m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.9V delay:34ms bitrate:39.8Mbps Height:136.0m Distance:71.8m HS:29.8m/s VS:2.6m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.9V delay:35ms bitrate:39.8Mbps Height:135.6m Distance:73.6m HS:29.7m/s VS:1.8m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.9V delay:40ms bitrate:37.0Mbps Height:135.6m Distance:73.6m HS:29.7m/s VS:1.8m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.9V delay:24ms bitrate:37.0Mbps Height:135.4m Distance:75.5m HS:29.6m/s VS:1.0m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.9V delay:32ms bitrate:34.3Mbps Height:135.3m Distance:77.6m HS:29.2m/s VS:0.1m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.9V delay:24ms bitrate:34.5Mbps Height:135.4m Distance:79.7m HS:28.6m/s VS:0.9m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.9V delay:25ms bitrate:34.5Mbps Height:135.4m Distance:79.7m HS:28.6m/s VS:0.9m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.9V delay:28ms bitrate:38.3Mbps Height:135.7m Distance:81.8m HS:27.8m/s VS:1.9m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.9V delay:28ms bitrate:38.3Mbps Height:136.2m Distance:83.7m HS:27.0m/s VS:2.8m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:25ms bitrate:43.6Mbps Height:136.9m Distance:85.7m HS:26.1m/s VS:3.7m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:23ms bitrate:46.2Mbps Height:136.9m Distance:85.7m HS:26.1m/s VS:3.7m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:25ms bitrate:46.2Mbps Height:137.8m Distance:87.5m HS:24.9m/s VS:4.5m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:26ms bitrate:48.4Mbps Height:138.8m Distance:89.2m HS:23.9m/s VS:5.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:24ms bitrate:48.4Mbps Height:139.9m Distance:90.8m HS:22.9m/s VS:5.4m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:29ms bitrate:49.7Mbps Height:139.9m Distance:90.8m HS:22.9m/s VS:5.4m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.9V delay:23ms bitrate:49.1Mbps Height:141.1m Distance:92.4m HS:21.9m/s VS:5.9m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.9V delay:25ms bitrate:49.1Mbps Height:142.4m Distance:93.6m HS:21.0m/s VS:6.4m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.9V delay:26ms bitrate:49.4Mbps Height:143.8m Distance:94.8m HS:20.0m/s VS:6.8m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.9V delay:29ms bitrate:50.1Mbps Height:143.8m Distance:94.8m HS:20.0m/s VS:6.8m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.9V delay:29ms bitrate:50.1Mbps Height:145.2m Distance:95.8m HS:19.1m/s VS:7.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.9V delay:30ms bitrate:50.5Mbps Height:146.6m Distance:96.5m HS:18.2m/s VS:7.1m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.9V delay:29ms bitrate:50.5Mbps Height:148.1m Distance:97.1m HS:17.5m/s VS:6.9m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:26ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:148.1m Distance:97.1m HS:17.5m/s VS:6.9m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:27ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:149.5m Distance:97.5m HS:16.7m/s VS:6.5m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:28ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:150.8m Distance:97.8m HS:16.0m/s VS:6.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:30ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:152.1m Distance:98.0m HS:15.3m/s VS:5.6m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:31ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:152.1m Distance:98.0m HS:15.3m/s VS:5.6m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:33ms bitrate:50.5Mbps Height:153.3m Distance:98.0m HS:14.6m/s VS:5.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:27ms bitrate:50.5Mbps Height:154.4m Distance:97.8m HS:13.9m/s VS:4.8m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.9V delay:30ms bitrate:50.5Mbps Height:155.5m Distance:97.5m HS:13.2m/s VS:4.5m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.9V delay:27ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:155.5m Distance:97.5m HS:13.2m/s VS:4.5m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.9V delay:28ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:156.5m Distance:97.1m HS:12.5m/s VS:4.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.9V delay:22ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:157.4m Distance:96.4m HS:12.2m/s VS:3.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.9V delay:27ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:158.0m Distance:95.5m HS:11.9m/s VS:1.7m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.9V delay:25ms bitrate:48.4Mbps Height:158.0m Distance:95.5m HS:11.9m/s VS:1.7m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:26ms bitrate:48.0Mbps Height:158.3m Distance:94.4m HS:11.9m/s VS:0.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:28ms bitrate:48.0Mbps Height:158.3m Distance:93.1m HS:11.9m/s VS:1.3m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:39ms bitrate:48.8Mbps Height:158.0m Distance:91.6m HS:11.9m/s VS:3.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:30ms bitrate:48.8Mbps Height:158.0m Distance:91.6m HS:11.9m/s VS:3.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:25ms bitrate:43.3Mbps Height:157.3m Distance:89.9m HS:12.1m/s VS:5.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:26ms bitrate:46.1Mbps Height:156.3m Distance:88.1m HS:12.3m/s VS:6.8m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:28ms bitrate:46.1Mbps Height:154.7m Distance:86.1m HS:12.3m/s VS:8.7m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:22ms bitrate:48.2Mbps Height:154.7m Distance:86.1m HS:12.3m/s VS:8.7m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:24ms bitrate:48.2Mbps Height:152.8m Distance:84.0m HS:12.4m/s VS:10.3m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:22ms bitrate:49.3Mbps Height:150.7m Distance:81.8m HS:12.8m/s VS:11.6m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:26ms bitrate:49.7Mbps Height:148.2m Distance:79.4m HS:13.5m/s VS:12.6m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:24ms bitrate:49.7Mbps Height:148.2m Distance:79.4m HS:13.5m/s VS:12.6m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:22ms bitrate:50.2Mbps Height:145.5m Distance:76.8m HS:14.3m/s VS:13.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:23ms bitrate:50.2Mbps Height:142.7m Distance:74.0m HS:15.2m/s VS:13.3m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:25ms bitrate:50.3Mbps Height:139.8m Distance:71.0m HS:16.2m/s VS:13.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:26ms bitrate:50.5Mbps Height:139.8m Distance:71.0m HS:16.2m/s VS:13.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:27ms bitrate:50.5Mbps Height:137.1m Distance:67.8m HS:17.1m/s VS:12.4m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:29ms bitrate:50.5Mbps Height:134.5m Distance:64.3m HS:18.2m/s VS:11.4m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:30ms bitrate:50.5Mbps Height:132.3m Distance:60.8m HS:19.2m/s VS:10.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:31ms bitrate:50.5Mbps Height:132.3m Distance:60.8m HS:19.2m/s VS:10.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:29ms bitrate:50.4Mbps Height:130.4m Distance:57.1m HS:19.9m/s VS:8.7m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:34ms bitrate:50.4Mbps Height:128.6m Distance:53.3m HS:20.5m/s VS:7.4m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:25ms bitrate:50.2Mbps Height:127.2m Distance:49.2m HS:21.1m/s VS:6.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:30ms bitrate:50.2Mbps Height:127.2m Distance:49.2m HS:21.1m/s VS:6.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:24ms bitrate:50.1Mbps Height:126.0m Distance:44.7m HS:21.3m/s VS:5.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:22ms bitrate:41.8Mbps Height:125.0m Distance:40.8m HS:21.6m/s VS:3.7m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:27ms bitrate:41.8Mbps Height:124.3m Distance:36.4m HS:21.6m/s VS:2.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:38ms bitrate:44.8Mbps Height:124.3m Distance:36.4m HS:21.6m/s VS:2.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:30ms bitrate:44.8Mbps Height:123.9m Distance:32.1m HS:21.4m/s VS:0.9m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:28ms bitrate:45.9Mbps Height:123.7m Distance:27.8m HS:21.2m/s VS:0.3m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:42ms bitrate:43.2Mbps Height:123.6m Distance:23.6m HS:20.9m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:37ms bitrate:43.2Mbps Height:123.6m Distance:23.6m HS:20.9m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:25ms bitrate:36.0Mbps Height:123.6m Distance:19.4m HS:20.7m/s VS:0.3m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:36ms bitrate:36.0Mbps Height:123.7m Distance:15.2m HS:20.4m/s VS:0.6m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:38ms bitrate:36.0Mbps Height:123.9m Distance:11.3m HS:20.3m/s VS:0.9m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:29ms bitrate:35.7Mbps Height:123.9m Distance:11.3m HS:20.3m/s VS:0.9m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:32ms bitrate:35.7Mbps Height:124.3m Distance:7.2m HS:20.0m/s VS:1.3m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:25ms bitrate:37.8Mbps Height:124.5m Distance:3.3m HS:19.8m/s VS:1.4m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:29ms bitrate:37.8Mbps Height:124.8m Distance:2.2m HS:19.6m/s VS:1.4m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:26ms bitrate:42.8Mbps Height:125.0m Distance:5.4m HS:19.5m/s VS:1.6m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:29ms bitrate:47.0Mbps Height:125.0m Distance:5.4m HS:19.5m/s VS:1.6m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:30ms bitrate:47.0Mbps Height:125.4m Distance:9.3m HS:19.3m/s VS:1.8m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:25ms bitrate:48.9Mbps Height:125.9m Distance:13.1m HS:19.2m/s VS:1.7m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:26ms bitrate:48.9Mbps Height:125.9m Distance:13.1m HS:19.2m/s VS:1.7m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:27ms bitrate:49.9Mbps Height:126.3m Distance:16.9m HS:18.9m/s VS:1.5m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:29ms bitrate:50.1Mbps Height:126.8m Distance:20.6m HS:18.7m/s VS:1.4m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:30ms bitrate:50.1Mbps Height:127.1m Distance:24.3m HS:18.5m/s VS:1.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:31ms bitrate:50.5Mbps Height:127.1m Distance:24.3m HS:18.5m/s VS:1.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:26ms bitrate:50.5Mbps Height:127.4m Distance:28.0m HS:18.2m/s VS:0.6m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:27ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:127.6m Distance:31.8m HS:17.9m/s VS:0.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:28ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:127.8m Distance:35.2m HS:17.7m/s VS:0.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:33ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:127.8m Distance:35.2m HS:17.7m/s VS:0.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:31ms bitrate:50.5Mbps Height:127.8m Distance:38.7m HS:17.6m/s VS:0.3m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.9V delay:29ms bitrate:50.5Mbps Height:127.8m Distance:42.2m HS:17.6m/s VS:0.5m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.9V delay:34ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:127.7m Distance:45.7m HS:17.6m/s VS:0.6m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.9V delay:25ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:127.7m Distance:45.7m HS:17.6m/s VS:0.6m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.9V delay:30ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:127.7m Distance:49.2m HS:17.6m/s VS:0.6m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.9V delay:31ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:127.5m Distance:52.8m HS:17.6m/s VS:0.7m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.9V delay:27ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:127.4m Distance:56.4m HS:17.6m/s VS:0.7m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:25ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:127.2m Distance:59.7m HS:17.6m/s VS:0.8m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:26ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:127.1m Distance:63.2m HS:17.3m/s VS:0.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:24ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:127.2m Distance:66.7m HS:16.1m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:22ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:127.2m Distance:66.7m HS:16.1m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:23ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:127.0m Distance:69.6m HS:12.6m/s VS:0.3m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:25ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:127.1m Distance:71.7m HS:7.2m/s VS:0.4m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:26ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:127.0m Distance:72.8m HS:1.7m/s VS:0.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:27ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:127.0m Distance:72.8m HS:1.7m/s VS:0.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:32ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:127.2m Distance:73.2m HS:0.3m/s VS:0.5m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:33ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:127.3m Distance:73.5m HS:0.3m/s VS:0.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:35ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:127.2m Distance:73.6m HS:0.4m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:29ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:127.2m Distance:73.6m HS:0.4m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:30ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:127.2m Distance:73.3m HS:0.4m/s VS:0.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.8V delay:29ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:127.2m Distance:73.2m HS:0.3m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.8V delay:30ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:127.2m Distance:73.1m HS:0.1m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.8V delay:31ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:127.2m Distance:73.1m HS:0.1m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.8V delay:26ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:127.2m Distance:73.1m HS:0.1m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.8V delay:27ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:127.2m Distance:73.0m HS:0.1m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.8V delay:28ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:127.3m Distance:73.0m HS:0.1m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.8V delay:30ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:127.3m Distance:73.0m HS:0.1m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.7V delay:31ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:127.3m Distance:72.9m HS:0.1m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.7V delay:27ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:127.4m Distance:72.9m HS:0.1m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.7V delay:27ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:127.5m Distance:72.9m HS:0.1m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.7V delay:28ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:127.5m Distance:72.9m HS:0.1m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.7V delay:28ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:127.6m Distance:72.9m HS:0.1m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.7V delay:31ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:127.7m Distance:72.9m HS:0.1m/s VS:0.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.7V delay:32ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:127.8m Distance:72.9m HS:0.1m/s VS:0.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:34ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:127.8m Distance:72.9m HS:0.1m/s VS:0.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:28ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:127.8m Distance:72.9m HS:0.1m/s VS:0.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:37ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:127.7m Distance:72.9m HS:0.1m/s VS:0.6m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:31ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:127.5m Distance:73.0m HS:0.1m/s VS:0.9m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:32ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:127.5m Distance:73.0m HS:0.1m/s VS:0.9m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:27ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:127.3m Distance:73.0m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.6V delay:25ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:127.2m Distance:73.0m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.6V delay:29ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:127.0m Distance:73.0m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.6V delay:31ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:127.0m Distance:73.0m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.6V delay:25ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:126.8m Distance:73.0m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.3m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.6V delay:26ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:126.6m Distance:73.0m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.3m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.6V delay:28ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:126.3m Distance:73.0m HS:0.1m/s VS:1.3m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.6V delay:26ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:126.3m Distance:73.0m HS:0.1m/s VS:1.3m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:30ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:126.0m Distance:73.0m HS:0.1m/s VS:1.3m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:32ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:125.7m Distance:73.0m HS:0.1m/s VS:1.4m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:26ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:125.4m Distance:73.0m HS:0.1m/s VS:1.7m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:25ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:125.0m Distance:73.0m HS:0.1m/s VS:1.8m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:29ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:125.0m Distance:73.0m HS:0.1m/s VS:1.8m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:30ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:124.6m Distance:73.0m HS:0.1m/s VS:1.9m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:33ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:124.4m Distance:73.0m HS:0.1m/s VS:2.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.5V delay:30ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:124.4m Distance:73.0m HS:0.1m/s VS:2.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.5V delay:27ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:124.0m Distance:73.0m HS:0.1m/s VS:2.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.5V delay:26ms bitrate:50.5Mbps Height:123.5m Distance:73.1m HS:0.1m/s VS:2.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.5V delay:27ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:123.1m Distance:73.0m HS:0.0m/s VS:2.3m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.5V delay:28ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:122.7m Distance:73.0m HS:0.0m/s VS:2.3m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.5V delay:30ms bitrate:50.5Mbps Height:122.7m Distance:73.0m HS:0.0m/s VS:2.3m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.7V delay:31ms bitrate:50.5Mbps Height:122.3m Distance:73.0m HS:0.0m/s VS:2.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.7V delay:25ms bitrate:50.4Mbps Height:121.9m Distance:73.0m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.9m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.7V delay:27ms bitrate:50.4Mbps Height:121.5m Distance:73.0m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.7m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.7V delay:25ms bitrate:50.4Mbps Height:121.5m Distance:73.0m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.7m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.7V delay:26ms bitrate:50.5Mbps Height:121.1m Distance:73.0m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.7m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.7V delay:31ms bitrate:50.5Mbps Height:120.7m Distance:73.0m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.6m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.7V delay:32ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:120.4m Distance:73.0m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.6m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:30ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:120.4m Distance:73.0m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.6m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:35ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:120.0m Distance:72.9m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.6m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:29ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:119.7m Distance:72.9m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.6m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:28ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:119.3m Distance:72.9m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.6m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:32ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:119.3m Distance:72.9m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.6m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:26ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:119.0m Distance:72.9m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.6m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:28ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:118.6m Distance:72.9m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.6m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:26ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:118.3m Distance:72.9m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.6m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:27ms bitrate:50.4Mbps Height:118.3m Distance:72.9m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.6m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:29ms bitrate:50.4Mbps Height:117.9m Distance:72.9m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.6m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:30ms bitrate:50.4Mbps Height:117.6m Distance:72.9m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.6m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:28ms bitrate:50.4Mbps Height:117.2m Distance:72.9m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.6m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:26ms bitrate:50.5Mbps Height:117.2m Distance:72.9m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.6m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.7V delay:29ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:116.8m Distance:72.9m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.6m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.7V delay:29ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:116.4m Distance:72.9m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.6m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.7V delay:23ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:116.1m Distance:72.8m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.6m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.7V delay:24ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:116.1m Distance:72.8m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.6m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.7V delay:26ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:115.7m Distance:72.8m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.6m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.7V delay:27ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:115.5m Distance:72.8m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.5m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.7V delay:28ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:115.1m Distance:72.8m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.5m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.6V delay:23ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:115.1m Distance:72.8m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.5m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.6V delay:29ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:114.7m Distance:72.8m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.6m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.6V delay:26ms bitrate:50.5Mbps Height:114.4m Distance:72.8m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.6m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.6V delay:27ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:114.1m Distance:72.8m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.6m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.6V delay:28ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:114.1m Distance:72.8m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.6m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.6V delay:23ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:113.7m Distance:72.8m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.6m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.6V delay:24ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:113.4m Distance:72.8m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.5m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.2V delay:22ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:113.1m Distance:72.8m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.5m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.2V delay:24ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:113.1m Distance:72.8m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.5m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.2V delay:25ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:112.8m Distance:72.8m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.5m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.2V delay:26ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:112.5m Distance:72.8m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.6m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.2V delay:24ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:112.2m Distance:72.8m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.6m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.2V delay:25ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:112.2m Distance:72.8m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.6m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.8V delay:23ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:111.9m Distance:72.8m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.6m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.8V delay:28ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:111.5m Distance:72.8m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.5m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.8V delay:26ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:111.2m Distance:72.8m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.5m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.8V delay:27ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:111.2m Distance:72.8m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.5m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.8V delay:22ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:110.9m Distance:72.8m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.6m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.8V delay:23ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:110.6m Distance:72.8m HS:0.2m/s VS:1.6m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.8V delay:25ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:110.2m Distance:72.8m HS:0.5m/s VS:1.6m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:26ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:110.2m Distance:72.8m HS:0.5m/s VS:1.6m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:27ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:109.9m Distance:72.7m HS:1.0m/s VS:1.6m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:22ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:109.6m Distance:72.6m HS:1.3m/s VS:1.6m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:23ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:109.3m Distance:72.5m HS:1.0m/s VS:1.4m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:26ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:109.0m Distance:72.4m HS:0.5m/s VS:1.5m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:24ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:108.7m Distance:72.3m HS:0.1m/s VS:1.5m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.9V delay:25ms bitrate:50.5Mbps Height:108.4m Distance:72.3m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.5m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.9V delay:30ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:108.4m Distance:72.3m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.5m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.9V delay:24ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:108.1m Distance:72.3m HS:0.1m/s VS:1.3m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.9V delay:22ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:107.9m Distance:72.3m HS:0.1m/s VS:1.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.9V delay:24ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:107.6m Distance:72.3m HS:0.1m/s VS:1.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.9V delay:25ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:107.6m Distance:72.3m HS:0.1m/s VS:1.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:25ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:107.4m Distance:72.3m HS:0.1m/s VS:1.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:28ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:107.2m Distance:72.3m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:29ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:107.0m Distance:72.3m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:24ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:107.0m Distance:72.3m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:22ms bitrate:50.5Mbps Height:106.7m Distance:72.2m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:23ms bitrate:50.4Mbps Height:106.5m Distance:72.2m HS:0.1m/s VS:1.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:28ms bitrate:50.4Mbps Height:106.3m Distance:72.2m HS:0.1m/s VS:1.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:29ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:106.3m Distance:72.2m HS:0.1m/s VS:1.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:34ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:106.1m Distance:72.2m HS:0.1m/s VS:1.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:25ms bitrate:50.2Mbps Height:105.8m Distance:72.1m HS:0.1m/s VS:1.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:23ms bitrate:50.1Mbps Height:105.5m Distance:72.1m HS:0.1m/s VS:1.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:28ms bitrate:50.1Mbps Height:105.3m Distance:72.1m HS:0.1m/s VS:1.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:29ms bitrate:50.5Mbps Height:105.3m Distance:72.1m HS:0.1m/s VS:1.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:23ms bitrate:50.5Mbps Height:105.1m Distance:72.0m HS:0.1m/s VS:1.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.6V delay:33ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:104.9m Distance:72.0m HS:0.1m/s VS:0.9m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.6V delay:26ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:104.9m Distance:72.0m HS:0.1m/s VS:0.9m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.6V delay:27ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:104.7m Distance:72.0m HS:0.1m/s VS:0.6m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.6V delay:29ms bitrate:50.5Mbps Height:104.7m Distance:72.0m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.4m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.6V delay:23ms bitrate:50.5Mbps Height:104.6m Distance:72.0m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.3m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.6V delay:24ms bitrate:50.0Mbps Height:104.6m Distance:72.0m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.3m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.6V delay:23ms bitrate:50.1Mbps Height:104.6m Distance:72.0m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.3m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.6V delay:34ms bitrate:50.1Mbps Height:104.5m Distance:72.0m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.3m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.6V delay:25ms bitrate:50.2Mbps Height:104.5m Distance:72.0m HS:0.1m/s VS:0.1m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.6V delay:23ms bitrate:50.2Mbps Height:104.5m Distance:72.0m HS:0.1m/s VS:0.1m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.6V delay:24ms bitrate:50.2Mbps Height:104.6m Distance:72.1m HS:0.1m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.6V delay:26ms bitrate:50.4Mbps Height:104.6m Distance:72.1m HS:0.1m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.6V delay:24ms bitrate:50.4Mbps Height:104.6m Distance:72.1m HS:0.1m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.2V delay:25ms bitrate:50.5Mbps Height:104.6m Distance:72.1m HS:0.1m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.2V delay:28ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:104.6m Distance:72.2m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.2V delay:24ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:104.6m Distance:72.2m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.2V delay:24ms bitrate:50.3Mbps Height:104.6m Distance:72.2m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.2V delay:34ms bitrate:50.3Mbps Height:104.6m Distance:72.2m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.2V delay:28ms bitrate:50.2Mbps Height:104.6m Distance:72.2m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.5V delay:25ms bitrate:50.2Mbps Height:104.6m Distance:72.2m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.5V delay:24ms bitrate:50.2Mbps Height:104.7m Distance:72.2m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.5V delay:25ms bitrate:50.2Mbps Height:104.7m Distance:72.2m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.5V delay:24ms bitrate:50.2Mbps Height:104.7m Distance:72.3m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.5V delay:25ms bitrate:50.4Mbps Height:104.7m Distance:72.3m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.5V delay:22ms bitrate:50.4Mbps Height:104.7m Distance:72.3m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.5V delay:24ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:104.7m Distance:72.3m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:25ms bitrate:50.5Mbps Height:104.7m Distance:72.3m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:26ms bitrate:50.5Mbps Height:104.8m Distance:72.3m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:25ms bitrate:50.3Mbps Height:104.8m Distance:72.3m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:26ms bitrate:50.3Mbps Height:104.8m Distance:72.3m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:27ms bitrate:50.3Mbps Height:104.8m Distance:72.3m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:31ms bitrate:50.3Mbps Height:104.8m Distance:72.3m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:23ms bitrate:50.3Mbps Height:104.8m Distance:72.4m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.4V delay:25ms bitrate:50.4Mbps Height:104.8m Distance:72.4m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.4V delay:26ms bitrate:50.4Mbps Height:104.8m Distance:72.4m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.4V delay:27ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:104.8m Distance:72.4m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.4V delay:22ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:104.8m Distance:72.4m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.4V delay:23ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:104.8m Distance:72.4m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.4V delay:24ms bitrate:50.5Mbps Height:104.8m Distance:72.4m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.9V delay:26ms bitrate:50.5Mbps Height:104.8m Distance:72.4m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.9V delay:27ms bitrate:50.3Mbps Height:104.8m Distance:72.5m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.9V delay:28ms bitrate:50.5Mbps Height:104.8m Distance:72.5m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.9V delay:30ms bitrate:50.5Mbps Height:104.9m Distance:72.5m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.9V delay:24ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:104.9m Distance:72.5m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.9V delay:25ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:104.9m Distance:72.5m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.9V delay:27ms bitrate:50.4Mbps Height:104.9m Distance:72.5m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:28ms bitrate:50.5Mbps Height:104.9m Distance:72.5m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:23ms bitrate:50.5Mbps Height:104.9m Distance:72.5m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:25ms bitrate:50.5Mbps Height:104.9m Distance:72.5m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:24ms bitrate:50.4Mbps Height:104.9m Distance:72.6m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:28ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:105.0m Distance:72.6m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:29ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:105.0m Distance:72.6m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:26ms bitrate:50.5Mbps Height:105.0m Distance:72.6m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:25ms bitrate:50.5Mbps Height:105.0m Distance:72.6m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:23ms bitrate:50.5Mbps Height:105.1m Distance:72.6m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:28ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:105.1m Distance:72.6m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:29ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:105.1m Distance:72.6m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:29ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:105.1m Distance:72.6m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.9V delay:25ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:105.1m Distance:72.6m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.9V delay:26ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:105.1m Distance:72.6m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.9V delay:25ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:105.1m Distance:72.6m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.9V delay:26ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:105.2m Distance:72.6m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.9V delay:27ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:105.1m Distance:72.6m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.9V delay:22ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:105.1m Distance:72.6m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.9V delay:23ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:105.1m Distance:72.6m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.8V delay:24ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:105.1m Distance:72.6m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.8V delay:26ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:105.0m Distance:72.6m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.8V delay:27ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:105.0m Distance:72.7m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.8V delay:25ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:105.0m Distance:72.7m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.8V delay:23ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:105.0m Distance:72.7m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.8V delay:24ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:104.9m Distance:72.7m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.8V delay:27ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:104.9m Distance:72.7m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:24ms bitrate:50.5Mbps Height:104.9m Distance:72.7m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:25ms bitrate:50.5Mbps Height:104.9m Distance:72.7m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:30ms bitrate:50.4Mbps Height:104.9m Distance:72.7m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:24ms bitrate:50.4Mbps Height:104.9m Distance:72.7m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:25ms bitrate:50.4Mbps Height:104.9m Distance:72.7m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:24ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:104.9m Distance:72.7m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:25ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:104.9m Distance:72.7m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:26ms bitrate:50.5Mbps Height:104.8m Distance:72.7m HS:0.1m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:28ms bitrate:50.4Mbps Height:104.8m Distance:72.7m HS:0.1m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:25ms bitrate:50.4Mbps Height:104.8m Distance:72.7m HS:0.1m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:25ms bitrate:50.4Mbps Height:104.8m Distance:72.7m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:26ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:104.8m Distance:72.7m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.0V delay:27ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:104.8m Distance:72.7m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.0V delay:29ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:104.8m Distance:72.7m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.0V delay:30ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:104.8m Distance:72.7m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.0V delay:25ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:104.9m Distance:72.7m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.0V delay:26ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:104.9m Distance:72.7m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.0V delay:27ms bitrate:50.3Mbps Height:104.8m Distance:72.8m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.0V delay:29ms bitrate:50.3Mbps Height:104.8m Distance:72.8m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:9.0V delay:23ms bitrate:50.3Mbps Height:104.8m Distance:72.8m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:9.0V delay:22ms bitrate:50.5Mbps Height:104.8m Distance:72.8m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:9.0V delay:26ms bitrate:50.5Mbps Height:104.9m Distance:72.8m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:9.0V delay:24ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:104.9m Distance:72.8m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:9.0V delay:26ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:104.9m Distance:72.8m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:9.0V delay:23ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:104.9m Distance:72.8m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:24ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:104.9m Distance:72.8m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:27ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:104.8m Distance:72.8m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:24ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:104.8m Distance:72.8m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:25ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:104.8m Distance:72.8m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:23ms bitrate:50.4Mbps Height:104.8m Distance:72.8m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:24ms bitrate:50.4Mbps Height:104.8m Distance:72.8m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:22ms bitrate:50.4Mbps Height:104.9m Distance:72.8m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:24ms bitrate:50.5Mbps Height:104.9m Distance:72.8m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:25ms bitrate:50.5Mbps Height:104.9m Distance:72.8m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:26ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:104.9m Distance:72.8m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:28ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:104.9m Distance:72.8m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:32ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:104.9m Distance:72.8m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:27ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:104.9m Distance:72.8m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:25ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:104.9m Distance:72.8m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.5V delay:26ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:104.8m Distance:72.8m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.5V delay:28ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:104.8m Distance:72.8m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.5V delay:29ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:104.8m Distance:72.8m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.5V delay:30ms bitrate:50.4Mbps Height:104.7m Distance:72.8m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.5V delay:32ms bitrate:50.4Mbps Height:104.7m Distance:72.8m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.5V delay:26ms bitrate:50.3Mbps Height:104.7m Distance:72.8m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.3V delay:27ms bitrate:50.5Mbps Height:104.7m Distance:72.8m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.3V delay:25ms bitrate:50.5Mbps Height:104.7m Distance:72.8m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.3V delay:26ms bitrate:50.4Mbps Height:104.7m Distance:72.8m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.3V delay:26ms bitrate:50.2Mbps Height:104.7m Distance:72.8m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.3V delay:24ms bitrate:50.1Mbps Height:104.7m Distance:72.8m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.3V delay:22ms bitrate:50.1Mbps Height:104.7m Distance:72.8m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:30ms bitrate:49.8Mbps Height:104.7m Distance:72.8m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:24ms bitrate:49.8Mbps Height:104.7m Distance:72.8m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:26ms bitrate:50.1Mbps Height:104.7m Distance:72.8m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:24ms bitrate:50.0Mbps Height:104.7m Distance:72.9m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:28ms bitrate:50.0Mbps Height:104.7m Distance:72.9m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:30ms bitrate:50.0Mbps Height:104.7m Distance:72.9m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:24ms bitrate:50.0Mbps Height:104.7m Distance:72.9m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:25ms bitrate:50.2Mbps Height:104.8m Distance:72.9m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:27ms bitrate:50.4Mbps Height:104.8m Distance:72.9m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:25ms bitrate:50.4Mbps Height:104.8m Distance:72.9m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:26ms bitrate:50.3Mbps Height:104.8m Distance:72.9m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:28ms bitrate:50.3Mbps Height:104.8m Distance:72.9m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:29ms bitrate:50.3Mbps Height:104.8m Distance:72.9m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.3V delay:24ms bitrate:50.5Mbps Height:104.8m Distance:72.9m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.3V delay:32ms bitrate:50.5Mbps Height:104.8m Distance:72.9m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.3V delay:23ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:104.8m Distance:72.9m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.3V delay:28ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:104.8m Distance:72.9m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.3V delay:29ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:104.7m Distance:72.9m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.3V delay:23ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:104.7m Distance:72.9m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.3V delay:25ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:104.7m Distance:72.9m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.3V delay:23ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:104.7m Distance:72.9m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.3V delay:24ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:104.6m Distance:72.9m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.3V delay:29ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:104.6m Distance:72.9m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.3V delay:30ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:104.6m Distance:72.9m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.3V delay:31ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:104.6m Distance:72.9m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.3V delay:26ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:104.6m Distance:72.9m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.3V delay:24ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:104.6m Distance:72.9m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.0V delay:27ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:104.5m Distance:72.9m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.0V delay:23ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:104.5m Distance:72.9m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.0V delay:28ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:104.5m Distance:72.9m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.0V delay:29ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:104.5m Distance:72.9m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.0V delay:27ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:104.5m Distance:72.9m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.0V delay:25ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:104.5m Distance:72.9m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:27ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:104.5m Distance:72.9m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:21ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:104.5m Distance:72.9m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:24ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:104.5m Distance:72.9m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:31ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:104.5m Distance:72.9m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:25ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:104.5m Distance:72.9m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:25ms bitrate:50.5Mbps Height:104.5m Distance:73.0m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:28ms bitrate:50.5Mbps Height:104.5m Distance:73.0m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:29ms bitrate:50.5Mbps Height:104.5m Distance:73.0m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:30ms bitrate:50.5Mbps Height:104.5m Distance:73.0m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:25ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:104.5m Distance:73.0m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:33ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:104.5m Distance:73.0m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:28ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:104.5m Distance:73.0m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:29ms bitrate:50.5Mbps Height:104.5m Distance:73.0m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.1V delay:30ms bitrate:50.5Mbps Height:104.5m Distance:73.0m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.3m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.1V delay:25ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:104.6m Distance:73.0m HS:0.1m/s VS:0.4m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.1V delay:23ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:104.6m Distance:73.0m HS:0.1m/s VS:0.4m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.1V delay:24ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:104.7m Distance:73.0m HS:0.1m/s VS:0.4m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.1V delay:29ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:104.8m Distance:72.9m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.3m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.1V delay:30ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:104.8m Distance:72.9m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.3m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.1V delay:25ms bitrate:50.5Mbps Height:104.8m Distance:72.9m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.3m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.1V delay:26ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:104.9m Distance:72.9m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.3m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.1V delay:24ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:105.0m Distance:72.9m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.3m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.1V delay:25ms bitrate:50.4Mbps Height:105.1m Distance:73.0m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.1V delay:30ms bitrate:50.4Mbps Height:105.1m Distance:73.0m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.1V delay:29ms bitrate:50.1Mbps Height:105.2m Distance:72.9m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.1V delay:23ms bitrate:50.1Mbps Height:105.3m Distance:72.9m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.1V delay:27ms bitrate:50.1Mbps Height:105.3m Distance:72.9m HS:0.1m/s VS:0.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:25ms bitrate:50.1Mbps Height:105.3m Distance:72.9m HS:0.1m/s VS:0.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:27ms bitrate:50.1Mbps Height:105.4m Distance:72.9m HS:0.1m/s VS:0.9m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:28ms bitrate:50.4Mbps Height:105.8m Distance:72.9m HS:0.1m/s VS:2.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:24ms bitrate:50.5Mbps Height:105.8m Distance:72.9m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.6m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:24ms bitrate:50.5Mbps Height:106.1m Distance:72.9m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.8m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:22ms bitrate:50.5Mbps Height:106.1m Distance:72.9m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.8m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:23ms bitrate:50.5Mbps Height:106.2m Distance:72.9m HS:0.1m/s VS:0.3m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:28ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:106.3m Distance:72.9m HS:0.1m/s VS:0.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:29ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:106.3m Distance:72.9m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:30ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:106.3m Distance:72.9m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:25ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:106.4m Distance:72.9m HS:0.1m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:26ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:106.4m Distance:72.9m HS:0.3m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:28ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:106.5m Distance:72.8m HS:0.7m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.1V delay:26ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:106.5m Distance:72.8m HS:0.7m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.1V delay:25ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:106.5m Distance:72.6m HS:1.2m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.1V delay:25ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:106.5m Distance:72.3m HS:1.7m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.1V delay:26ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:106.6m Distance:72.0m HS:2.1m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.1V delay:24ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:106.6m Distance:72.0m HS:2.1m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.1V delay:26ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:106.6m Distance:71.6m HS:2.4m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.1V delay:27ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:106.6m Distance:71.1m HS:2.8m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:9.1V delay:28ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:106.6m Distance:70.5m HS:3.2m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:9.1V delay:30ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:106.6m Distance:70.5m HS:3.2m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:9.1V delay:26ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:106.6m Distance:69.8m HS:3.7m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:9.1V delay:26ms bitrate:50.4Mbps Height:106.6m Distance:69.1m HS:4.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:9.1V delay:27ms bitrate:50.4Mbps Height:106.6m Distance:68.3m HS:4.3m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:9.1V delay:28ms bitrate:50.5Mbps Height:106.6m Distance:68.3m HS:4.3m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:30ms bitrate:50.5Mbps Height:106.6m Distance:67.4m HS:4.7m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:24ms bitrate:50.5Mbps Height:106.6m Distance:66.5m HS:4.9m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:27ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:106.6m Distance:65.5m HS:5.2m/s VS:0.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:28ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:106.7m Distance:64.4m HS:5.4m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:29ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:106.7m Distance:63.3m HS:5.5m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:24ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:106.7m Distance:62.3m HS:5.5m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:22ms bitrate:50.5Mbps Height:106.7m Distance:62.3m HS:5.5m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:28ms bitrate:50.5Mbps Height:106.7m Distance:61.3m HS:5.2m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:25ms bitrate:50.5Mbps Height:106.6m Distance:60.3m HS:5.0m/s VS:0.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:26ms bitrate:50.5Mbps Height:106.6m Distance:59.3m HS:4.6m/s VS:0.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:27ms bitrate:50.4Mbps Height:106.6m Distance:59.3m HS:4.6m/s VS:0.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:22ms bitrate:50.5Mbps Height:106.6m Distance:58.5m HS:4.3m/s VS:0.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:26ms bitrate:50.5Mbps Height:106.6m Distance:57.6m HS:4.1m/s VS:0.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.1V delay:25ms bitrate:50.4Mbps Height:106.6m Distance:56.7m HS:4.0m/s VS:0.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.1V delay:26ms bitrate:50.5Mbps Height:106.6m Distance:56.7m HS:4.0m/s VS:0.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.1V delay:27ms bitrate:50.5Mbps Height:106.6m Distance:55.9m HS:4.0m/s VS:0.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.1V delay:29ms bitrate:50.3Mbps Height:106.6m Distance:55.1m HS:4.1m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.1V delay:23ms bitrate:50.3Mbps Height:106.5m Distance:54.4m HS:4.1m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.1V delay:24ms bitrate:50.5Mbps Height:106.5m Distance:54.4m HS:4.1m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.0V delay:26ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:106.5m Distance:53.6m HS:4.4m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.0V delay:30ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:106.5m Distance:52.9m HS:4.6m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.0V delay:28ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:106.5m Distance:52.1m HS:4.8m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.0V delay:23ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:106.5m Distance:52.1m HS:4.8m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.0V delay:24ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:106.5m Distance:51.5m HS:5.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.0V delay:22ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:106.5m Distance:50.8m HS:4.9m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.0V delay:24ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:106.5m Distance:50.3m HS:3.4m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:28ms bitrate:50.4Mbps Height:106.5m Distance:50.3m HS:3.4m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:23ms bitrate:50.4Mbps Height:106.5m Distance:50.0m HS:1.9m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:21ms bitrate:50.4Mbps Height:106.5m Distance:49.8m HS:1.1m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:25ms bitrate:50.5Mbps Height:106.5m Distance:49.7m HS:0.6m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:24ms bitrate:50.5Mbps Height:106.5m Distance:49.7m HS:0.6m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:25ms bitrate:50.4Mbps Height:106.5m Distance:49.7m HS:0.2m/s VS:0.1m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:29ms bitrate:50.4Mbps Height:106.5m Distance:49.8m HS:0.2m/s VS:0.2m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:24ms bitrate:50.5Mbps Height:106.6m Distance:49.9m HS:0.1m/s VS:0.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:22ms bitrate:50.3Mbps Height:106.6m Distance:49.9m HS:0.1m/s VS:0.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:27ms bitrate:50.3Mbps Height:106.5m Distance:50.0m HS:0.1m/s VS:0.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:25ms bitrate:50.4Mbps Height:106.6m Distance:50.1m HS:0.1m/s VS:0.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:26ms bitrate:50.4Mbps Height:106.6m Distance:50.1m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:27ms bitrate:50.4Mbps Height:106.6m Distance:50.1m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.1V delay:25ms bitrate:50.5Mbps Height:106.7m Distance:50.2m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.1V delay:23ms bitrate:50.5Mbps Height:106.7m Distance:50.2m HS:0.1m/s VS:0.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.1V delay:25ms bitrate:50.4Mbps Height:106.8m Distance:50.2m HS:0.1m/s VS:0.3m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.1V delay:26ms bitrate:50.4Mbps Height:106.8m Distance:50.2m HS:0.1m/s VS:0.3m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.1V delay:27ms bitrate:50.4Mbps Height:106.9m Distance:50.3m HS:0.2m/s VS:0.3m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.1V delay:29ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:107.0m Distance:50.2m HS:0.3m/s VS:0.4m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.1V delay:23ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:107.0m Distance:50.2m HS:0.4m/s VS:0.4m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.2V delay:26ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:107.1m Distance:50.1m HS:0.2m/s VS:0.2m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.2V delay:27ms bitrate:50.3Mbps Height:107.2m Distance:50.1m HS:0.1m/s VS:0.1m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.2V delay:28ms bitrate:50.4Mbps Height:107.2m Distance:50.1m HS:0.1m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.2V delay:23ms bitrate:50.4Mbps Height:107.2m Distance:50.1m HS:0.1m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.2V delay:24ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:107.1m Distance:50.1m HS:0.1m/s VS:0.7m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.2V delay:26ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:107.0m Distance:50.1m HS:0.1m/s VS:1.0m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.3V delay:24ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:106.8m Distance:50.2m HS:0.1m/s VS:0.8m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.3V delay:32ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:106.8m Distance:50.2m HS:0.1m/s VS:0.8m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.3V delay:27ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:106.7m Distance:50.2m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.6m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.3V delay:24ms bitrate:50.3Mbps Height:106.6m Distance:50.2m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.5m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.3V delay:24ms bitrate:50.2Mbps Height:106.4m Distance:50.2m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.6m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:25ms bitrate:50.2Mbps Height:106.3m Distance:50.2m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.6m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:26ms bitrate:50.2Mbps Height:106.1m Distance:50.2m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.6m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:25ms bitrate:50.5Mbps Height:106.0m Distance:50.3m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.6m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:29ms bitrate:50.5Mbps Height:106.0m Distance:50.3m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.6m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:24ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:105.9m Distance:50.3m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.5m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:25ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:105.7m Distance:50.3m HS:0.1m/s VS:0.5m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:23ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:105.7m Distance:50.3m HS:0.1m/s VS:0.3m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:22ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:105.7m Distance:50.3m HS:0.1m/s VS:0.2m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:29ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:105.7m Distance:50.3m HS:0.1m/s VS:0.2m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:23ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:105.7m Distance:50.3m HS:0.1m/s VS:0.2m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:25ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:105.6m Distance:50.3m HS:0.1m/s VS:0.2m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:33ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:105.6m Distance:50.3m HS:0.1m/s VS:0.2m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:27ms bitrate:50.4Mbps Height:105.6m Distance:50.2m HS:0.1m/s VS:0.2m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.3V delay:22ms bitrate:50.4Mbps Height:105.6m Distance:50.2m HS:0.1m/s VS:0.2m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.3V delay:30ms bitrate:50.5Mbps Height:105.6m Distance:50.2m HS:0.1m/s VS:0.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.3V delay:29ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:105.5m Distance:50.2m HS:0.1m/s VS:0.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.3V delay:26ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:105.5m Distance:50.2m HS:0.1m/s VS:0.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.3V delay:24ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:105.5m Distance:50.2m HS:0.1m/s VS:0.2m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.3V delay:25ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:105.5m Distance:50.1m HS:0.1m/s VS:0.2m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.3V delay:27ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:105.5m Distance:50.1m HS:0.1m/s VS:0.2m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.4V delay:24ms bitrate:50.4Mbps Height:105.4m Distance:50.1m HS:0.1m/s VS:0.2m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.4V delay:23ms bitrate:50.4Mbps Height:105.4m Distance:50.1m HS:0.1m/s VS:0.2m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.4V delay:24ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:105.4m Distance:50.1m HS:0.1m/s VS:0.2m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.4V delay:26ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:105.3m Distance:50.1m HS:0.1m/s VS:0.2m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.4V delay:27ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:105.3m Distance:50.1m HS:0.1m/s VS:0.2m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.4V delay:28ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:105.3m Distance:50.0m HS:0.1m/s VS:0.2m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.4V delay:24ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:105.3m Distance:50.0m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.3m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:34ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:105.3m Distance:50.0m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.3m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:28ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:105.2m Distance:50.0m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.3m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:26ms bitrate:50.2Mbps Height:105.1m Distance:49.9m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.4m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:28ms bitrate:50.1Mbps Height:105.0m Distance:49.9m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.5m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:22ms bitrate:50.1Mbps Height:105.0m Distance:49.9m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.5m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:24ms bitrate:50.2Mbps Height:104.9m Distance:49.9m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.7m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.2V delay:25ms bitrate:50.2Mbps Height:104.8m Distance:49.9m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.9m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.2V delay:26ms bitrate:50.2Mbps Height:104.6m Distance:49.9m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.9m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.2V delay:28ms bitrate:50.2Mbps Height:104.4m Distance:49.9m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.0m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.2V delay:22ms bitrate:50.2Mbps Height:104.4m Distance:49.9m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.0m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.2V delay:23ms bitrate:50.3Mbps Height:104.2m Distance:49.9m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.0m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.2V delay:22ms bitrate:50.3Mbps Height:104.1m Distance:49.9m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.0m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.2V delay:23ms bitrate:50.5Mbps Height:103.9m Distance:49.9m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.0m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.5V delay:27ms bitrate:50.5Mbps Height:103.9m Distance:49.9m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.0m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.5V delay:26ms bitrate:50.5Mbps Height:103.6m Distance:49.9m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.1m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.5V delay:30ms bitrate:50.5Mbps Height:103.4m Distance:49.9m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.1m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.5V delay:25ms bitrate:50.5Mbps Height:103.2m Distance:49.9m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.0m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.5V delay:33ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:103.2m Distance:49.9m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.0m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.5V delay:24ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:103.0m Distance:49.9m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.0m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.5V delay:29ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:102.8m Distance:49.9m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.0m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:9.0V delay:27ms bitrate:50.5Mbps Height:102.6m Distance:49.9m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.0m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:9.0V delay:28ms bitrate:50.5Mbps Height:102.6m Distance:49.9m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.0m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:9.0V delay:23ms bitrate:50.4Mbps Height:102.4m Distance:49.9m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.0m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:9.0V delay:24ms bitrate:50.5Mbps Height:102.3m Distance:49.9m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.0m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:9.0V delay:25ms bitrate:50.5Mbps Height:102.1m Distance:49.9m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.0m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:9.0V delay:27ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:102.1m Distance:49.9m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.0m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:24ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:101.9m Distance:49.9m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.0m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:29ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:101.7m Distance:49.9m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.0m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:31ms bitrate:50.4Mbps Height:101.5m Distance:49.9m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.0m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:32ms bitrate:50.4Mbps Height:101.5m Distance:49.9m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.0m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:24ms bitrate:50.2Mbps Height:101.3m Distance:49.9m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.0m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:28ms bitrate:50.2Mbps Height:101.1m Distance:49.8m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.0m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:19ms bitrate:50.0Mbps Height:100.9m Distance:49.9m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.8m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:26ms bitrate:50.1Mbps Height:100.8m Distance:49.8m HS:0.1m/s VS:0.3m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:32ms bitrate:50.1Mbps Height:100.8m Distance:49.8m HS:0.1m/s VS:0.3m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:26ms bitrate:50.1Mbps Height:100.7m Distance:49.8m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.1m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:28ms bitrate:50.1Mbps Height:100.7m Distance:49.8m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:29ms bitrate:50.0Mbps Height:100.7m Distance:49.8m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:23ms bitrate:50.2Mbps Height:100.7m Distance:49.8m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:25ms bitrate:50.2Mbps Height:100.7m Distance:49.8m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.9V delay:26ms bitrate:50.3Mbps Height:100.7m Distance:49.8m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.9V delay:24ms bitrate:50.3Mbps Height:100.7m Distance:49.8m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.9V delay:26ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:100.7m Distance:49.8m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.9V delay:27ms bitrate:50.3Mbps Height:100.7m Distance:49.8m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.9V delay:21ms bitrate:50.3Mbps Height:100.7m Distance:49.8m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.9V delay:30ms bitrate:50.3Mbps Height:100.7m Distance:49.8m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.0V delay:31ms bitrate:50.3Mbps Height:100.7m Distance:49.8m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.0V delay:32ms bitrate:50.5Mbps Height:100.7m Distance:49.8m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.0V delay:27ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:100.7m Distance:49.8m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.0V delay:28ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:100.7m Distance:49.8m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.0V delay:26ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:100.7m Distance:49.9m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.0V delay:28ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:100.7m Distance:49.9m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.0V delay:29ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:100.8m Distance:49.9m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:30ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:100.8m Distance:49.9m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:32ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:100.8m Distance:49.9m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:30ms bitrate:50.5Mbps Height:100.8m Distance:49.9m HS:0.4m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:28ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:100.8m Distance:49.7m HS:0.8m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:29ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:100.8m Distance:49.7m HS:0.8m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:30ms bitrate:50.5Mbps Height:100.8m Distance:49.5m HS:1.3m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:25ms bitrate:50.5Mbps Height:100.8m Distance:49.3m HS:1.7m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:33ms bitrate:50.4Mbps Height:100.8m Distance:48.9m HS:2.2m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:27ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:100.8m Distance:48.9m HS:2.2m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:29ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:100.8m Distance:48.4m HS:2.7m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:30ms bitrate:50.5Mbps Height:100.8m Distance:47.9m HS:3.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:31ms bitrate:50.5Mbps Height:100.7m Distance:47.3m HS:3.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:26ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:100.7m Distance:47.3m HS:3.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.0V delay:27ms bitrate:50.5Mbps Height:100.7m Distance:46.7m HS:3.1m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.0V delay:29ms bitrate:50.5Mbps Height:100.7m Distance:46.0m HS:3.1m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.0V delay:27ms bitrate:50.5Mbps Height:100.7m Distance:45.4m HS:3.1m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.0V delay:31ms bitrate:50.5Mbps Height:100.7m Distance:45.4m HS:3.1m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.0V delay:26ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:100.7m Distance:44.8m HS:3.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.0V delay:27ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:100.7m Distance:44.2m HS:3.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.0V delay:25ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:100.7m Distance:43.6m HS:3.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.8V delay:27ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:100.7m Distance:43.6m HS:3.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.8V delay:28ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:100.7m Distance:42.9m HS:3.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.8V delay:29ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:100.7m Distance:42.4m HS:2.9m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.8V delay:31ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:100.7m Distance:41.8m HS:2.9m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.8V delay:28ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:100.7m Distance:41.8m HS:2.9m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.8V delay:26ms bitrate:50.5Mbps Height:100.6m Distance:41.2m HS:2.9m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.4V delay:28ms bitrate:50.5Mbps Height:100.6m Distance:40.7m HS:2.9m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.4V delay:29ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:100.6m Distance:40.1m HS:2.9m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.4V delay:30ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:100.6m Distance:40.1m HS:2.9m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.4V delay:25ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:100.6m Distance:39.5m HS:2.9m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.4V delay:29ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:100.6m Distance:39.0m HS:2.9m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.4V delay:28ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:100.6m Distance:38.4m HS:2.9m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.4V delay:29ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:100.6m Distance:38.4m HS:2.9m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:30ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:100.6m Distance:37.8m HS:2.9m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:32ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:100.6m Distance:37.3m HS:2.9m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:26ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:100.6m Distance:36.7m HS:3.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:27ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:100.6m Distance:36.7m HS:3.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:29ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:100.6m Distance:36.1m HS:3.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:30ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:100.6m Distance:35.5m HS:3.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:31ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:100.6m Distance:35.0m HS:3.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:33ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:100.6m Distance:35.0m HS:3.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:27ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:100.6m Distance:34.4m HS:3.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:25ms bitrate:50.5Mbps Height:100.6m Distance:33.8m HS:3.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:30ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:100.6m Distance:33.2m HS:3.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:28ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:100.6m Distance:33.2m HS:3.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:26ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:100.6m Distance:32.6m HS:3.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.4V delay:32ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:100.6m Distance:32.0m HS:3.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.4V delay:28ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:100.6m Distance:31.5m HS:3.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.4V delay:27ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:100.6m Distance:31.5m HS:3.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.4V delay:28ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:100.6m Distance:30.9m HS:2.9m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.4V delay:29ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:100.6m Distance:30.3m HS:2.9m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.4V delay:31ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:100.7m Distance:29.7m HS:3.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.4V delay:29ms bitrate:50.4Mbps Height:100.6m Distance:29.2m HS:3.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.6V delay:30ms bitrate:50.4Mbps Height:100.6m Distance:29.2m HS:3.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.6V delay:28ms bitrate:50.4Mbps Height:100.6m Distance:28.6m HS:2.9m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.6V delay:29ms bitrate:50.5Mbps Height:100.6m Distance:28.0m HS:2.9m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.6V delay:27ms bitrate:50.5Mbps Height:100.6m Distance:27.4m HS:3.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.6V delay:32ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:100.6m Distance:27.4m HS:3.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.6V delay:26ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:100.6m Distance:26.8m HS:2.9m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.6V delay:28ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:100.6m Distance:26.3m HS:2.9m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:29ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:100.6m Distance:25.8m HS:2.9m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:27ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:100.6m Distance:25.8m HS:2.9m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:25ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:100.6m Distance:25.2m HS:2.9m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:31ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:100.6m Distance:24.6m HS:2.9m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:31ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:100.5m Distance:24.0m HS:2.9m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:26ms bitrate:50.5Mbps Height:100.5m Distance:24.0m HS:2.9m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:27ms bitrate:50.5Mbps Height:100.6m Distance:23.5m HS:3.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:31ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:100.6m Distance:22.9m HS:3.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:30ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:100.6m Distance:22.3m HS:3.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:31ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:100.6m Distance:22.3m HS:3.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:32ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:100.6m Distance:21.7m HS:3.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:27ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:100.7m Distance:21.1m HS:3.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:28ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:100.7m Distance:20.5m HS:3.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:30ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:100.7m Distance:20.5m HS:3.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:28ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:100.7m Distance:19.9m HS:3.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:25ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:100.7m Distance:19.3m HS:3.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:34ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:100.7m Distance:18.8m HS:3.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:25ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:100.7m Distance:18.8m HS:3.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:26ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:100.7m Distance:18.2m HS:3.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:28ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:100.7m Distance:17.6m HS:2.9m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.9V delay:29ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:100.7m Distance:17.0m HS:2.9m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.9V delay:27ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:100.7m Distance:17.0m HS:2.9m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.9V delay:28ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:100.7m Distance:16.4m HS:2.9m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.9V delay:29ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:100.7m Distance:15.9m HS:3.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.9V delay:31ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:100.7m Distance:15.3m HS:3.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.9V delay:29ms bitrate:50.5Mbps Height:100.7m Distance:15.3m HS:3.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:30ms bitrate:50.5Mbps Height:100.7m Distance:14.7m HS:3.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:31ms bitrate:50.5Mbps Height:100.7m Distance:14.1m HS:3.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:26ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:100.7m Distance:13.6m HS:3.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:27ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:100.7m Distance:13.6m HS:3.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:29ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:100.7m Distance:13.0m HS:2.9m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:27ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:100.7m Distance:12.4m HS:2.9m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:31ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:100.7m Distance:11.8m HS:2.9m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:33ms bitrate:50.4Mbps Height:100.7m Distance:11.8m HS:2.9m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:27ms bitrate:50.4Mbps Height:100.7m Distance:11.3m HS:2.9m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:32ms bitrate:50.4Mbps Height:100.7m Distance:10.7m HS:2.8m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:30ms bitrate:50.4Mbps Height:100.7m Distance:10.1m HS:2.9m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:31ms bitrate:50.4Mbps Height:100.7m Distance:10.1m HS:2.9m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:26ms bitrate:50.4Mbps Height:100.7m Distance:9.5m HS:2.9m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:34ms bitrate:50.4Mbps Height:100.7m Distance:9.0m HS:2.9m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.7V delay:28ms bitrate:50.4Mbps Height:100.7m Distance:8.4m HS:2.9m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.7V delay:30ms bitrate:50.4Mbps Height:100.7m Distance:8.4m HS:2.9m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.7V delay:31ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:100.7m Distance:7.8m HS:2.9m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.7V delay:32ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:100.7m Distance:7.2m HS:2.9m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.7V delay:27ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:100.7m Distance:6.6m HS:2.9m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.7V delay:29ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:100.7m Distance:6.1m HS:2.9m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.8V delay:29ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:100.7m Distance:6.1m HS:2.9m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.8V delay:31ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:100.7m Distance:5.5m HS:3.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.8V delay:25ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:100.7m Distance:4.9m HS:2.9m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.8V delay:33ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:100.7m Distance:4.9m HS:2.9m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.8V delay:28ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:100.7m Distance:4.4m HS:2.9m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.8V delay:26ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:100.7m Distance:3.8m HS:2.8m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.8V delay:31ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:100.7m Distance:3.3m HS:2.5m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:32ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:100.7m Distance:3.3m HS:2.5m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:26ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:100.7m Distance:2.8m HS:2.2m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:28ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:100.7m Distance:2.3m HS:1.8m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:29ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:100.7m Distance:2.0m HS:1.6m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:30ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:100.7m Distance:2.0m HS:1.6m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:29ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:100.7m Distance:1.7m HS:1.3m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:30ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:100.7m Distance:1.5m HS:1.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:24ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:100.7m Distance:1.3m HS:0.9m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:26ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:100.7m Distance:1.3m HS:0.9m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:27ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:100.7m Distance:1.2m HS:0.7m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:28ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:100.7m Distance:1.0m HS:0.6m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:30ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:100.7m Distance:1.0m HS:0.5m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:24ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:100.7m Distance:1.0m HS:0.5m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:26ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:100.7m Distance:0.9m HS:0.5m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:34ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:100.7m Distance:0.8m HS:0.4m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:28ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:100.8m Distance:0.8m HS:0.3m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:30ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:100.8m Distance:0.8m HS:0.3m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:32ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:100.8m Distance:0.7m HS:0.3m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:25ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:100.8m Distance:0.7m HS:0.3m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:27ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:100.8m Distance:0.6m HS:0.3m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.7V delay:29ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:100.8m Distance:0.6m HS:0.2m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.7V delay:31ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:100.8m Distance:0.5m HS:0.2m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.7V delay:32ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:100.8m Distance:0.5m HS:0.2m/s VS:0.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.7V delay:27ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:100.8m Distance:0.5m HS:0.2m/s VS:0.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.7V delay:25ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:100.8m Distance:0.5m HS:0.1m/s VS:0.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.7V delay:26ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:100.8m Distance:0.4m HS:0.1m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.8V delay:28ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:100.8m Distance:0.4m HS:0.1m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.8V delay:29ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:100.8m Distance:0.4m HS:0.1m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.8V delay:30ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:100.8m Distance:0.4m HS:0.1m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.8V delay:28ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:100.8m Distance:0.3m HS:0.1m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.8V delay:26ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:100.8m Distance:0.3m HS:0.1m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.8V delay:27ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:100.8m Distance:0.3m HS:0.1m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:29ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:100.8m Distance:0.3m HS:0.1m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:30ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:100.8m Distance:0.3m HS:0.1m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:34ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:100.8m Distance:0.3m HS:0.1m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:27ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:100.8m Distance:0.2m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:30ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:100.8m Distance:0.2m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:29ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:100.8m Distance:0.2m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:34ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:100.8m Distance:0.2m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:31ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:100.8m Distance:0.2m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:26ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:100.8m Distance:0.2m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:30ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:100.8m Distance:0.2m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:28ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:100.8m Distance:0.2m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:31ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:100.8m Distance:0.2m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.8V delay:32ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:100.7m Distance:0.2m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.8V delay:27ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:100.7m Distance:0.3m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.8V delay:28ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:100.7m Distance:0.3m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.8V delay:26ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:100.7m Distance:0.3m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.8V delay:32ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:100.7m Distance:0.3m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.8V delay:34ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:100.7m Distance:0.3m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.8V delay:28ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:100.7m Distance:0.3m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.8V delay:26ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:100.7m Distance:0.3m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.8V delay:28ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:100.7m Distance:0.4m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.8V delay:29ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:100.7m Distance:0.4m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.8V delay:26ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:100.7m Distance:0.4m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.8V delay:28ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:100.7m Distance:0.4m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.8V delay:26ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:100.7m Distance:0.4m HS:0.1m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:27ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:100.7m Distance:0.4m HS:0.1m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:25ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:100.7m Distance:0.5m HS:0.1m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:30ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:100.7m Distance:0.5m HS:0.1m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:31ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:100.7m Distance:0.5m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:26ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:100.7m Distance:0.5m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:27ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:100.7m Distance:0.5m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:29ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:100.8m Distance:0.5m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:30ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:100.8m Distance:0.5m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:31ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:100.9m Distance:0.5m HS:0.1m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:33ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:100.9m Distance:0.5m HS:0.1m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:34ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:100.8m Distance:0.5m HS:0.1m/s VS:0.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:28ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:100.7m Distance:0.5m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:30ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:100.7m Distance:0.5m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:31ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:100.7m Distance:0.5m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:26ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:100.6m Distance:0.5m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:27ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:100.6m Distance:0.5m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:33ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:100.6m Distance:0.5m HS:0.1m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:26ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:100.6m Distance:0.5m HS:0.1m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:31ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:100.5m Distance:0.5m HS:0.3m/s VS:0.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:27ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:100.5m Distance:0.5m HS:0.5m/s VS:0.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.9V delay:27ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:100.4m Distance:0.6m HS:0.7m/s VS:0.4m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.9V delay:28ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:100.4m Distance:0.6m HS:0.7m/s VS:0.4m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.9V delay:29ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:100.3m Distance:0.8m HS:0.9m/s VS:0.6m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.9V delay:31ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:100.2m Distance:0.9m HS:1.0m/s VS:0.8m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.9V delay:26ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:100.0m Distance:1.1m HS:1.0m/s VS:0.9m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.9V delay:33ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:100.0m Distance:1.1m HS:1.0m/s VS:0.9m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:28ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:99.8m Distance:1.3m HS:0.9m/s VS:1.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:29ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:99.6m Distance:1.4m HS:0.9m/s VS:1.3m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:27ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:99.3m Distance:1.6m HS:0.9m/s VS:1.6m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:29ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:99.3m Distance:1.6m HS:0.9m/s VS:1.6m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:30ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:99.0m Distance:1.8m HS:0.8m/s VS:1.7m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:25ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:98.6m Distance:2.0m HS:0.8m/s VS:1.9m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:29ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:98.2m Distance:2.1m HS:0.9m/s VS:2.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:27ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:98.2m Distance:2.1m HS:0.9m/s VS:2.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:29ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:97.8m Distance:2.3m HS:0.8m/s VS:2.3m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:30ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:97.4m Distance:2.4m HS:0.7m/s VS:2.5m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:31ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:96.9m Distance:2.6m HS:0.5m/s VS:2.7m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:33ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:96.9m Distance:2.6m HS:0.5m/s VS:2.7m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:27ms bitrate:50.5Mbps Height:96.2m Distance:2.7m HS:0.4m/s VS:3.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:28ms bitrate:50.5Mbps Height:95.6m Distance:2.8m HS:0.4m/s VS:3.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.7V delay:30ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:95.0m Distance:2.8m HS:0.3m/s VS:3.4m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.7V delay:31ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:95.0m Distance:2.8m HS:0.3m/s VS:3.4m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.7V delay:32ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:94.3m Distance:2.9m HS:0.3m/s VS:3.6m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.7V delay:34ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:93.4m Distance:2.9m HS:0.3m/s VS:3.9m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.7V delay:28ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:92.6m Distance:3.0m HS:0.4m/s VS:4.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.7V delay:26ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:92.6m Distance:3.0m HS:0.4m/s VS:4.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.6V delay:31ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:91.8m Distance:3.0m HS:0.3m/s VS:4.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.6V delay:25ms bitrate:50.5Mbps Height:91.0m Distance:3.0m HS:0.2m/s VS:4.4m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.6V delay:27ms bitrate:50.5Mbps Height:90.1m Distance:3.0m HS:0.1m/s VS:4.6m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.6V delay:29ms bitrate:50.5Mbps Height:90.1m Distance:3.0m HS:0.1m/s VS:4.6m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.6V delay:26ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:89.2m Distance:3.1m HS:0.2m/s VS:4.8m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.6V delay:31ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:88.2m Distance:3.1m HS:0.3m/s VS:4.8m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.6V delay:26ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:87.2m Distance:3.1m HS:0.2m/s VS:4.9m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:27ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:87.2m Distance:3.1m HS:0.2m/s VS:4.9m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:25ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:86.2m Distance:3.1m HS:0.2m/s VS:5.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:26ms bitrate:50.5Mbps Height:85.2m Distance:3.1m HS:0.3m/s VS:5.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:27ms bitrate:50.5Mbps Height:84.2m Distance:3.2m HS:0.5m/s VS:5.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:32ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:84.2m Distance:3.2m HS:0.5m/s VS:5.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:30ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:83.2m Distance:3.1m HS:0.7m/s VS:4.9m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:35ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:82.2m Distance:3.1m HS:0.7m/s VS:4.9m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:29ms bitrate:50.3Mbps Height:81.2m Distance:3.1m HS:0.5m/s VS:4.9m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:30ms bitrate:50.3Mbps Height:81.2m Distance:3.1m HS:0.5m/s VS:4.9m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:29ms bitrate:50.0Mbps Height:80.2m Distance:3.1m HS:0.3m/s VS:5.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:28ms bitrate:50.3Mbps Height:79.2m Distance:3.1m HS:0.2m/s VS:5.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:24ms bitrate:50.3Mbps Height:78.2m Distance:3.2m HS:0.4m/s VS:5.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:26ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:78.2m Distance:3.2m HS:0.4m/s VS:5.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:25ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:77.1m Distance:3.2m HS:0.4m/s VS:5.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:35ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:76.1m Distance:3.3m HS:0.6m/s VS:4.8m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:30ms bitrate:50.5Mbps Height:75.2m Distance:3.3m HS:0.6m/s VS:4.9m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:31ms bitrate:50.5Mbps Height:75.2m Distance:3.3m HS:0.6m/s VS:4.9m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:32ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:74.1m Distance:3.4m HS:0.4m/s VS:4.9m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:34ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:73.2m Distance:3.4m HS:0.1m/s VS:4.8m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:28ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:72.2m Distance:3.5m HS:0.3m/s VS:4.8m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:27ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:72.2m Distance:3.5m HS:0.3m/s VS:4.8m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:28ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:71.2m Distance:3.5m HS:0.5m/s VS:5.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:32ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:70.2m Distance:3.5m HS:0.6m/s VS:5.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:34ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:69.2m Distance:3.6m HS:0.7m/s VS:4.9m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:28ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:69.2m Distance:3.6m HS:0.7m/s VS:4.9m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:26ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:68.2m Distance:3.7m HS:0.5m/s VS:4.9m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:28ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:67.3m Distance:3.8m HS:0.5m/s VS:4.9m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.9V delay:27ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:66.2m Distance:3.8m HS:0.6m/s VS:4.9m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.9V delay:30ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:66.2m Distance:3.8m HS:0.6m/s VS:4.9m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.9V delay:25ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:65.3m Distance:3.9m HS:0.9m/s VS:4.9m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.9V delay:26ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:64.3m Distance:3.9m HS:0.9m/s VS:4.9m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.9V delay:28ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:63.3m Distance:4.0m HS:0.9m/s VS:4.9m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.9V delay:29ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:63.3m Distance:4.0m HS:0.9m/s VS:4.9m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:30ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:62.4m Distance:4.1m HS:0.5m/s VS:4.9m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:32ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:61.5m Distance:4.1m HS:0.2m/s VS:5.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:30ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:60.6m Distance:4.1m HS:0.4m/s VS:4.9m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:27ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:60.6m Distance:4.1m HS:0.4m/s VS:4.9m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:26ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:59.7m Distance:4.1m HS:0.5m/s VS:4.9m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:30ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:58.7m Distance:4.0m HS:0.4m/s VS:4.9m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:31ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:57.8m Distance:4.0m HS:0.2m/s VS:5.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:33ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:57.8m Distance:4.0m HS:0.2m/s VS:5.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:27ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:57.0m Distance:3.9m HS:0.2m/s VS:5.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:29ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:56.0m Distance:3.9m HS:0.3m/s VS:4.9m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:34ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:55.1m Distance:3.8m HS:0.4m/s VS:4.9m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:31ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:55.1m Distance:3.8m HS:0.4m/s VS:4.9m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:33ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:54.1m Distance:3.7m HS:0.4m/s VS:4.9m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:27ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:53.2m Distance:3.6m HS:0.4m/s VS:5.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.9V delay:28ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:52.2m Distance:3.6m HS:0.2m/s VS:5.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.9V delay:27ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:52.2m Distance:3.6m HS:0.2m/s VS:5.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.9V delay:28ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:51.2m Distance:3.5m HS:0.0m/s VS:5.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.9V delay:29ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:50.3m Distance:3.5m HS:0.1m/s VS:5.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.9V delay:31ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:49.3m Distance:3.4m HS:0.2m/s VS:5.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.9V delay:28ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:49.3m Distance:3.4m HS:0.2m/s VS:5.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.9V delay:26ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:48.3m Distance:3.4m HS:0.2m/s VS:4.9m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.9V delay:27ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:47.3m Distance:3.4m HS:0.2m/s VS:4.9m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.9V delay:29ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:46.4m Distance:3.4m HS:0.1m/s VS:4.9m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.9V delay:30ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:46.4m Distance:3.4m HS:0.1m/s VS:4.9m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.9V delay:25ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:45.4m Distance:3.4m HS:0.0m/s VS:4.9m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.9V delay:26ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:44.4m Distance:3.4m HS:0.2m/s VS:4.9m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.9V delay:28ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:43.4m Distance:3.3m HS:0.1m/s VS:5.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:29ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:43.4m Distance:3.3m HS:0.1m/s VS:5.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:23ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:42.5m Distance:3.3m HS:0.2m/s VS:4.9m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:26ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:41.5m Distance:3.2m HS:0.2m/s VS:4.9m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:23ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:40.6m Distance:3.2m HS:0.1m/s VS:4.9m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:24ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:40.6m Distance:3.2m HS:0.1m/s VS:4.9m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:22ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:39.6m Distance:3.1m HS:0.2m/s VS:5.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:23ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:38.6m Distance:3.1m HS:0.4m/s VS:4.9m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:25ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:37.7m Distance:3.0m HS:0.5m/s VS:4.8m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:23ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:37.7m Distance:3.0m HS:0.5m/s VS:4.8m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:24ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:36.8m Distance:2.8m HS:0.5m/s VS:4.6m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:25ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:35.9m Distance:2.7m HS:0.4m/s VS:4.5m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:27ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:35.0m Distance:2.6m HS:0.4m/s VS:4.3m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:28ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:35.0m Distance:2.6m HS:0.4m/s VS:4.3m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:29ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:34.2m Distance:2.5m HS:0.6m/s VS:4.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:29ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:33.4m Distance:2.4m HS:0.6m/s VS:4.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:25ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:32.7m Distance:2.3m HS:0.4m/s VS:3.8m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:24ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:31.9m Distance:2.2m HS:0.4m/s VS:3.7m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:28ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:31.9m Distance:2.2m HS:0.4m/s VS:3.7m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:29ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:31.2m Distance:2.1m HS:0.4m/s VS:3.7m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:24ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:30.5m Distance:2.1m HS:0.3m/s VS:3.5m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.9V delay:25ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:29.8m Distance:2.0m HS:0.1m/s VS:3.4m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.9V delay:23ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:29.8m Distance:2.0m HS:0.1m/s VS:3.4m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.9V delay:28ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:29.2m Distance:2.1m HS:0.2m/s VS:3.3m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.9V delay:29ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:28.6m Distance:2.1m HS:0.3m/s VS:3.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.9V delay:30ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:27.9m Distance:2.2m HS:0.3m/s VS:3.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.9V delay:22ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:27.9m Distance:2.2m HS:0.3m/s VS:3.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:23ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:27.4m Distance:2.2m HS:0.4m/s VS:2.9m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:25ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:26.8m Distance:2.3m HS:0.4m/s VS:2.8m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:23ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:26.3m Distance:2.3m HS:0.3m/s VS:2.7m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:25ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:25.7m Distance:2.3m HS:0.3m/s VS:2.6m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:27ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:25.2m Distance:2.3m HS:0.3m/s VS:2.5m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.3V delay:24ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:24.7m Distance:2.3m HS:0.2m/s VS:2.4m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:26ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:24.7m Distance:2.3m HS:0.2m/s VS:2.4m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:28ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:24.2m Distance:2.2m HS:0.1m/s VS:2.4m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:28ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:23.7m Distance:2.2m HS:0.3m/s VS:2.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:23ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:23.3m Distance:2.1m HS:0.3m/s VS:2.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:21ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:23.3m Distance:2.1m HS:0.3m/s VS:2.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:22ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:22.9m Distance:2.1m HS:0.1m/s VS:2.1m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:27ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:22.5m Distance:2.0m HS:0.2m/s VS:2.0m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:28ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:22.1m Distance:1.9m HS:0.2m/s VS:1.9m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:20ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:22.1m Distance:1.9m HS:0.2m/s VS:1.9m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:31ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:21.7m Distance:1.8m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.9m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:25ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:21.3m Distance:1.8m HS:0.2m/s VS:1.8m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:24ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:21.0m Distance:1.8m HS:0.1m/s VS:1.7m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:25ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:21.0m Distance:1.8m HS:0.1m/s VS:1.7m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:26ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:20.6m Distance:1.8m HS:0.1m/s VS:1.7m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:24ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:20.3m Distance:1.8m HS:0.2m/s VS:1.6m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:29ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:20.0m Distance:1.8m HS:0.2m/s VS:1.6m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:23ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:20.0m Distance:1.8m HS:0.2m/s VS:1.6m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:25ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:19.7m Distance:1.8m HS:0.1m/s VS:1.5m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:27ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:19.4m Distance:1.9m HS:0.1m/s VS:1.4m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:27ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:19.1m Distance:1.9m HS:0.1m/s VS:1.4m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:29ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:19.1m Distance:1.9m HS:0.1m/s VS:1.4m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:24ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:18.9m Distance:1.9m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.4m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:25ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:18.6m Distance:1.9m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.4m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:26ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:18.3m Distance:1.9m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.4m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:29ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:18.0m Distance:1.9m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.4m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:20ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:17.7m Distance:1.9m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.4m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.6V delay:28ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:17.4m Distance:1.9m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.4m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.6V delay:23ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:17.4m Distance:1.9m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.4m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.6V delay:25ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:17.2m Distance:1.9m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.4m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.6V delay:28ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:16.9m Distance:2.0m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.4m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.6V delay:30ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:16.6m Distance:2.0m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.4m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.6V delay:24ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:16.6m Distance:2.0m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.4m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:22ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:16.3m Distance:2.0m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.3m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:27ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:16.1m Distance:2.0m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.4m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:28ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:15.8m Distance:2.0m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.3m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:23ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:15.8m Distance:2.0m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.3m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:25ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:15.6m Distance:2.0m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.3m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:25ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:15.3m Distance:2.0m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.3m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:24ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:15.0m Distance:2.0m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.3m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:25ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:15.0m Distance:2.0m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.3m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:26ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:14.8m Distance:2.0m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.3m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:25ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:14.5m Distance:1.9m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.3m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:25ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:14.3m Distance:1.9m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.3m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:23ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:14.3m Distance:1.9m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.3m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:26ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:14.0m Distance:1.9m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.3m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:26ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:13.7m Distance:1.9m HS:0.1m/s VS:1.3m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.9V delay:27ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:13.5m Distance:1.9m HS:0.1m/s VS:1.3m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.9V delay:29ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:13.5m Distance:1.9m HS:0.1m/s VS:1.3m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.9V delay:23ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:13.2m Distance:1.8m HS:0.1m/s VS:1.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.9V delay:25ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:13.0m Distance:1.8m HS:0.1m/s VS:1.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.9V delay:26ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:12.7m Distance:1.7m HS:0.1m/s VS:1.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.9V delay:27ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:12.7m Distance:1.7m HS:0.1m/s VS:1.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:27ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:12.5m Distance:1.7m HS:0.1m/s VS:1.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:30ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:12.2m Distance:1.6m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:24ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:12.0m Distance:1.6m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:26ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:12.0m Distance:1.6m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:27ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:11.8m Distance:1.6m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:22ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:11.5m Distance:1.6m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:23ms bitrate:50.5Mbps Height:11.3m Distance:1.6m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:24ms bitrate:50.5Mbps Height:11.3m Distance:1.6m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:24ms bitrate:50.5Mbps Height:11.1m Distance:1.6m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:24ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:10.8m Distance:1.6m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:25ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:10.6m Distance:1.6m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:27ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:10.6m Distance:1.6m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:24ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:10.3m Distance:1.6m HS:0.1m/s VS:1.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:22ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:10.1m Distance:1.6m HS:0.1m/s VS:1.2m/s gpsNum:27
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.7V delay:24ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:9.8m Distance:1.6m HS:0.1m/s VS:1.2m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.7V delay:25ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:9.8m Distance:1.6m HS:0.1m/s VS:1.2m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.7V delay:26ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:9.6m Distance:1.7m HS:0.1m/s VS:1.1m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.7V delay:28ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:9.3m Distance:1.7m HS:0.1m/s VS:1.2m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.7V delay:29ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:9.1m Distance:1.7m HS:0.1m/s VS:1.2m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.7V delay:23ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:9.1m Distance:1.7m HS:0.1m/s VS:1.2m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:22ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:8.9m Distance:1.8m HS:0.1m/s VS:1.1m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:23ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:8.6m Distance:1.7m HS:0.1m/s VS:1.1m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:24ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:8.4m Distance:1.7m HS:0.1m/s VS:1.1m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:29ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:8.4m Distance:1.7m HS:0.1m/s VS:1.1m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:23ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:8.2m Distance:1.7m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.1m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:22ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:8.0m Distance:1.7m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.1m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.7V delay:24ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:7.7m Distance:1.6m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.1m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.7V delay:26ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:7.5m Distance:1.6m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.1m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.7V delay:27ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:7.3m Distance:1.6m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.1m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.7V delay:24ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:7.1m Distance:1.6m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.1m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.7V delay:23ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:7.1m Distance:1.6m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.1m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.7V delay:24ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:6.9m Distance:1.6m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.1m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.8V delay:25ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:6.7m Distance:1.6m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.1m/s gpsNum:25
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.8V delay:27ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:6.5m Distance:1.5m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.0m/s gpsNum:25
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.8V delay:21ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:6.5m Distance:1.5m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.0m/s gpsNum:25
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.8V delay:23ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:6.2m Distance:1.5m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.0m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.8V delay:21ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:6.0m Distance:1.5m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.0m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.8V delay:25ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:5.8m Distance:1.5m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.0m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.8V delay:27ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:5.6m Distance:1.5m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.0m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.8V delay:28ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:5.6m Distance:1.5m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.0m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.8V delay:22ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:5.4m Distance:1.5m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.0m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.8V delay:24ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:5.2m Distance:1.5m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.0m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.8V delay:25ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:5.0m Distance:1.5m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.0m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.8V delay:26ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:5.0m Distance:1.5m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.0m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.8V delay:25ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:4.8m Distance:1.5m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.0m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.8V delay:26ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:4.6m Distance:1.5m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.0m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.8V delay:27ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:4.4m Distance:1.5m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.0m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.8V delay:23ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:4.4m Distance:1.5m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.0m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.8V delay:23ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:4.2m Distance:1.5m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.0m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.8V delay:24ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:4.1m Distance:1.5m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.0m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.8V delay:30ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:3.9m Distance:1.5m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.0m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:8.8V delay:27ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:3.9m Distance:1.5m HS:0.0m/s VS:1.0m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.6V delay:28ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:3.7m Distance:1.4m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.9m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.6V delay:27ms bitrate:50.5Mbps Height:3.5m Distance:1.4m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.9m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.6V delay:31ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:3.3m Distance:1.4m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.8m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.6V delay:26ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:3.3m Distance:1.4m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.8m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.6V delay:24ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:3.2m Distance:1.4m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.5m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.6V delay:28ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:3.1m Distance:1.5m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.3m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.6V delay:30ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:3.0m Distance:1.5m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.2m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:24ms bitrate:50.5Mbps Height:3.0m Distance:1.5m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.2m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:25ms bitrate:50.5Mbps Height:3.0m Distance:1.5m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.2m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:24ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:2.9m Distance:1.5m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.2m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:28ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:2.9m Distance:1.5m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.2m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:29ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:2.9m Distance:1.5m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.2m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:24ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:2.9m Distance:1.5m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.1m/s gpsNum:26
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:22ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:2.8m Distance:1.5m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.1m/s gpsNum:25
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:23ms bitrate:50.1Mbps Height:2.8m Distance:1.5m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.1m/s gpsNum:25
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:26ms bitrate:50.2Mbps Height:2.8m Distance:1.5m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.2m/s gpsNum:25
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:24ms bitrate:50.5Mbps Height:2.7m Distance:1.5m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.2m/s gpsNum:25
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:26ms bitrate:50.5Mbps Height:2.7m Distance:1.6m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.2m/s gpsNum:25
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:23ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:2.7m Distance:1.6m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.2m/s gpsNum:25
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:25ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:2.6m Distance:1.6m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.2m/s gpsNum:25
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:29ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:2.6m Distance:1.6m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.2m/s gpsNum:25
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:27ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:2.5m Distance:1.6m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.2m/s gpsNum:25
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:29ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:2.5m Distance:1.6m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.2m/s gpsNum:25
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:23ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:2.5m Distance:1.6m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.2m/s gpsNum:25
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:21ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:2.4m Distance:1.6m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.1m/s gpsNum:24
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:26ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:2.4m Distance:1.5m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.1m/s gpsNum:24
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:24ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:2.4m Distance:1.5m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.1m/s gpsNum:24
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:22ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:2.4m Distance:1.6m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.2m/s gpsNum:24
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:23ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:2.3m Distance:1.6m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.2m/s gpsNum:24
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:21ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:2.3m Distance:1.6m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.2m/s gpsNum:24
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:23ms bitrate:50.4Mbps Height:2.3m Distance:1.6m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.2m/s gpsNum:24
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:27ms bitrate:50.4Mbps Height:2.2m Distance:1.6m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.2m/s gpsNum:24
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:28ms bitrate:50.4Mbps Height:2.2m Distance:1.6m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.2m/s gpsNum:24
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.7V delay:30ms bitrate:50.3Mbps Height:2.2m Distance:1.6m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.2m/s gpsNum:24
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.7V delay:31ms bitrate:50.3Mbps Height:2.2m Distance:1.6m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.2m/s gpsNum:24
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.7V delay:25ms bitrate:50.5Mbps Height:2.1m Distance:1.6m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.2m/s gpsNum:24
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.7V delay:24ms bitrate:50.3Mbps Height:2.1m Distance:1.6m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.2m/s gpsNum:24
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.7V delay:28ms bitrate:50.3Mbps Height:2.0m Distance:1.6m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.3m/s gpsNum:24
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.7V delay:30ms bitrate:50.4Mbps Height:2.0m Distance:1.6m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.3m/s gpsNum:24
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.7V delay:26ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:1.9m Distance:1.6m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.5m/s gpsNum:24
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.7V delay:32ms bitrate:50.6Mbps Height:1.8m Distance:1.6m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.5m/s gpsNum:24
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.7V delay:34ms bitrate:50.4Mbps Height:1.7m Distance:1.6m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.5m/s gpsNum:24
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.7V delay:28ms bitrate:50.4Mbps Height:1.7m Distance:1.6m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.5m/s gpsNum:24
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.7V delay:22ms bitrate:50.5Mbps Height:1.6m Distance:1.6m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.5m/s gpsNum:24
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.7V delay:24ms bitrate:50.5Mbps Height:1.5m Distance:1.6m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.4m/s gpsNum:24
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.7V delay:26ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:1.4m Distance:1.6m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.3m/s gpsNum:24
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.7V delay:23ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:1.4m Distance:1.6m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.3m/s gpsNum:24
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.7V delay:25ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:1.4m Distance:1.7m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.3m/s gpsNum:23
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.7V delay:26ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:1.3m Distance:1.6m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.3m/s gpsNum:23
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.7V delay:27ms bitrate:50.7Mbps Height:1.2m Distance:1.6m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.2m/s gpsNum:23
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.7V delay:22ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:1.2m Distance:1.6m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.2m/s gpsNum:23
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.7V delay:26ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:1.2m Distance:1.6m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.2m/s gpsNum:22
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.7V delay:25ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:1.1m Distance:1.6m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.2m/s gpsNum:22
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:9.0V delay:26ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:1.1m Distance:1.6m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.1m/s gpsNum:22
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:9.0V delay:27ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:1.1m Distance:1.6m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.1m/s gpsNum:22
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:9.0V delay:29ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:1.1m Distance:1.6m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.1m/s gpsNum:22
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:9.0V delay:30ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:1.0m Distance:1.6m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.1m/s gpsNum:22
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:9.0V delay:24ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:1.0m Distance:1.6m HS:0.1m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:22
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:9.0V delay:26ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:1.0m Distance:1.6m HS:0.1m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:22
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:27ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:1.0m Distance:1.6m HS:0.1m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:22
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:28ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:1.0m Distance:1.6m HS:0.1m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:22
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:20ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:1.0m Distance:1.6m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:22
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:28ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:1.0m Distance:1.6m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:22
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:26ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:1.0m Distance:1.6m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:22
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:24ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:1.0m Distance:1.6m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:22
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.5V delay:25ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:1.0m Distance:1.6m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:22
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:23ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:1.0m Distance:1.6m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:22
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:22ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:1.0m Distance:1.6m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:22
signal:N/A ch:N/A flightTime:N/A uavBat:N/A glsBat:7.4V delay:25ms bitrate:50.8Mbps Height:1.0m Distance:1.6m HS:0.0m/s VS:0.0m/s gpsNum:22